[
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'budoo'?",
      "options": [
        "すばらしい",
        "ぶどう",
        "たいへん（な）",
        "ファーストフードてん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ぶどう"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'スリランカ'?",
      "options": [
        "tsuma",
        "Suriranka",
        "soba",
        "nori"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Suriranka"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to copy'?",
      "options": [
        "コピー",
        "おそい",
        "インド",
        "ひきます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "コピー"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'student'?",
      "options": [
        "shoppai",
        "soto",
        "kiree",
        "gakusee"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "gakusee"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tatami'?",
      "options": [
        "うたいます",
        "シリアル",
        "がくせい",
        "たたみ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "たたみ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Ajia'?",
      "options": [
        "おきます",
        "かのじょ",
        "えび",
        "アジア"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "アジア"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'にんぎょう'?",
      "options": [
        "eega",
        "ningyoo",
        "hashi",
        "ongaku o kikimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ningyoo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for '〜 ya (san)'?",
      "options": [
        "scary / frightening",
        "〜 shop / restaurant",
        "anime / animated cartoons",
        "udon noodles"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜 shop / restaurant"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'door'?",
      "options": [
        "kowai",
        "kissaten",
        "uisukii",
        "doa"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "doa"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'byooin'?",
      "options": [
        "みます",
        "びょういん",
        "コンテスト",
        "タイ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "びょういん"
    },
    
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'あつい'?",
      "options": [
        "butaniku / pooku",
        "Nihonjin",
        "hanabi-taikai",
        "atsui"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "atsui"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'cola'?",
      "options": [
        "アイロン",
        "コーラ",
        "バーベキュー",
        "おどり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "コーラ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ryoori (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "answer",
        "fireworks",
        "to keep a diary",
        "to cook"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to cook"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'りんご'?",
      "options": [
        "kopii (o) shimasu",
        "ringo",
        "keeki",
        "konsaato"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ringo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'やさしい'?",
      "options": [
        "yasashii",
        "uta",
        "yoshuu",
        "jogingu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "yasashii"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'karendaa'?",
      "options": [
        "〜を　あげます",
        "ようしつ",
        "カレ ンダー",
        "かたづけます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "カレ ンダー"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'sandwich'?",
      "options": [
        "sandoicchi",
        "hashi",
        "mikan",
        "sobo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sandoicchi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'くらい'?",
      "options": [
        "dark",
        "(someone else's) elder sister",
        "watermelon",
        "baseball"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "dark"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ロック'?",
      "options": [
        "sofa",
        "Arabic language",
        "butter",
        "rock music"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "rock music"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ふるい'?",
      "options": [
        "to go to 〜",
        "homework",
        "old",
        "to look"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "old"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'katazukemasu'?",
      "options": [
        "かたづけます",
        "〜に　いきます",
        "おてら／てら",
        "べんきょう（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かたづけます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'supagethi (pasuta)'?",
      "options": [
        "ほんだな",
        "じむしつ",
        "スパゲティ（パスタ）",
        "おとうと"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "スパゲティ（パスタ）"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'chiizu-baagaa'?",
      "options": [
        "orange juice",
        "cheese burger",
        "review",
        "to ask a question"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "cheese burger"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'うんどう（を）します'?",
      "options": [
        "yoshuu",
        "undoo (o) shimasu",
        "gaikoku",
        "Eego"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "undoo (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'momijigari'?",
      "options": [
        "にほんりょうり",
        "キャベツ",
        "おみやげ",
        "もみじがり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "もみじがり"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'friend'?",
      "options": [
        "わたしたち",
        "ともだち",
        "けいようし",
        "フランス"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ともだち"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'taihen'?",
      "options": [
        "things (found at home)",
        "baggage / luggage",
        "terrible",
        "to go to 〜"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "terrible"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'biza'?",
      "options": [
        "ビザ",
        "ベランダ",
        "つめたい",
        "ページ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ビザ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'autumn festival'?",
      "options": [
        "ちかく",
        "ちゃわん",
        "あきま つり",
        "ダンス"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "あきま つり"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'dokusho'?",
      "options": [
        "どくしょ",
        "じゅこうしゃ",
        "みなさん",
        "スポーツ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "どくしょ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'suzushii'?",
      "options": [
        "homework",
        "tomato",
        "Golden Week holidays",
        "cool"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "cool"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ソファ'?",
      "options": [
        "kare",
        "ii",
        "keetai-denwa",
        "sofa"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sofa"
    },
    
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for '〜が　できます'?",
      "options": [
        "hanami",
        "〜ga dekimasu",
        "Kankoku",
        "juudoo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜ga dekimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'nagai'?",
      "options": [
        "swimming",
        "small / cramped",
        "pen",
        "long"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "long"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'じゅこうしゃ'?",
      "options": [
        "cookie",
        "China",
        "participant",
        "to go home"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "participant"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'expensive'?",
      "options": [
        "ダンス",
        "かおを　あらいます",
        "ときどき",
        "たかい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "たかい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'メキシコ'?",
      "options": [
        "matsuri",
        "satoo",
        "Mekishiko",
        "otoko"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Mekishiko"
    },
    
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'hanbaagaa'?",
      "options": [
        "school",
        "I",
        "cold",
        "hamburger"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hamburger"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'jinja'?",
      "options": [
        "example",
        "shrine",
        "trip / to go on a trip",
        "comedy"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shrine"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'Sumo'?",
      "options": [
        "yoshuu",
        "sumoo",
        "zangyoo (o) shimasu",
        "momijigari"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sumoo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'タイ'?",
      "options": [
        "Tai",
        "natsu-yasumi",
        "suki",
        "kirai"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Tai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'greetings'?",
      "options": [
        "あいさつ",
        "おふろ",
        "〜の　せわをします",
        "バスケットボール"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "あいさつ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to sing'?",
      "options": [
        "utaimasu",
        "niku",
        "ane",
        "kissaten"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "utaimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'おふろ'?",
      "options": [
        "intaanetto (o) shimasu",
        "gooruden-uiiku",
        "ofuro",
        "shoosetsu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ofuro"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'daidokoro'?",
      "options": [
        "kitchen",
        "iron",
        "people from … (nationality)",
        "reading"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kitchen"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'hako'?",
      "options": [
        "はこ",
        "つくえ",
        "J ポップ",
        "にっきを　かきます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "はこ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'konpyuutaa'?",
      "options": [
        "souvenir",
        "cat",
        "slow",
        "computer"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "computer"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'しんぶんを　よみます'?",
      "options": [
        "long",
        "company / firm",
        "to explain",
        "to read a newspaper"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to read a newspaper"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'tidy / clean'?",
      "options": [
        "soodan (o) shimasu",
        "takusan",
        "kiree",
        "Tookyoo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kiree"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'うんどう（を）します'?",
      "options": [
        "toilet",
        "〜 food / 〜 cuisine",
        "to do exercise",
        "card"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to do exercise"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Kanada'?",
      "options": [
        "うどん",
        "〜じん",
        "ラーメン",
        "カナダ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "カナダ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'people / person'?",
      "options": [
        "ひと",
        "まど",
        "かきます",
        "ふゆやすみ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ひと"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'あに'?",
      "options": [
        "butter",
        "(my) elder brother",
        "museum",
        "fireworks"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(my) elder brother"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'delicious / tasty'?",
      "options": [
        "ワイン",
        "あつい",
        "おいしい",
        "サンドイッチ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おいしい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'onna'?",
      "options": [
        "〜の　せわをします",
        "すばらしい",
        "おんな",
        "インド"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おんな"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'すいえい'?",
      "options": [
        "swimming",
        "grape picking",
        "Brazil",
        "karaoke"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "swimming"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'konsaato'?",
      "options": [
        "concert",
        "to play",
        "to work / do one's job",
        "to look"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "concert"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'J ポップ'?",
      "options": [
        "you",
        "textbook",
        "always",
        "Japanese pop music"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Japanese pop music"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'たくさん'?",
      "options": [
        "light",
        "a lot",
        "sliding door",
        "foreign country"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "a lot"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'Arabic language'?",
      "options": [
        "ha o migakimasu",
        "Arabiago",
        "e (o kakimasu)",
        "chekku (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Arabiago"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'skating'?",
      "options": [
        "Nihongo",
        "Eego",
        "tsukue",
        "sukeeto"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sukeeto"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'tsukue'?",
      "options": [
        "onion",
        "France",
        "desk",
        "grape picking"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "desk"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'utaimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "にわ",
        "ちいさい",
        "うたいます",
        "じえいぎょう"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "うたいます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'teeburu'?",
      "options": [
        "friend",
        "Malaysia",
        "manga / comic strips / comic books",
        "table"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "table"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to stop over / to stay at (a hotel)'?",
      "options": [
        "こうむいん",
        "バター",
        "アクション",
        "〜に　とまりま す"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜に　とまりま す"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'あまり'?",
      "options": [
        "autumn-leaf viewing",
        "(not) many / (not) much",
        "review",
        "bird"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(not) many / (not) much"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'しゃしん（を　とります）'?",
      "options": [
        "office / company / firm",
        "jam",
        "photograph (to take a photo)",
        "to listen"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "photograph (to take a photo)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to put on clothes'?",
      "options": [
        "チェック（を）します",
        "ふくを　きます",
        "オーストラリア",
        "しゃしん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ふくを　きます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'おさけ／さけ'?",
      "options": [
        "alcoholic drinks / Japanese sake",
        "wall",
        "to drink 〜",
        "orange juice"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "alcoholic drinks / Japanese sake"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'hot'?",
      "options": [
        "shokki",
        "undoo (o) shimasu",
        "atsui",
        "karendaa"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "atsui"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'beddo-ruumu'?",
      "options": [
        "summer festival",
        "bedroom",
        "refrigerator",
        "meal"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "bedroom"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'summer holidays'?",
      "options": [
        "basuketto-booru",
        "natsu-yasumi",
        "rooka",
        "konsaato"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "natsu-yasumi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'wasabi (Japanese horseradish)'?",
      "options": [
        "wasabi",
        "bungaku",
        "denshi-renji",
        "nikki o kakimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "wasabi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for '〜を　あげます'?",
      "options": [
        "French language",
        "to give",
        "doll",
        "strawberry"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to give"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ゲーム'?",
      "options": [
        "video game / computer game",
        "fireworks",
        "knife",
        "the Philippines"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "video game / computer game"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'gyuuniku / biifu'?",
      "options": [
        "beef",
        "(someone else's) grandmother",
        "calendar",
        "participant"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "beef"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ベッド'?",
      "options": [
        "people from … (nationality)",
        "Asia",
        "to practice",
        "bed"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "bed"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'coffee'?",
      "options": [
        "〜 ni nite imasu ne",
        "fukushuu",
        "koohii",
        "Nyuujiirando"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "koohii"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to smoke'?",
      "options": [
        "りょうしん",
        "たばこを　すいます",
        "ペン",
        "まど"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "たばこを　すいます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ひろい'?",
      "options": [
        "shashin (o torimasu)",
        "hiroi",
        "eega",
        "subarashii"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hiroi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'summer festival'?",
      "options": [
        "oinori (o) shimasu",
        "natsu-matsuri",
        "niwa",
        "esu-efu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "natsu-matsuri"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'たいへん（な）'?",
      "options": [
        "oinori (o) shimasu",
        "kyooshi",
        "taihen",
        "chokoreeto"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "taihen"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'chokoreeto'?",
      "options": [
        "でんわ",
        "けいようし",
        "チョコレート",
        "しょっき"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "チョコレート"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kyanpu (o shimasu)'?",
      "options": [
        "class / lesson",
        "camping / to go camping",
        "pork",
        "salt"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "camping / to go camping"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'さら'?",
      "options": [
        "banana",
        "yooshitsu",
        "sara",
        "ningyoo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sara"
    },
    
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'photograph (to take a photo)'?",
      "options": [
        "〜 o moraimasu",
        "denki",
        "shashin (o torimasu)",
        "gyuuniku / biifu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shashin (o torimasu)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'jogingu'?",
      "options": [
        "せんぷうき",
        "はこ",
        "ゴルフ",
        "ジョギング"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ジョギング"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'busy'?",
      "options": [
        "いそがしい",
        "パンフレット",
        "〜を　のみます",
        "ゴールデンウィーク"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "いそがしい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'hoteru'?",
      "options": [
        "〜や（さん）",
        "ホ テル",
        "もの",
        "ベランダ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ホ テル"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'leaflet / flyer'?",
      "options": [
        "レモン",
        "ほんだな",
        "おこさん",
        "チラシ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "チラシ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ちゅうごくご'?",
      "options": [
        "Chinese language",
        "literature",
        "chopsticks",
        "preparation (for the lesson)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Chinese language"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'sukoshi'?",
      "options": [
        "フランス",
        "でんわ",
        "アイス",
        "すこし"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "すこし"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ほんだな'?",
      "options": [
        "girl",
        "bookshelf",
        "question / problem",
        "strawberry"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "bookshelf"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'poster'?",
      "options": [
        "posutaa",
        "naka",
        "orenji-juusu",
        "osushi / sushi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "posutaa"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ikebana'?",
      "options": [
        "flower arrangement",
        "Spanish language",
        "dark",
        "horror"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "flower arrangement"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'karaoke'?",
      "options": [
        "のうか",
        "カラオケ",
        "ひろい",
        "あつい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "カラオケ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'bookshelf'?",
      "options": [
        "intaanetto (o) shimasu",
        "kikimasu",
        "hon-dana",
        "sara"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hon-dana"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'hiru-gohan'?",
      "options": [
        "たべもの",
        "ひるごはん",
        "だいどころ",
        "はなびたいかい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ひるごはん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'karaoke'?",
      "options": [
        "karaoke",
        "desk / table",
        "classical music",
        "sour"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "karaoke"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'うえ'?",
      "options": [
        "mountain-climbing (to climb a mountain)",
        "we",
        "on / above",
        "to go to bed / to sleep"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "on / above"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'フィリピン'?",
      "options": [
        "France",
        "the Philippines",
        "guitar",
        "floor cushion"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "the Philippines"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'のうか'?",
      "options": [
        "farmer",
        "lettuce",
        "grandchild",
        "he"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "farmer"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'sliding-door closet'?",
      "options": [
        "〜 o agemasu",
        "aisu",
        "oshi'ire",
        "karendaa"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "oshi'ire"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'cup'?",
      "options": [
        "mae",
        "hanabi-taikai",
        "kappu",
        "Chuugoku"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kappu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'dansu'?",
      "options": [
        "slippers",
        "carrot",
        "boring / dull",
        "dance"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "dance"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'restaurant'?",
      "options": [
        "てつだいます",
        "はつもうで",
        "レストラン",
        "チョコレート"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "レストラン"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to listen'?",
      "options": [
        "かんごし",
        "たのしい",
        "バナナ",
        "ききます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ききます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'sara'?",
      "options": [
        "ともだちが　きます",
        "じゅうどう",
        "さら",
        "えいご"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "さら"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'horaa'?",
      "options": [
        "スポーツ",
        "ホラー",
        "たばこを　すいます",
        "〜りょうり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ホラー"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'U.K.'?",
      "options": [
        "sukoshi",
        "uisukii",
        "soto",
        "Igirisu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Igirisu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'エンジニア'?",
      "options": [
        "onna-no-hito",
        "supagethi (pasuta)",
        "enjinia",
        "tamago"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "enjinia"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'インド'?",
      "options": [
        "India",
        "living room",
        "a friend comes to visit",
        "mountain-climbing (to climb a mountain)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "India"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'jazu'?",
      "options": [
        "dark",
        "jazz",
        "Spain",
        "foreign language"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "jazz"
    },
    
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'おんな'?",
      "options": [
        "a friend comes to visit",
        "trip / to go on a trip",
        "woman / female",
        "number"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "woman / female"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'じえいぎょう'?",
      "options": [
        "ane",
        "hikimasu",
        "omiyage",
        "jieegyoo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "jieegyoo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ぜんぜん'?",
      "options": [
        "Japanese food",
        "classroom",
        "never",
        "glass"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "never"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'あめ'?",
      "options": [
        "big / large",
        "sushi",
        "banana",
        "(hard) candy"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(hard) candy"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'refrigerator'?",
      "options": [
        "arubaito (baito)",
        "minna",
        "hayai",
        "reezooko"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "reezooko"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'E-meeru (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "レタス",
        "ききます",
        "メール／ E メール（を）します",
        "アメリカ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "メール／ E メール（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'arubaito (baito)'?",
      "options": [
        "わたしたち",
        "アルバイト",
        "おとしより",
        "コーヒー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "アルバイト"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'nikki o kakimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "Japan",
        "summer holidays",
        "to keep a diary",
        "passport"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to keep a diary"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'Oosutoraria'?",
      "options": [
        "Australia",
        "to check",
        "to go to bed / to sleep",
        "hot (coffee / tea)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Australia"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'よこ'?",
      "options": [
        "Asia",
        "barbecue",
        "beside",
        "dislike / hate"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "beside"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'park'?",
      "options": [
        "jogingu",
        "oshoogatsu",
        "kooen",
        "otooto"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kooen"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'べんとう'?",
      "options": [
        "packed lunch / lunch box",
        "to clean",
        "to take care of / look after",
        "to shave"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "packed lunch / lunch box"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'しょくじ（を）します'?",
      "options": [
        "pencil",
        "to have a meal",
        "to talk / to speak",
        "foreign country"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to have a meal"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ぶどうがり'?",
      "options": [
        "budoogari",
        "isogashii",
        "mono",
        "obaasan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "budoogari"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'part-time job'?",
      "options": [
        "arubaito (baito)",
        "toriniku / chikin",
        "ningyoo",
        "neko"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "arubaito (baito)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'まつり'?",
      "options": [
        "map",
        "photograph",
        "festival / celebration",
        "people from … (nationality)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "festival / celebration"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'やすみます'?",
      "options": [
        "yasumimasu",
        "setsumee (o) shimasu",
        "suiee",
        "kazoku"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "yasumimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ラジオ'?",
      "options": [
        "radio",
        "water",
        "desk",
        "to watch TV"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "radio"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'juice'?",
      "options": [
        "〜を　のみます",
        "あつい",
        "ジュース",
        "はやい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ジュース"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'エンジニア'?",
      "options": [
        "concert",
        "engineer",
        "trip / to go on a trip",
        "Korean language"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "engineer"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'autumn-leaf viewing'?",
      "options": [
        "momijigari",
        "kaisha",
        "kudamono",
        "shio"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "momijigari"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'udon noodles'?",
      "options": [
        "ヨガ（を）します",
        "うどん",
        "ゆっくりします",
        "そのほか"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "うどん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'taihen'?",
      "options": [
        "たいへん（な）",
        "しつもん（を）します",
        "にっきを　かきます",
        "ホワイトボード"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "たいへん（な）"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'sport'?",
      "options": [
        "yoku",
        "supootsu",
        "tsumetai",
        "hotto"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "supootsu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ぜんぜん'?",
      "options": [
        "kitchen",
        "(not) at all",
        "cross (false)",
        "a little / a few"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(not) at all"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Indonesia'?",
      "options": [
        "ひるごはん",
        "もんだい",
        "インドネシア",
        "いけばな"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "インドネシア"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kaisha'?",
      "options": [
        "beer",
        "company / firm",
        "(someone else's) elder sister",
        "to check"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "company / firm"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'rokku'?",
      "options": [
        "なか",
        "こわい",
        "ロック",
        "しょっぱい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ロック"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'うた'?",
      "options": [
        "song",
        "cross (false)",
        "Golden Week holidays",
        "bright"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "song"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'hot'?",
      "options": [
        "がっこう",
        "あつい",
        "スペイン",
        "でかけます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "あつい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'すばらしい'?",
      "options": [
        "elderly person",
        "to get tired",
        "amazing / wonderful",
        "Golden Week holidays"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "amazing / wonderful"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'terebi'?",
      "options": [
        "television",
        "photograph",
        "tempura",
        "cheese burger"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "television"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for '(not) many / (not) much'?",
      "options": [
        "やきゅう",
        "コンサート",
        "あまり",
        "はなびたいかい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "あまり"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for '(someone else's) husband'?",
      "options": [
        "shokuji (o) shimasu",
        "goshujin",
        "shoosetsu",
        "Arabiago"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "goshujin"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'かんごし'?",
      "options": [
        "nurse",
        "examination",
        "medical doctor",
        "he"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "nurse"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ぶんがく'?",
      "options": [
        "Japanese-style room",
        "literature",
        "to do a part-time job",
        "ramen noodles"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "literature"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'すき（な）'?",
      "options": [
        "Bon Festival dance",
        "manga / comic strips / comic books",
        "like",
        "to brush / clean one's teeth"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "like"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tonari no hito'?",
      "options": [
        "となりのひと",
        "テレビを　みます",
        "はを　みがきます",
        "あね"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "となりのひと"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'hanabi'?",
      "options": [
        "うしろ",
        "なまえ",
        "たっきゅう／ピンポン",
        "は なび"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "は なび"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'misoshiru'?",
      "options": [
        "ラーメン",
        "ソファ",
        "わたしたち",
        "みそしる"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "みそしる"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tsukue'?",
      "options": [
        "オーストラリア",
        "いい",
        "つくえ",
        "とりにく／チキン"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "つくえ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'ribingu'?",
      "options": [
        "やきゅう",
        "リビング",
        "のうか",
        "おかあさん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "リビング"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'chair'?",
      "options": [
        "isu",
        "hima",
        "danboo",
        "batsu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "isu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'じしょ'?",
      "options": [
        "dictionary",
        "desk",
        "basketball",
        "knife"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "dictionary"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ファンタジー'?",
      "options": [
        "out / outside",
        "in / inside",
        "fantasy fiction",
        "hobby / interest"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "fantasy fiction"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'hiroi'?",
      "options": [
        "いもうと",
        "ひろい",
        "バースデー",
        "トマト"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ひろい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'isu'?",
      "options": [
        "toilet",
        "she",
        "chair",
        "magazine"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "chair"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for '(someone else's) wife'?",
      "options": [
        "tonari no hito",
        "washitsu",
        "okusan",
        "chichi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "okusan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'スーツケース'?",
      "options": [
        "ane",
        "tsukaremasu",
        "suutsukeesu",
        "oniisan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "suutsukeesu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'すいえい'?",
      "options": [
        "yuki-matsuri",
        "sentakuki / sentakki",
        "suiee",
        "asobimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "suiee"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'じこしょうかい（します）'?",
      "options": [
        "jiko-shookai (shimasu)",
        "chawan",
        "otto",
        "shokki"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "jiko-shookai (shimasu)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'a little / a few'?",
      "options": [
        "geemu",
        "howaito-boodo",
        "chotto",
        "fukushuu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "chotto"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'かれ'?",
      "options": [
        "hot",
        "to rest / take a rest",
        "cooking / dish",
        "he"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "he"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to clean'?",
      "options": [
        "suupu",
        "tonari",
        "arubaito / baito (o) shimasu",
        "sooji (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sooji (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'やきそば'?",
      "options": [
        "(someone else's) elder brother",
        "chair",
        "fried noodles",
        "movie / film"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "fried noodles"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'school'?",
      "options": [
        "がっこう",
        "おきます",
        "コンテスト",
        "じこしょうかい（します）"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "がっこう"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ごしゅじん'?",
      "options": [
        "knife",
        "number",
        "baseball",
        "(someone else's) husband"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(someone else's) husband"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'lunch'?",
      "options": [
        "poppusu",
        "hiru-gohan",
        "hon",
        "kazoku"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hiru-gohan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'sport'?",
      "options": [
        "スポーツ",
        "やすい",
        "にんじん",
        "じぶん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "スポーツ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ともだちが　きます'?",
      "options": [
        "tokee",
        "〜go",
        "otoosan",
        "tomodachi ga kimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tomodachi ga kimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'そぼ'?",
      "options": [
        "hiru-gohan",
        "sobo",
        "yooguruto",
        "sandoicchi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sobo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'すこし'?",
      "options": [
        "camping / to go camping",
        "a little / a few",
        "reading",
        "youth"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "a little / a few"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'haiku'?",
      "options": [
        "はいく",
        "かいわ（を）します",
        "コピー（を）します",
        "せつめい（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "はいく"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'おどり'?",
      "options": [
        "desk",
        "to read",
        "breakfast",
        "dance"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "dance"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'sentaku (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "to wash clothes",
        "ticket",
        "autumn festival",
        "fried noodles"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to wash clothes"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'balcony'?",
      "options": [
        "ベランダ",
        "みかん",
        "まえ",
        "ナイフ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ベランダ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ii'?",
      "options": [
        "dish / plate",
        "classroom",
        "〜 language",
        "nice / good"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "nice / good"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'Asia'?",
      "options": [
        "usagi",
        "tana",
        "Ajia",
        "kagu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Ajia"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to consult / to discuss'?",
      "options": [
        "ban-gohan",
        "soodan (o) shimasu",
        "kagu",
        "Chuugoku"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "soodan (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to copy'?",
      "options": [
        "toire",
        "ryoori",
        "hiru-gohan",
        "kopii (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kopii (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'hoteru'?",
      "options": [
        "English language",
        "tempura",
        "(someone else's) younger brother",
        "hotel"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hotel"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to explain'?",
      "options": [
        "ミステリー",
        "いぬ",
        "おとうと",
        "せつめい（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "せつめい（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'あさごはん'?",
      "options": [
        "ocha",
        "jukoosha",
        "sentaku (o) shimasu",
        "asa-gohan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "asa-gohan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'carrot'?",
      "options": [
        "みず",
        "コメディ",
        "にんじん",
        "ウイスキー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "にんじん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'jiko-shookai (shimasu)'?",
      "options": [
        "to smoke",
        "whiteboard",
        "self-introduction (to introduce oneself)",
        "(my) grandfather"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "self-introduction (to introduce oneself)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'hoteru'?",
      "options": [
        "おもしろい",
        "ホテル",
        "かなしい",
        "はやい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ホテル"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'on / above'?",
      "options": [
        "kakimasu",
        "kodomo",
        "fooku",
        "ue"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ue"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'brothers and sisters'?",
      "options": [
        "gitaa",
        "kyoodai",
        "terebi o mimasu",
        "tsumaranai"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kyoodai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'department store'?",
      "options": [
        "みんな",
        "ともだちに　あいます",
        "デパート",
        "イタリア"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "デパート"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'きらい（な）'?",
      "options": [
        "kamera",
        "kirai",
        "tonari no hito",
        "kaishain"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kirai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'むすこ'?",
      "options": [
        "Mekishiko",
        "rokku",
        "musuko",
        "mago"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "musuko"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'cooking / dish'?",
      "options": [
        "カード",
        "りょうり",
        "むすこ",
        "きんぎょ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "りょうり"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Suriranka'?",
      "options": [
        "えび",
        "スリランカ",
        "でんき",
        "パン"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "スリランカ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'food'?",
      "options": [
        "bangoo",
        "ryooshin",
        "paatotaimu (paato)",
        "tabemono"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tabemono"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'そば'?",
      "options": [
        "furui",
        "tsuri (o shimasu)",
        "soba",
        "tsukue"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "soba"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'やまのぼり（を　します）'?",
      "options": [
        "like",
        "carrot",
        "school",
        "mountain-climbing (to climb a mountain)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "mountain-climbing (to climb a mountain)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'アイロン'?",
      "options": [
        "natsu-matsuri",
        "airon",
        "enjinia",
        "semai"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "airon"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'あかるい'?",
      "options": [
        "cooking / dish",
        "Italy",
        "cake",
        "bright"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "bright"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'water'?",
      "options": [
        "mizu",
        "jukoosha",
        "sofa",
        "koomuin"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "mizu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'せまい'?",
      "options": [
        "paatotaimu (paato)",
        "goshujin",
        "semai",
        "aisu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "semai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ポップス'?",
      "options": [
        "potato",
        "under / below",
        "festival / celebration",
        "pop music"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "pop music"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'パーティー'?",
      "options": [
        "otooto",
        "Mareeshia",
        "paathii",
        "ofuro"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "paathii"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'アフリカ'?",
      "options": [
        "Afurika",
        "aki-matsuri",
        "jiko-shookai (shimasu)",
        "beddo-ruumu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Afurika"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'パン'?",
      "options": [
        "electrical appliance",
        "bookshelf",
        "cheese burger",
        "bread"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "bread"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'そふ'?",
      "options": [
        "to play a game",
        "mystery",
        "coffee",
        "(my) grandfather"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(my) grandfather"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'misuterii'?",
      "options": [
        "スパゲティ（パスタ）",
        "ミステリー",
        "ひげを　そります",
        "ベランダ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ミステリー"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'isogashii'?",
      "options": [
        "いそがしい",
        "ぼんさい",
        "にく",
        "みそしる"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "いそがしい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'スペインご'?",
      "options": [
        "Spanish language",
        "cookie",
        "bright",
        "strawberry"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Spanish language"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'salad'?",
      "options": [
        "あに",
        "〜に　いきます",
        "サラダ",
        "かいもの（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "サラダ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to draw'?",
      "options": [
        "でんわ",
        "かきます",
        "つくえ",
        "ざんぎょう（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かきます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'student studying abroad / international student'?",
      "options": [
        "おばあさん",
        "りゅうがくせい",
        "つめたい",
        "がいこくじん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "りゅうがくせい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ちち'?",
      "options": [
        "Thailand",
        "department store",
        "microwave oven",
        "(my) father"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(my) father"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'sliding door'?",
      "options": [
        "わかもの",
        "ふすま",
        "ぶどう",
        "ひろい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ふすま"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ジョギング'?",
      "options": [
        "spaghetti / pasta",
        "alcoholic drinks / Japanese sake",
        "jogging",
        "foreign country"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "jogging"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'fuku o nugimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "ふくを　ぬぎます",
        "おかあさん",
        "おとうと",
        "けいたいでんわ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ふくを　ぬぎます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'れんあい'?",
      "options": [
        "natto (fermented soybeans)",
        "romance / love story",
        "slow",
        "soup"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "romance / love story"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'おんなのひと'?",
      "options": [
        "ane",
        "bijutsukan",
        "kao o araimasu",
        "onna-no-hito"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "onna-no-hito"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ポップス'?",
      "options": [
        "yakyuu",
        "poppusu",
        "osoi",
        "oinori (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "poppusu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'おかあさん'?",
      "options": [
        "sweet",
        "(someone else's) mother",
        "family",
        "(hard) candy"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(someone else's) mother"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'poppusu'?",
      "options": [
        "にんぎょう",
        "かぞく",
        "ポップス",
        "おおきい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ポップス"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to work overtime / extra hours'?",
      "options": [
        "Hangarii",
        "zangyoo (o) shimasu",
        "takai",
        "ebi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "zangyoo (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'hot water'?",
      "options": [
        "karee",
        "suiee",
        "oyu",
        "ocha"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "oyu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'bijutsukan'?",
      "options": [
        "きょうかしょ",
        "たっきゅう／ピンポン",
        "ねむい",
        "びじゅつかん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "びじゅつかん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'boy'?",
      "options": [
        "otooto",
        "keeyooshi",
        "otoko-no-ko",
        "ninjin"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "otoko-no-ko"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kaigoshi'?",
      "options": [
        "かいごし",
        "（ひとが）おおい",
        "しつもん（を）します",
        "おきます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かいごし"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to drink 〜'?",
      "options": [
        "sara",
        "〜 o nomimasu",
        "ninjin",
        "resutoran"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜 o nomimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'shooji'?",
      "options": [
        "きょうし",
        "チーズ",
        "あいさつ",
        "しょうじ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "しょうじ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'キャベツ'?",
      "options": [
        "raamen",
        "atatakai",
        "oshi'ire",
        "kyabetsu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kyabetsu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'snow festival'?",
      "options": [
        "おもしろい",
        "おしょうがつ／しょうがつ",
        "ゆきまつり",
        "おふろ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ゆきまつり"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ふすま'?",
      "options": [
        "batsu",
        "pen",
        "fusuma",
        "baasudee"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "fusuma"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ビール'?",
      "options": [
        "to work overtime / extra hours",
        "beer",
        "the person next to you",
        "big / large"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "beer"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'がっこう'?",
      "options": [
        "airon",
        "gakkoo",
        "(hito ga) ooi",
        "fukushuu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "gakkoo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'action'?",
      "options": [
        "tenisu",
        "kukkii",
        "musume",
        "akushon"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "akushon"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'キャンプ（を　します）'?",
      "options": [
        "kyanpu (o shimasu)",
        "jamu",
        "otoko-no-ko",
        "Amerika"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kyanpu (o shimasu)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'eakon'?",
      "options": [
        "to do a part-time job",
        "coffee",
        "air conditioner",
        "horror"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "air conditioner"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'hatsu-moode'?",
      "options": [
        "(my) younger brother",
        "cooking / dish",
        "New Year's visit to a shrine or temple",
        "chopsticks"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "New Year's visit to a shrine or temple"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'everyone'?",
      "options": [
        "minasan",
        "okashi",
        "undoo (o) shimasu",
        "matsuri"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "minasan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'fooku'?",
      "options": [
        "bread",
        "Japanese pop music",
        "Bon Festival dance",
        "fork"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "fork"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'swimming in the sea'?",
      "options": [
        "かいす いよく",
        "ジャズ",
        "コンサート",
        "バーベキュー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かいす いよく"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'でんわ（を）します／かけます'?",
      "options": [
        "chawan",
        "budoo",
        "denwa (o) shimasu / kakemasu",
        "pasupooto"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "denwa (o) shimasu / kakemasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'garden'?",
      "options": [
        "おにいさん",
        "にわ",
        "アイスクリーム",
        "こども"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "にわ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'gaikokugo'?",
      "options": [
        "いもうと",
        "アイロン",
        "かつどう・イベント",
        "がいこくご／〜ご"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "がいこくご／〜ご"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for '(my) husband'?",
      "options": [
        "kontesuto",
        "kurai",
        "otto",
        "〜 ni nite imasu ne"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "otto"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'wain'?",
      "options": [
        "wine",
        "Japanese pop music",
        "to do a part-time job",
        "amazing / wonderful"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "wine"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'everyone'?",
      "options": [
        "でんしレンジ",
        "みんな",
        "ギター",
        "でんわ（を）します／かけます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "みんな"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'パンフレット'?",
      "options": [
        "egg",
        "to do exercise",
        "myself / me",
        "brochure / pamphlet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "brochure / pamphlet"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'book'?",
      "options": [
        "Eego",
        "watashi",
        "hon",
        "mazui"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hon"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'gyuunyuu / miruku'?",
      "options": [
        "ニュージーランド",
        "きゅうり",
        "おどります",
        "ぎゅうにゅう／ミルク"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ぎゅうにゅう／ミルク"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'スポーツ'?",
      "options": [
        "interesting",
        "to read",
        "sport",
        "bean curd / tofu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sport"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'shigoto (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "present",
        "man",
        "to work / do one's job",
        "snow festival"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to work / do one's job"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to help'?",
      "options": [
        "おいしい",
        "おどります",
        "〜を　あげます",
        "てつだいます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "てつだいます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'computer'?",
      "options": [
        "jiko-shookai (shimasu)",
        "konpyuutaa",
        "atatakai",
        "tana"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "konpyuutaa"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'black tea'?",
      "options": [
        "にほん／にっぽん",
        "〜を　のみます",
        "ほん",
        "こうちゃ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "こうちゃ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'した'?",
      "options": [
        "to smoke",
        "passport",
        "hot / spicy / salty",
        "under / below"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "under / below"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'gakkoo'?",
      "options": [
        "school",
        "Brazil",
        "to take care of / look after",
        "(my) mother"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "school"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'reservation / booking (to make a reservation)'?",
      "options": [
        "は なび",
        "よやく （を　しま す）",
        "プレゼント",
        "ふるい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "よやく （を　しま す）"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'tamago'?",
      "options": [
        "cucumber",
        "show",
        "egg",
        "cereal"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "egg"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'participant'?",
      "options": [
        "shokuji",
        "hanashimasu",
        "manga",
        "jukoosha"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "jukoosha"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'temple'?",
      "options": [
        "おてら／てら",
        "いい",
        "ろうか",
        "よこ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おてら／てら"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'mondai'?",
      "options": [
        "Europe",
        "question / problem",
        "answer",
        "taiko drumming"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "question / problem"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ざんぎょう（を）します'?",
      "options": [
        "museum",
        "to work overtime / extra hours",
        "glass / cup",
        "housewife / homemaker"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to work overtime / extra hours"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'seasonal events'?",
      "options": [
        "〜に にて いますね",
        "にもつ",
        "きせつのイベント",
        "キャンプ（を　します）"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "きせつのイベント"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'つま'?",
      "options": [
        "washing machine",
        "tableware",
        "(my) wife",
        "concert"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(my) wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'floor cushion'?",
      "options": [
        "piza",
        "zabuton",
        "kowai",
        "momijigari"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "zabuton"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'nemasu'?",
      "options": [
        "かぶき",
        "ねます",
        "コンサート",
        "にほんりょうり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ねます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'washing machine'?",
      "options": [
        "surippa",
        "sentakuki / sentakki",
        "okusan",
        "hoteru"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sentakuki / sentakki"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'busy'?",
      "options": [
        "ame",
        "isogashii",
        "koora",
        "okusan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "isogashii"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'shumi'?",
      "options": [
        "え",
        "しゅみ",
        "ファーストフードてん",
        "げんかん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "しゅみ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'in / inside'?",
      "options": [
        "たべもの",
        "なか",
        "やすみます",
        "〜に　とまります"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "なか"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'benkyoo (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "せんたくき",
        "べんきょう（を）します",
        "ポップス",
        "マレーシア"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "べんきょう（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'sukeeto'?",
      "options": [
        "goldfish",
        "anime / animated cartoons",
        "skating",
        "hobby / interest"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "skating"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'front'?",
      "options": [
        "バスケットボール",
        "にんじん",
        "まえ",
        "メニュー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "まえ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'gakkoo'?",
      "options": [
        "watermelon",
        "hospital",
        "school",
        "parents"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "school"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'hon'?",
      "options": [
        "ほん",
        "わさび",
        "ふるい",
        "おしいれ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ほん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'party'?",
      "options": [
        "パーティー",
        "きょうし",
        "ちゅうごくご",
        "カップ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "パーティー"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'soccer / football'?",
      "options": [
        "sakkaa",
        "enjinia",
        "kaigoshi",
        "oinori (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sakkaa"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'shitsumon (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "あいさつ",
        "べんきょう（を）します",
        "しお",
        "しつもん（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "しつもん（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'alcove'?",
      "options": [
        "tokonoma",
        "Roshia",
        "senpuuki",
        "e (o kakimasu)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tokonoma"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'remon'?",
      "options": [
        "hot / spicy / salty",
        "radio",
        "salty",
        "lemon"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "lemon"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'Burajiru'?",
      "options": [
        "Brazil",
        "electric fan",
        "〜 food / 〜 cuisine",
        "Mexico"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for '〜に　とまります'?",
      "options": [
        "autumn festival",
        "travel / trip",
        "to stop over / to stay at (a hotel)",
        "(my) son"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to stop over / to stay at (a hotel)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'like'?",
      "options": [
        "すき",
        "（ひとが）おおい",
        "だんぼう",
        "すこ し"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "すき"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'pasupooto'?",
      "options": [
        "slippers",
        "passport",
        "reading",
        "corridor"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "passport"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'かいもの（を）します'?",
      "options": [
        "small / cramped",
        "to go shopping",
        "travel / trip",
        "doll"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to go shopping"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to wash clothes'?",
      "options": [
        "よやく （を します）",
        "そふ",
        "せんたく（を）します",
        "がくせい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "せんたく（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'otoko-no-ko'?",
      "options": [
        "Haiku",
        "electric fan",
        "boy",
        "meat"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "boy"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'corridor'?",
      "options": [
        "ピザ",
        "ろうか",
        "さんぽ（を）します",
        "ゲーム"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ろうか"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'tea ceremony'?",
      "options": [
        "Indoneshia",
        "kingyo",
        "sadoo",
        "denki"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sadoo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for '(my) elder sister'?",
      "options": [
        "gaikoku",
        "ane",
        "shawaa o abimasu",
        "kaishain"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ane"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'mountain-climbing (to climb a mountain)'?",
      "options": [
        "せんせい",
        "やまのぼり（を　します）",
        "じこしょうかい（します）",
        "アイスクリーム"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "やまのぼり（を　します）"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'isogashii'?",
      "options": [
        "everyone",
        "corridor",
        "egg",
        "busy"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "busy"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'obaasan'?",
      "options": [
        "restaurant",
        "cross (false)",
        "(someone else's) grandmother",
        "table tennis / ping-pong"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(someone else's) grandmother"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'poster'?",
      "options": [
        "すき（な）",
        "ポスター",
        "ワイン",
        "むすこ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ポスター"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'たのしい'?",
      "options": [
        "kaado",
        "kyookasho",
        "Furansugo",
        "tanoshii"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tanoshii"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'keeyooshi'?",
      "options": [
        "(someone else's) wife",
        "trip / to go on a trip",
        "glass",
        "adjectives"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'aisu'?",
      "options": [
        "iced (coffee / tea)",
        "reservation / booking (to make a reservation)",
        "Japanese-style room",
        "bedroom"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "iced (coffee / tea)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'soto'?",
      "options": [
        "out / outside",
        "girl",
        "to clean",
        "art museum"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "out / outside"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'はくぶつかん'?",
      "options": [
        "imootosan",
        "shio",
        "hakubutsukan",
        "Burajiru"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hakubutsukan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'cat'?",
      "options": [
        "えいが",
        "ねこ",
        "ソファ",
        "しつもん（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ねこ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'うちに　かえります'?",
      "options": [
        "to go home",
        "romance / love story",
        "Russia",
        "slow"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to go home"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'grape picking'?",
      "options": [
        "ぶどうがり",
        "おちゃ／ちゃ",
        "にほんりょうり",
        "きせつのイベント"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ぶどうがり"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'グラス'?",
      "options": [
        "gurasu",
        "hayai",
        "horaa",
        "poppusu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "gurasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'brochure / pamphlet'?",
      "options": [
        "カーテン",
        "ほん",
        "びょういん",
        "パンフレット"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "パンフレット"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for '(my) younger sister'?",
      "options": [
        "imooto",
        "bungaku",
        "mado",
        "suika"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "imooto"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'otoosan'?",
      "options": [
        "よこ",
        "おとうさん",
        "テスト",
        "ゴルフ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おとうさん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'スーツケース'?",
      "options": [
        "スーツケ ース",
        "〜を　たべます",
        "クラス",
        "リビング"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "スーツケ ース"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'telephone'?",
      "options": [
        "ばんごはん",
        "ばつ",
        "でんわ",
        "かいもの（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "でんわ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'gyuuniku / biifu'?",
      "options": [
        "しんぶんを　よみます",
        "ぎゅうにく／ビーフ",
        "きょうしつ",
        "なつまつり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ぎゅうにく／ビーフ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'aki-matsuri'?",
      "options": [
        "tennis",
        "autumn festival",
        "everyone",
        "to take a shower"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "autumn festival"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'バナナ'?",
      "options": [
        "coffee",
        "foreigner",
        "banana",
        "part-time job"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "banana"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'おんがくを　ききます'?",
      "options": [
        "cool",
        "people / person",
        "New Year's visit to a shrine or temple",
        "to listen to music"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to listen to music"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'reezooko'?",
      "options": [
        "anime / animated cartoons",
        "woman / female",
        "refrigerator",
        "elderly person"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "refrigerator"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'denki-seehin'?",
      "options": [
        "example",
        "pizza",
        "electrical appliance",
        "(not) at all"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "electrical appliance"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'あそびます'?",
      "options": [
        "konpyuutaa",
        "asa-gohan",
        "geemu",
        "asobimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "asobimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'かたづけます'?",
      "options": [
        "beside",
        "bookshelf",
        "sushi",
        "to tidy up"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to tidy up"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'ofuro'?",
      "options": [
        "おふろ",
        "はこ",
        "ショー",
        "ファーストフードてん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おふろ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Malaysia'?",
      "options": [
        "ビール",
        "かいごし",
        "コーラ",
        "マレーシア"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "マレーシア"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kaidan'?",
      "options": [
        "たいこ",
        "まご",
        "かいだん",
        "アフリカ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かいだん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'futon'?",
      "options": [
        "〜に　いきます",
        "ミステリー",
        "みかん",
        "ふとん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ふとん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'hot / spicy / salty'?",
      "options": [
        "バーベキュー",
        "からい",
        "アルバイト（バイト）",
        "おにぎり（おむすび）"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "からい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'じぶん'?",
      "options": [
        "coffee shop",
        "new",
        "classroom",
        "oneself"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "oneself"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'calendar'?",
      "options": [
        "そと",
        "ペン",
        "カレンダー",
        "テスト"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "カレンダー"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'geemu'?",
      "options": [
        "べんとう",
        "ゲーム",
        "ぎゅうにゅう／ミルク",
        "おふろ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ゲーム"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'aisu'?",
      "options": [
        "カレー",
        "アイス",
        "かんごし",
        "タイ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "アイス"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'Tokyo'?",
      "options": [
        "Tookyoo",
        "jogingu",
        "chokoreeto",
        "kamera"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Tookyoo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for '(my) wife'?",
      "options": [
        "つま",
        "〜と　おしゃべり（を）します",
        "ファーストフードてん",
        "りょうり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "つま"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ページ'?",
      "options": [
        "reezooko",
        "〜 ryoori",
        "peeji",
        "nemasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "peeji"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'くらい'?",
      "options": [
        "kurai",
        "misoshiru",
        "E-meeru (o) shimasu",
        "supootsu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kurai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'jieegyoo'?",
      "options": [
        "おとうさん",
        "けしごむ",
        "じえいぎょう",
        "かなしい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "じえいぎょう"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'science fiction'?",
      "options": [
        "shukudai",
        "esu-efu",
        "sonohoka",
        "kagu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "esu-efu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'milk'?",
      "options": [
        "sandoicchi",
        "bijutsukan",
        "gyuunyuu / miruku",
        "chotto"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "gyuunyuu / miruku"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'hanashimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "アメリカ",
        "はなします",
        "あめ",
        "〜りょうり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "はなします"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'fishing / to go fishing'?",
      "options": [
        "tokee",
        "tsuri (o shimasu)",
        "Suriranka",
        "uisukii"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tsuri (o shimasu)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'フランス'?",
      "options": [
        "France",
        "near / close",
        "brothers and sisters",
        "piano"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "France"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for '〜を　たべます'?",
      "options": [
        "doll",
        "to eat 〜",
        "to say / to tell",
        "sliding screen"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to eat 〜"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'しごと（を）します'?",
      "options": [
        "biiru",
        "shigoto (o) shimasu",
        "hashi",
        "kyuuri"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shigoto (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'oishii'?",
      "options": [
        "barbecue",
        "delicious / tasty",
        "Europe",
        "to practice"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "delicious / tasty"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ほん'?",
      "options": [
        "woman / female",
        "beautiful / pretty",
        "in / inside",
        "book"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "book"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'romance / love story'?",
      "options": [
        "しょくじ（を）します",
        "つま",
        "すこし",
        "れんあい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "れんあい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ベトナム'?",
      "options": [
        "Betonamu",
        "matsuri",
        "paathii",
        "jugyoo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Betonamu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for '(my) husband'?",
      "options": [
        "そば",
        "べんとう",
        "おっと",
        "てつだいます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おっと"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ギター'?",
      "options": [
        "shooji",
        "Amerika",
        "gitaa",
        "Doitsu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "gitaa"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'dance'?",
      "options": [
        "うさぎ",
        "りゅうがくせい",
        "アイスクリーム",
        "ダンス"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ダンス"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'アイス'?",
      "options": [
        "aisu",
        "resutoran",
        "banana",
        "bangoo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "aisu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to go out'?",
      "options": [
        "dekakemasu",
        "fuyu-yasumi",
        "shigoto (o) shimasu",
        "supagethi (pasuta)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "dekakemasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'Italy'?",
      "options": [
        "konpyuutaa",
        "gohan",
        "Itaria",
        "kopii (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Itaria"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'さむい'?",
      "options": [
        "tableware",
        "India",
        "cold",
        "(hard) candy"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "cold"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'chopsticks'?",
      "options": [
        "アジア",
        "パートタイム（パート）",
        "おとこのひと",
        "はし"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "はし"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'gakkoo'?",
      "options": [
        "にっきを　かきます",
        "がっこう",
        "アイロン",
        "たまねぎ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "がっこう"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'shigoto (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "ふくを　きます",
        "しごと（を）します",
        "かいしゃ",
        "ヨーロッパ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "しごと（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'keeyooshi'?",
      "options": [
        "ゴールデンウィーク",
        "ぶんがく",
        "たかい",
        "けいようし"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "けいようし"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'nihon-ryoori'?",
      "options": [
        "to get up / to wake up",
        "mountain-climbing (to climb a mountain)",
        "sushi",
        "Japanese food"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Japanese food"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kamera'?",
      "options": [
        "camera",
        "staircase",
        "brothers and sisters",
        "Kabuki"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "camera"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'Arabiago'?",
      "options": [
        "front",
        "self-employed",
        "rock music",
        "Arabic language"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Arabic language"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'J ポップ'?",
      "options": [
        "bijutsukan",
        "namae",
        "J-poppu",
        "shumi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "J-poppu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'posutaa'?",
      "options": [
        "サンドイッチ",
        "ちょ っと",
        "ポ スター",
        "かに"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ポ スター"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'a lot'?",
      "options": [
        "takusan",
        "kappu",
        "hanashimasu",
        "Afurika"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "takusan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'ryooshin'?",
      "options": [
        "しゅみ",
        "りょうしん",
        "がっこう",
        "カメラ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "りょうしん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'きょうし'?",
      "options": [
        "yuki-matsuri",
        "kyooshi",
        "anime",
        "orenji-juusu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kyooshi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'いま'?",
      "options": [
        "takkyuu / pinpon",
        "ima",
        "ren'ai",
        "hiru-gohan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ima"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tamanegi'?",
      "options": [
        "たまねぎ",
        "ホット",
        "しんぶんを　よみます",
        "ときどき"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "たまねぎ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'reezooko'?",
      "options": [
        "おおきい",
        "みず",
        "れいぞうこ",
        "きょうだい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "れいぞうこ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ファーストフードてん'?",
      "options": [
        "myself / me",
        "self-employed",
        "doll",
        "fast-food restaurant"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "fast-food restaurant"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'じゅうどう'?",
      "options": [
        "Judo",
        "to give",
        "mountain-climbing (to climb a mountain)",
        "to relax"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Judo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'tokidoki'?",
      "options": [
        "question / problem",
        "door",
        "like",
        "sometimes"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sometimes"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Amerika'?",
      "options": [
        "しゃしん",
        "すいか",
        "アメリカ",
        "びょういん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "アメリカ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Supeingo'?",
      "options": [
        "おこさん",
        "スペインご",
        "すずしい",
        "おとこのこ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "スペインご"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'あめ'?",
      "options": [
        "chiisai",
        "shokuji (o) shimasu",
        "kippu",
        "ame"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ame"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'hito'?",
      "options": [
        "people / person",
        "old",
        "examination",
        "dictionary"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "people / person"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to do housework'?",
      "options": [
        "hanabi-taikai",
        "arubaito / baito (o) shimasu",
        "kaji (o) shimasu",
        "sadoo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kaji (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'tabako o suimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "to wash one's face",
        "Canada",
        "to smoke",
        "electrical appliance"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to smoke"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'トマト'?",
      "options": [
        "tomato",
        "tomodachi",
        "sadoo",
        "chichi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tomato"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'party'?",
      "options": [
        "supagethi (pasuta)",
        "mono",
        "jogingu",
        "paathii"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "paathii"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kontesuto'?",
      "options": [
        "チラシ",
        "おこさん",
        "コンテスト",
        "はいく"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "コンテスト"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'fruit'?",
      "options": [
        "koohii",
        "kudamono",
        "e",
        "futon"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kudamono"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ホット'?",
      "options": [
        "chawan",
        "hotto",
        "hanami",
        "yasashii"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hotto"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to have a meal'?",
      "options": [
        "メニュー",
        "そば",
        "しょくじ（を）します",
        "カラオケ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "しょくじ（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'cold'?",
      "options": [
        "つまらない",
        "ベトナム",
        "さむい",
        "しょっき"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "さむい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'Indoneshia'?",
      "options": [
        "Indonesia",
        "to wash clothes",
        "test",
        "skating"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Indonesia"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'イタリア'?",
      "options": [
        "rice bowl",
        "electrical appliance",
        "Italy",
        "to go shopping"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Italy"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'vacuum cleaner'?",
      "options": [
        "そうじき",
        "フランスご",
        "おしょうがつ／しょうがつ",
        "とり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "そうじき"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'dog'?",
      "options": [
        "きょうしつ",
        "いぬ",
        "なつまつり",
        "チーズバーガー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "いぬ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'natto (fermented soybeans)'?",
      "options": [
        "nattoo",
        "soojiki",
        "hanami",
        "yasashii"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "nattoo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to meet a friend'?",
      "options": [
        "gooruden-uiiku",
        "odori",
        "panfuretto",
        "tomodachi ni aimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tomodachi ni aimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'ramen noodles'?",
      "options": [
        "ラーメン",
        "うた",
        "バスケットボール",
        "せんせい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ラーメン"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'アニメ'?",
      "options": [
        "bean curd / tofu",
        "U.S.A. / America",
        "anime / animated cartoons",
        "to have breakfast / lunch / dinner"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "anime / animated cartoons"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'Nyuujiirando'?",
      "options": [
        "to chat with 〜",
        "people / person",
        "mobile phone / cellular phone",
        "New Zealand"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "New Zealand"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'souvenir'?",
      "options": [
        "jugyoo",
        "sakana",
        "omiyage",
        "obaasan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "omiyage"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to go shopping'?",
      "options": [
        "はなびたいかい",
        "スリランカ",
        "プレゼント",
        "かいもの（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かいもの（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'パスポート'?",
      "options": [
        "かぶき",
        "うさぎ",
        "パスポ ート",
        "コピー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "パスポ ート"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'carrot'?",
      "options": [
        "okaasan",
        "Doitsugo",
        "kare",
        "ninjin"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ninjin"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'アフリカ'?",
      "options": [
        "Italy",
        "tatami mat",
        "(my) mother",
        "Africa"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Africa"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'movie / film'?",
      "options": [
        "kyooshi",
        "terebi",
        "Ejiputo",
        "eega"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "eega"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kappu'?",
      "options": [
        "かんごし",
        "カップ",
        "ナイフ",
        "ふくを　ぬぎます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "カップ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kanashii'?",
      "options": [
        "よく",
        "なつまつり",
        "かなしい",
        "とりにく／チキン"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かなしい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tenisu'?",
      "options": [
        "みます",
        "ゲーム",
        "テニス",
        "すもう"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "テニス"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kanashii'?",
      "options": [
        "sad",
        "slow",
        "nearby",
        "radio"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sad"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'a little / a few'?",
      "options": [
        "kaidan",
        "jugyoo",
        "sukoshi",
        "uisukii"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sukoshi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'sashimi'?",
      "options": [
        "はなび",
        "さしみ",
        "スープ",
        "せんたく（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "さしみ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'でんき'?",
      "options": [
        "light",
        "(my) daughter",
        "teacher / instructor",
        "sliding door"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "light"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'tenisu'?",
      "options": [
        "travel / trip",
        "jogging",
        "tennis",
        "origami"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tennis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'ryokan'?",
      "options": [
        "なまえ",
        "りょかん",
        "ハンバーガー",
        "そぼ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "りょかん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'cake'?",
      "options": [
        "asobimasu",
        "obaasan",
        "keeki",
        "ryokan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "keeki"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'いそがしい'?",
      "options": [
        "to have a meal",
        "busy",
        "German language",
        "self-introduction (to introduce oneself)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "busy"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'ice cream'?",
      "options": [
        "アイスクリーム",
        "みかん",
        "コーヒー",
        "フランス"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "アイスクリーム"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for '(my) elder brother'?",
      "options": [
        "Firipin",
        "danboo",
        "sumoo",
        "ani"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ani"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to go out'?",
      "options": [
        "ちゅうごく",
        "エンジニア",
        "でかけます",
        "えいが"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "でかけます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'concert'?",
      "options": [
        "nikki o kakimasu",
        "konsaato",
        "fusuma",
        "juudoo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "konsaato"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'page'?",
      "options": [
        "ページ",
        "アルバイト（バイト）",
        "チケット",
        "フォーク"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ページ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ロシア'?",
      "options": [
        "uta",
        "Roshia",
        "isogashii",
        "kuukoo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Roshia"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'じゅぎょう'?",
      "options": [
        "mago",
        "gaikokujin",
        "banana",
        "jugyoo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "jugyoo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to drink 〜'?",
      "options": [
        "がいこくご／〜ご",
        "あに",
        "〜を　のみます",
        "たくさん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜を　のみます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'shooyu'?",
      "options": [
        "ふくを　きます",
        "たな",
        "しょうゆ",
        "いい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "しょうゆ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'musuko'?",
      "options": [
        "manga / comic strips / comic books",
        "jam",
        "(my) son",
        "box"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(my) son"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to listen to music'?",
      "options": [
        "おんがくを　ききます",
        "ぼんおどり",
        "さとう",
        "とり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おんがくを　ききます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'yoshuu'?",
      "options": [
        "みんな",
        "よく",
        "よしゅう",
        "はいく"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "よしゅう"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'コンテスト'?",
      "options": [
        "yogurt",
        "contest",
        "small",
        "origami"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "contest"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to pray'?",
      "options": [
        "takai",
        "soto",
        "〜 ni nite imasu ne",
        "oinori (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "oinori (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'e (o kakimasu)'?",
      "options": [
        "ケーキ",
        "さどう",
        "びょういん",
        "え（を　かきます）"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "え（を　かきます）"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kotoba'?",
      "options": [
        "アジア",
        "ことば",
        "J ポップ",
        "おねえさん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ことば"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'おてら／てら'?",
      "options": [
        "ryuugakusee",
        "muzukashii",
        "hakubutsukan",
        "otera"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "otera"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'anata'?",
      "options": [
        "to stop over / to stay at (a hotel)",
        "you",
        "table",
        "to play the guitar / piano"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "you"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'watashitachi'?",
      "options": [
        "we",
        "movie / film",
        "floor cushion",
        "elderly person"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "we"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'shooyu'?",
      "options": [
        "staircase",
        "washing machine",
        "soy sauce",
        "passport"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "soy sauce"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'shawaa o abimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "notebook",
        "to take a shower",
        "(my) grandfather",
        "to explain"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to take a shower"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'どくしょ'?",
      "options": [
        "reading",
        "anime / animated cartoons",
        "sweet",
        "textbook"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "reading"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'トマト'?",
      "options": [
        "fun / enjoyable",
        "girl",
        "tomato",
        "textbook"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tomato"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'benkyoo (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "to study",
        "sliding screen",
        "hamburger",
        "to go to bed / to sleep"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to study"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kaigoshi'?",
      "options": [
        "New Year's holiday",
        "to go out",
        "to watch TV",
        "care worker"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "care worker"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'fireworks display'?",
      "options": [
        "きらい（な）",
        "フォーク",
        "（ひとが）おおい",
        "はなびたいかい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "はなびたいかい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Afurika'?",
      "options": [
        "アフリカ",
        "おいしい",
        "グラス",
        "ポップス"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "アフリカ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'swimming'?",
      "options": [
        "しつもん（を）します",
        "ふくを　きます",
        "すいえい",
        "オーストラリア"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "すいえい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'hot'?",
      "options": [
        "はなびたいかい",
        "ひげを　そります",
        "きたない",
        "あつい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "あつい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'microwave oven'?",
      "options": [
        "アイロン",
        "ウイスキー",
        "こわい",
        "でんしレンジ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "でんしレンジ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tsukaremasu'?",
      "options": [
        "ヨーロッパ",
        "は なび",
        "つかれま す",
        "すいえい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "つかれま す"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'hatsu-moode'?",
      "options": [
        "はつも うで",
        "はいく",
        "ぶどうがり",
        "こども"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "はつも うで"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'he'?",
      "options": [
        "かれ",
        "たかい",
        "ワイン",
        "たくさん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かれ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'door'?",
      "options": [
        "カード",
        "あかるい",
        "やまのぼり（を　します）",
        "ドア"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ドア"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'takkyuu / pinpon'?",
      "options": [
        "Japanese-style room",
        "preparation (for the lesson)",
        "free / not occupied",
        "table tennis / ping-pong"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "table tennis / ping-pong"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ryokan'?",
      "options": [
        "Mt. Fuji",
        "hotel / Japanese inn",
        "swimming",
        "lemon"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hotel / Japanese inn"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Japanese person'?",
      "options": [
        "おゆ／ゆ",
        "はこ",
        "アクション",
        "にほんじん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "にほんじん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ぶどうがり'?",
      "options": [
        "cereal",
        "to meet a friend",
        "grape picking",
        "(my) elder brother"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "grape picking"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'bonsai'?",
      "options": [
        "mountain-climbing (to climb a mountain)",
        "milk",
        "to help",
        "Bonsai"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Bonsai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'みます'?",
      "options": [
        "mobile phone / cellular phone",
        "to look",
        "soup",
        "goldfish"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to look"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'near / close'?",
      "options": [
        "musume",
        "〜 ryoori",
        "e (o kakimasu)",
        "chikaku"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "chikaku"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'origami'?",
      "options": [
        "フランスご",
        "にほんじん",
        "おりがみ",
        "しょうじ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おりがみ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'おおきい'?",
      "options": [
        "crab",
        "big / large",
        "fork",
        "Indonesia"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "big / large"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'present'?",
      "options": [
        "nagai",
        "furui",
        "purezento",
        "kopii (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "purezento"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'engineer'?",
      "options": [
        "わたし",
        "きょうし",
        "エンジニア",
        "メニュー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "エンジニア"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'ree'?",
      "options": [
        "じえいぎょう",
        "れい",
        "どくしょ",
        "レモン"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "れい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to get tired'?",
      "options": [
        "hige o sorimasu",
        "Nihon / Nippon",
        "tsukaremasu",
        "retasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tsukaremasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'しゅふ'?",
      "options": [
        "housewife / homemaker",
        "untidy / dirty",
        "fishing / to go fishing",
        "U.S.A. / America"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "housewife / homemaker"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'にほん／にっぽん'?",
      "options": [
        "Nihon / Nippon",
        "gitaa",
        "origami",
        "ikebana"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Nihon / Nippon"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kyabetsu'?",
      "options": [
        "cabbage",
        "romance / love story",
        "alcove",
        "big / spacious / large"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "cabbage"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'アイスクリーム'?",
      "options": [
        "ice cream",
        "homework",
        "to read",
        "chopsticks"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ice cream"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'salty'?",
      "options": [
        "メキシコ",
        "おばあさん",
        "〜を　あげます",
        "しょっぱい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "しょっぱい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'otoshiyori'?",
      "options": [
        "breakfast",
        "floor cushion",
        "refrigerator",
        "elderly person"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "elderly person"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for '〜 no sewa o shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "Western-style room",
        "(my) mother",
        "to take care of / look after",
        "to write"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to take care of / look after"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'koppu'?",
      "options": [
        "China",
        "〜 food / 〜 cuisine",
        "to rest / take a rest",
        "glass / cup"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "glass / cup"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'となり'?",
      "options": [
        "strawberry",
        "bedding",
        "next to",
        "foreign language"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "next to"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'かつどう・イベント'?",
      "options": [
        "expensive",
        "(someone else's) mother",
        "activities and events",
        "reservation / booking (to make a reservation)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "activities and events"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'beef'?",
      "options": [
        "daidokoro",
        "gyuuniku / biifu",
        "hako",
        "yoyaku (o shimasu)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "gyuuniku / biifu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'せんたくき'?",
      "options": [
        "washing machine",
        "curtain",
        "baseball",
        "to go home"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "washing machine"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'jazz'?",
      "options": [
        "tokidoki",
        "ii",
        "teeburu",
        "jazu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "jazu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ふすま'?",
      "options": [
        "chopsticks",
        "cake",
        "temple",
        "sliding door"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sliding door"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'shumi'?",
      "options": [
        "refrigerator",
        "hobby / interest",
        "Mexico",
        "New Year's visit to a shrine or temple"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hobby / interest"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'beer'?",
      "options": [
        "わさび",
        "ビール",
        "ひきます",
        "バスケットボール"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ビール"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'fishing / to go fishing'?",
      "options": [
        "しゅふ",
        "つり（を　します）",
        "クラシック",
        "ちゃわん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "つり（を　します）"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'かきます'?",
      "options": [
        "isu",
        "misuterii",
        "okeshoo (o) shimasu",
        "kakimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kakimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for '〜 o agemasu'?",
      "options": [
        "おとうさん",
        "フォーク",
        "〜を　あげます",
        "コンピューター"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜を　あげます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to practice'?",
      "options": [
        "chikaku",
        "depaato",
        "renshuu (o) shimasu",
        "udon"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "renshuu (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ベッド'?",
      "options": [
        "〜ga dekimasu",
        "imooto",
        "kaishain",
        "beddo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "beddo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'sadoo'?",
      "options": [
        "bright",
        "tea ceremony",
        "salad",
        "origami"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tea ceremony"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'maru'?",
      "options": [
        "パン",
        "しゅみ",
        "まる",
        "せんぷうき"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "まる"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for '〜と　おしゃべり（を）します'?",
      "options": [
        "sentaku (o) shimasu",
        "hanabi-taikai",
        "〜 to oshaberi (o) shimasu",
        "terebi o mimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜 to oshaberi (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'hanashimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "hamburger",
        "civil servant",
        "to talk / to speak",
        "souvenir"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to talk / to speak"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'そと'?",
      "options": [
        "beddo-ruumu",
        "soto",
        "shiken",
        "kaimono (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "soto"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kotae'?",
      "options": [
        "miso soup",
        "sliding-door closet",
        "to rest / take a rest",
        "answer"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "answer"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ねこ'?",
      "options": [
        "horaa",
        "juusu",
        "〜 ni nite imasu ne",
        "neko"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "neko"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'cookie'?",
      "options": [
        "クッキー",
        "ピアノ",
        "おかし",
        "くだもの"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "クッキー"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'チケット'?",
      "options": [
        "コップ",
        "オーストラリア",
        "りんご",
        "チ ケット／チケ ット"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "チ ケット／チケ ット"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'rice bowl'?",
      "options": [
        "kyanpu (o shimasu)",
        "bonsai",
        "hoteru",
        "chawan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "chawan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'juusu'?",
      "options": [
        "English language",
        "juice",
        "piano",
        "out / outside"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "juice"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kyooshi'?",
      "options": [
        "なつまつり",
        "れんあい",
        "きょうし",
        "ぶたにく／ポーク"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "きょうし"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for '(someone else's) elder sister'?",
      "options": [
        "konsaato",
        "〜 ni tomarimasu",
        "oneesan",
        "iimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "oneesan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'oyu'?",
      "options": [
        "photograph (to take a photo)",
        "balcony",
        "to brush / clean one's teeth",
        "hot water"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hot water"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'おにぎり（おむすび）'?",
      "options": [
        "to go to bed / to sleep",
        "student studying abroad / international student",
        "(my) younger brother",
        "rice ball"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "rice ball"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ちかく'?",
      "options": [
        "hiroi",
        "Furansugo",
        "chikaku",
        "kappu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "chikaku"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'man'?",
      "options": [
        "sakkaa",
        "bijutsukan",
        "otoko-no-hito",
        "goshujin"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "otoko-no-hito"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kaisuiyoku'?",
      "options": [
        "ときどき",
        "かいすいよく",
        "つくえ",
        "いけばな"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かいすいよく"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ぜんぜん'?",
      "options": [
        "〜 o nomimasu",
        "shiriaru",
        "paatotaimu (paato)",
        "zenzen"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "zenzen"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'つま'?",
      "options": [
        "toire",
        "washitsu",
        "tsuma",
        "kowai"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tsuma"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'かきます'?",
      "options": [
        "to draw",
        "department store",
        "to smoke",
        "restaurant"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to draw"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'quantity'?",
      "options": [
        "あたらしい",
        "りょう",
        "つま",
        "わたしたち"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "りょう"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'surippa'?",
      "options": [
        "slippers",
        "butter",
        "door",
        "to rest / take a rest"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "slippers"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'boring / dull'?",
      "options": [
        "zangyoo (o) shimasu",
        "hashi",
        "shiriaru",
        "tsumaranai"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tsumaranai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Chinese language'?",
      "options": [
        "イギリス",
        "ちゅうごくご",
        "ふゆやすみ",
        "にもつ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ちゅうごくご"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'suutsukeesu'?",
      "options": [
        "suitcase",
        "hamburger",
        "to do yoga",
        "amazing / wonderful"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "suitcase"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'けしごむ'?",
      "options": [
        "pork",
        "eraser",
        "garden",
        "to talk / to speak"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "eraser"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'taiko'?",
      "options": [
        "garden",
        "Japanese food",
        "taiko drumming",
        "parents"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "taiko drumming"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'neko'?",
      "options": [
        "lots of (people) / crowded (with people)",
        "heater",
        "cat",
        "family"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "cat"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'いぬ'?",
      "options": [
        "inu",
        "paatotaimu (paato)",
        "sentakuki / sentakki",
        "yooguruto"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "inu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ヨーロッパ'?",
      "options": [
        "Yooroppa",
        "biiru",
        "kamera",
        "dokusho"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Yooroppa"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'パーティー'?",
      "options": [
        "jogging",
        "song",
        "quick",
        "party"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "party"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kaisha'?",
      "options": [
        "かいしゃ",
        "たな",
        "かなしい",
        "パーティー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かいしゃ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ちゅうごくご'?",
      "options": [
        "okimasu",
        "hanashimasu",
        "〜jin",
        "Chuugokugo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Chuugokugo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'foreign country'?",
      "options": [
        "yuki-matsuri",
        "beddo",
        "fuyu-yasumi",
        "gaikoku"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "gaikoku"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'travel / trip'?",
      "options": [
        "shukudai",
        "kurashikku",
        "ryokoo",
        "sooji (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ryokoo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'あきまつり'?",
      "options": [
        "imootosan",
        "aki-matsuri",
        "Kankoku",
        "〜go"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "aki-matsuri"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'アメリカ'?",
      "options": [
        "jibun",
        "ikebana",
        "soba",
        "Amerika"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Amerika"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'カレンダー'?",
      "options": [
        "neko",
        "naka",
        "karendaa",
        "hashi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "karendaa"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'tenisu'?",
      "options": [
        "things (found at home)",
        "light",
        "contest",
        "tennis"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tennis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'ocha'?",
      "options": [
        "さしみ",
        "おどり",
        "おちゃ",
        "せんぷうき"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おちゃ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'bedding'?",
      "options": [
        "futon",
        "yasui",
        "panfuretto",
        "ame"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "futon"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'おとうとさん'?",
      "options": [
        "fukushuu",
        "taihen",
        "otootosan",
        "konsaato"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "otootosan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'あつい'?",
      "options": [
        "video game / computer game",
        "old",
        "hot",
        "to sing"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hot"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to check'?",
      "options": [
        "テレビを　みます",
        "カーテン",
        "チェック（を）します",
        "メール／ E メール（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "チェック（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'カメラ'?",
      "options": [
        "ryuugakusee",
        "undoo (o) shimasu",
        "kamera",
        "yasashii"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kamera"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'あたたかい'?",
      "options": [
        "atatakai",
        "shoosetsu",
        "akarui",
        "tamanegi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "atatakai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'knife'?",
      "options": [
        "terebi",
        "uisukii",
        "jieegyoo",
        "naifu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "naifu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'chirashi'?",
      "options": [
        "(my) elder brother",
        "jazz",
        "leaflet / flyer",
        "baseball"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "leaflet / flyer"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Furansugo'?",
      "options": [
        "ひげを　そります",
        "クラス",
        "いもうとさん",
        "フランスご"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "フランスご"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'デパート'?",
      "options": [
        "department store",
        "quantity",
        "hot / spicy / salty",
        "Haiku"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "department store"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'passport'?",
      "options": [
        "tomato",
        "hako",
        "ninjin",
        "pasupooto"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "pasupooto"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'mono'?",
      "options": [
        "もの",
        "やすい",
        "つめたい",
        "アルバイト（バイト）"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "もの"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kissaten'?",
      "options": [
        "fried potatoes / french fries / chips",
        "busy",
        "Brazil",
        "coffee shop"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "coffee shop"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'classroom'?",
      "options": [
        "ofuro",
        "kyooshitsu",
        "tetsudaimasu",
        "ringo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kyooshitsu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'yasai'?",
      "options": [
        "scary / frightening",
        "vegetable",
        "apple",
        "next to"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "vegetable"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'orange'?",
      "options": [
        "hottodoggu",
        "nagai",
        "mikan",
        "minasan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "mikan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ane'?",
      "options": [
        "to make a phone call",
        "salt",
        "(my) elder sister",
        "dictionary"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(my) elder sister"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'piano'?",
      "options": [
        "to explain",
        "piano",
        "to write",
        "woman"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "piano"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'tea / Japanese tea'?",
      "options": [
        "jimushitsu",
        "ocha",
        "fantajii",
        "natsu-yasumi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ocha"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'natsu-yasumi'?",
      "options": [
        "なつやすみ",
        "なか",
        "アイロン",
        "ねこ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "なつやすみ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'たいこ'?",
      "options": [
        "retasu",
        "anata",
        "nagai",
        "taiko"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "taiko"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'France'?",
      "options": [
        "keshigomu",
        "Furansu",
        "Doitsugo",
        "shukudai"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Furansu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'やさい'?",
      "options": [
        "budoogari",
        "〜 o tabemasu",
        "yasai",
        "mizu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "yasai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kurai'?",
      "options": [
        "〜を　あげます",
        "くらい",
        "ふとん",
        "かぶき"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "くらい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'たのしい'?",
      "options": [
        "たのし い",
        "あなた",
        "かのじょ",
        "おすし／すし"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "たのし い"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ジャム'?",
      "options": [
        "jam",
        "table tennis / ping-pong",
        "hot (coffee / tea)",
        "big / large"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "jam"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'Indonesia'?",
      "options": [
        "terebi",
        "otoosan",
        "uisukii",
        "Indoneshia"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Indoneshia"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'nimotsu'?",
      "options": [
        "baggage / luggage",
        "camping / to go camping",
        "to have a meal",
        "anime / animated cartoons"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "baggage / luggage"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'ningyoo'?",
      "options": [
        "みます",
        "たのしい",
        "ホワイトボード",
        "にんぎょう"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "にんぎょう"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'まつり'?",
      "options": [
        "matsuri",
        "chawan",
        "banana",
        "genkan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "matsuri"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'プレゼント'?",
      "options": [
        "present",
        "near / close",
        "Japanese person",
        "egg"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "present"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'りゅうがくせい'?",
      "options": [
        "window",
        "student studying abroad / international student",
        "to play the guitar / piano",
        "bathroom / bath"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "student studying abroad / international student"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ざっし'?",
      "options": [
        "(my) younger brother",
        "card",
        "magazine",
        "banana"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "magazine"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'adult'?",
      "options": [
        "kaisha",
        "ribingu",
        "banana",
        "otona"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "otona"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Vietnam'?",
      "options": [
        "ベトナム",
        "スケート",
        "マレーシア",
        "さしみ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ベトナム"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'barbecue'?",
      "options": [
        "エアコン",
        "にほんりょうり",
        "にわ",
        "バーベキュー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "バーベキュー"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'uisukii'?",
      "options": [
        "とうふ",
        "スープ",
        "キャベツ",
        "ウイスキー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ウイスキー"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Please call me \"〜\"'?",
      "options": [
        "〜が　できます",
        "せんたく（を）します",
        "〜と よんでください",
        "かぐ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜と よんでください"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'nikki o kakimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "にっきを　かきます",
        "サラダ",
        "よこ",
        "きらい（な）"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "にっきを　かきます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'question / problem'?",
      "options": [
        "mondai",
        "yooshitsu",
        "tsumaranai",
        "sonohoka"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "mondai"
    },
    
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'おにいさん'?",
      "options": [
        "others",
        "(someone else's) elder brother",
        "wall",
        "visa"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(someone else's) elder brother"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to take a walk'?",
      "options": [
        "surippa",
        "sanpo (o) shimasu",
        "ebi",
        "yasui"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sanpo (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'エアコン'?",
      "options": [
        "eakon",
        "kazoku",
        "jieegyoo",
        "karee"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "eakon"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'むずかしい'?",
      "options": [
        "swimming in the sea",
        "difficult",
        "oneself",
        "suitcase"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "difficult"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'child'?",
      "options": [
        "こども",
        "なまえ",
        "ひと",
        "しょっぱい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "こども"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'baabekyuu'?",
      "options": [
        "to dance",
        "barbecue",
        "greetings",
        "skating"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "barbecue"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ねむい'?",
      "options": [
        "suteeki",
        "nemui",
        "tsukue",
        "Itaria"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "nemui"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'arubaito / baito (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "comedy",
        "souvenir",
        "grape picking",
        "to do a part-time job"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to do a part-time job"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ペン'?",
      "options": [
        "retasu",
        "mago",
        "yoshuu",
        "pen"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "pen"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'えいご'?",
      "options": [
        "Eego",
        "〜 ni tomarimasu",
        "tanjoobi",
        "koocha"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Eego"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for '〜 food / 〜 cuisine'?",
      "options": [
        "きもの",
        "スペインご",
        "〜りょうり",
        "おとうとさん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜りょうり"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kissaten'?",
      "options": [
        "おんな",
        "ゴールデンウィーク",
        "きっさてん",
        "しょっき"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "きっさてん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'fuyu-yasumi'?",
      "options": [
        "マレーシア",
        "ふゆやすみ",
        "ゆきまつり",
        "あに"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ふゆやすみ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ときどき'?",
      "options": [
        "kimono",
        "muzukashii",
        "jibun",
        "tokidoki"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tokidoki"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'crab'?",
      "options": [
        "トマト",
        "かに",
        "うれしい",
        "あさ／ひる／ばんごはんを　たべます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かに"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'koohii'?",
      "options": [
        "coffee",
        "woman / female",
        "(my) elder brother",
        "delicious / tasty"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "coffee"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'コンテスト'?",
      "options": [
        "oyu",
        "oshoogatsu",
        "Kanada",
        "kontesuto"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kontesuto"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'gakusee'?",
      "options": [
        "student",
        "student studying abroad / international student",
        "mobile phone / cellular phone",
        "taiko drumming"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "student"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'amai'?",
      "options": [
        "サンドイッチ",
        "あそびます",
        "あまい",
        "おにぎり（おむすび）"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "あまい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'hot dog'?",
      "options": [
        "おんな",
        "ホットドッグ",
        "こども",
        "エンジニア"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ホットドッグ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'sooji (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "textbook",
        "to clean",
        "electrical appliance",
        "cheese"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to clean"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'otoko'?",
      "options": [
        "always",
        "hot water",
        "(my) grandmother",
        "man / male"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "man / male"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for '〜と よんでください'?",
      "options": [
        "Please call me \"〜\"",
        "elderly person",
        "to listen",
        "knife"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Please call me \"〜\""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Japanese sake / rice wine'?",
      "options": [
        "にほんしゅ",
        "きっぷ",
        "ミステリー",
        "こうちゃ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "にほんしゅ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'otera'?",
      "options": [
        "temple",
        "karaoke",
        "woman",
        "swimming"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "temple"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'hige o sorimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "entrance",
        "class / school lessons",
        "door",
        "to shave"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to shave"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'こども'?",
      "options": [
        "kodomo",
        "gitaa",
        "yakyuu",
        "osoi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kodomo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'hikimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "SF",
        "ひきます",
        "テニス",
        "うどん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ひきます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'Chuugoku'?",
      "options": [
        "China",
        "literature",
        "French language",
        "(hard) candy"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "China"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'slippers'?",
      "options": [
        "スリッパ",
        "にほんご",
        "いつも",
        "チェック（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "スリッパ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'never'?",
      "options": [
        "zenzen",
        "oneesan",
        "tomodachi ni aimasu",
        "otoko-no-hito"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "zenzen"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'birthday'?",
      "options": [
        "ホット",
        "バースデー",
        "ページ",
        "おすし／すし"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "バースデー"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'にほん／にっぽん'?",
      "options": [
        "haiku",
        "Nihon / Nippon",
        "kagu",
        "sumoo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Nihon / Nippon"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'senpuuki'?",
      "options": [
        "electric fan",
        "unappetizing",
        "chicken",
        "miso soup"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "electric fan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'vacuum cleaner'?",
      "options": [
        "setsumee (o) shimasu",
        "J-poppu",
        "soojiki",
        "koomuin"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "soojiki"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'basketball'?",
      "options": [
        "basuketto-booru",
        "gaikokugo",
        "pan",
        "ureshii"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "basuketto-booru"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ojiisan'?",
      "options": [
        "Brazil",
        "spoon",
        "(someone else's) grandfather",
        "adult"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(someone else's) grandfather"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ブラジル'?",
      "options": [
        "Burajiru",
        "kingyo",
        "oshoogatsu",
        "matsuri"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Burajiru"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'reservation / booking (to make a reservation)'?",
      "options": [
        "よやく （を します）",
        "でんわ（を）します／かけます",
        "れい",
        "インターネット（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "よやく （を します）"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'カレー'?",
      "options": [
        "nimotsu",
        "jiko-shookai (shimasu)",
        "karee",
        "intaanetto (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "karee"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'yoku'?",
      "options": [
        "しゃしん（を　とります）",
        "ちいさい",
        "かいす いよく",
        "よ く"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "よ く"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to read'?",
      "options": [
        "kirai",
        "eakon",
        "ningyoo",
        "yomimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "yomimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'テニス'?",
      "options": [
        "fuku o nugimasu",
        "shoppai",
        "dekakemasu",
        "tenisu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tenisu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'table'?",
      "options": [
        "setsumee (o) shimasu",
        "isogashii",
        "tsumetai",
        "teeburu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "teeburu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ミステリー'?",
      "options": [
        "big / spacious / large",
        "mystery",
        "company employee",
        "Spanish language"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "mystery"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'Kabuki'?",
      "options": [
        "kaidan",
        "kabuki",
        "〜 ni tomarimasu",
        "oshi'ire"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kabuki"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'nemui'?",
      "options": [
        "festival / celebration",
        "whiteboard",
        "sleepy",
        "washing machine"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sleepy"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'naka'?",
      "options": [
        "cherry-blossom viewing",
        "ticket",
        "in / inside",
        "to clean"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "in / inside"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'チェック（を）します'?",
      "options": [
        "to check",
        "hot dog",
        "to cook",
        "light"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to check"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'hon'?",
      "options": [
        "コピー（を）します",
        "ほん",
        "ひと",
        "かなしい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ほん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kome'?",
      "options": [
        "suitcase",
        "yogurt",
        "rice",
        "entrance"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "rice"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'Judo'?",
      "options": [
        "juudoo",
        "anime",
        "mazui",
        "hito"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "juudoo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'salt'?",
      "options": [
        "tomodachi ga kimasu",
        "misuterii",
        "otera",
        "shio"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shio"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'zabuton'?",
      "options": [
        "たいこ",
        "かきます",
        "しゅみ",
        "ざぶとん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ざぶとん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'barbecue'?",
      "options": [
        "shinbun o yomimasu",
        "baabekyuu",
        "jamu",
        "gurasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "baabekyuu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ぎゅうにゅう／ミルク'?",
      "options": [
        "mobile phone / cellular phone",
        "milk",
        "student studying abroad / international student",
        "notebook"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "milk"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'shawaa o abimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "さどう",
        "シャワーを　あびます",
        "カレンダー",
        "たべもの"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "シャワーを　あびます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to study'?",
      "options": [
        "benkyoo (o) shimasu",
        "shufu",
        "chokoreeto",
        "koppu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "benkyoo (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'nagai'?",
      "options": [
        "にほんじん",
        "ながい",
        "かぶき",
        "やすみます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ながい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'かんこうち'?",
      "options": [
        "sakana",
        "pan",
        "shitsumon (o) shimasu",
        "kankoochi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kankoochi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'flower arrangement'?",
      "options": [
        "ファーストフードてん",
        "せまい",
        "いけばな",
        "きょうし"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "いけばな"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'chizu'?",
      "options": [
        "Canada",
        "to go out",
        "map",
        "movie / film"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "map"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'amai'?",
      "options": [
        "pork",
        "always",
        "sweet",
        "window"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sweet"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'おいしい'?",
      "options": [
        "otootosan",
        "okosan",
        "jazu",
        "oishii"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "oishii"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'golf'?",
      "options": [
        "ゴルフ",
        "メール／ E メール（を）します",
        "うさぎ",
        "ジャズ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ゴルフ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'レストラン'?",
      "options": [
        "restaurant",
        "guitar",
        "Canada",
        "Bonsai"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "restaurant"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for '〜 shop / restaurant'?",
      "options": [
        "うしろ",
        "ゴルフ",
        "〜や（さん）",
        "よみます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜や（さん）"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'fuku o kimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "(my) elder brother",
        "woman",
        "(my) wife",
        "to put on clothes"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to put on clothes"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'こめ'?",
      "options": [
        "wakamono",
        "kome",
        "kowai",
        "wasabi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kome"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'よやく （を します）'?",
      "options": [
        "Japanese language",
        "reservation / booking (to make a reservation)",
        "soccer / football",
        "mobile phone / cellular phone"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "reservation / booking (to make a reservation)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kurasu'?",
      "options": [
        "たっきゅう／ピンポン",
        "おばあさん",
        "ポップス",
        "クラス"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "クラス"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'goldfish'?",
      "options": [
        "denki",
        "〜 to yonde kudasai",
        "kingyo",
        "hako"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kingyo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'きれい（な）'?",
      "options": [
        "okosan",
        "bangoo",
        "kiree",
        "bijutsukan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kiree"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'wall'?",
      "options": [
        "kabe",
        "uta",
        "juudoo",
        "otooto"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kabe"
    },
  
    
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'koohii'?",
      "options": [
        "コーヒー",
        "つまらない",
        "いもうと",
        "ページ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "コーヒー"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to rest / take a rest'?",
      "options": [
        "やすみます",
        "つくえ",
        "アクション",
        "うさぎ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "やすみます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'wasabi'?",
      "options": [
        "woman / female",
        "seasonal events",
        "wasabi (Japanese horseradish)",
        "woman"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "wasabi (Japanese horseradish)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'おかあさん'?",
      "options": [
        "mimasu",
        "oshoogatsu",
        "okaasan",
        "naka"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "okaasan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'oinori (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "to pray",
        "language",
        "Vietnam",
        "to sing"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to pray"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'サラダ'?",
      "options": [
        "mazui",
        "yoga (o) shimasu",
        "sarada",
        "〜go"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sarada"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Egypt'?",
      "options": [
        "パートタイム（パート）",
        "かいしゃ",
        "ホット",
        "エジプト"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "エジプト"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ふくを　ぬぎます'?",
      "options": [
        "〜 shop / restaurant",
        "pizza",
        "to take off clothes",
        "always"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to take off clothes"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to write'?",
      "options": [
        "たかい",
        "おこさん",
        "でんわ",
        "かきます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かきます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'いぬ'?",
      "options": [
        "beside",
        "(someone else's) husband",
        "to read a newspaper",
        "dog"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "dog"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'danboo'?",
      "options": [
        "heater",
        "pop music",
        "barbecue",
        "English language"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "heater"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'always'?",
      "options": [
        "アイロン",
        "もみじがり",
        "けいたいでんわ",
        "い つも"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "い つも"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'さしみ'?",
      "options": [
        "Asia",
        "raw fish dish",
        "action",
        "to play a game"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "raw fish dish"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'light'?",
      "options": [
        "でんき",
        "キャンプ（を　します）",
        "チケット",
        "じゅこうしゃ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "でんき"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'にほんりょうり'?",
      "options": [
        "odori",
        "ofuro",
        "gohan",
        "nihon-ryoori"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "nihon-ryoori"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'tatami mat'?",
      "options": [
        "menyuu",
        "sooji (o) shimasu",
        "tatami",
        "ojiisan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tatami"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'otoko-no-hito'?",
      "options": [
        "man",
        "to go out",
        "orange juice",
        "watermelon"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "man"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'otona'?",
      "options": [
        "to keep a diary",
        "Sumo",
        "parents",
        "adult"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "adult"
    },
    
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'basuketto-booru'?",
      "options": [
        "basketball",
        "cup",
        "(hard) candy",
        "to put on clothes"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "basketball"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ひま（な）'?",
      "options": [
        "zenzen",
        "hima",
        "ibento",
        "juusu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hima"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'shokuji'?",
      "options": [
        "スーツケース",
        "しょくじ",
        "おどります",
        "えび"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "しょくじ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to dance'?",
      "options": [
        "もの",
        "さどう",
        "おどります",
        "サンドイッチ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おどります"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'oneself'?",
      "options": [
        "じぶん",
        "クラシック",
        "ロシア",
        "にほんご"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "じぶん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ハンガリー'?",
      "options": [
        "supagethi (pasuta)",
        "kangoshi",
        "Hangarii",
        "esu-efu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Hangarii"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to brush / clean one's teeth'?",
      "options": [
        "tori",
        "ha o migakimasu",
        "kurasu",
        "piza"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ha o migakimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'chiketto'?",
      "options": [
        "サラダ",
        "なっとう",
        "チケット",
        "ひま（な）"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "チケット"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kowai'?",
      "options": [
        "adult",
        "long",
        "visa",
        "scary / frightening"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "scary / frightening"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for '〜じん'?",
      "options": [
        "to chat with 〜",
        "people from … (nationality)",
        "table",
        "to put on clothes"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "people from … (nationality)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Japanese food'?",
      "options": [
        "たっきゅう／ピンポン",
        "まつり",
        "ラジオ",
        "にほんりょうり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "にほんりょうり"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ばつ'?",
      "options": [
        "preparation (for the lesson)",
        "adjectives",
        "cross (false)",
        "page"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "cross (false)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'わたし'?",
      "options": [
        "tempura",
        "I",
        "cake",
        "to look"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "I"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'まる'?",
      "options": [
        "hashi",
        "keetai-denwa",
        "fantajii",
        "maru"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "maru"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'sour'?",
      "options": [
        "suppai",
        "Furansugo",
        "musuko",
        "yasumimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "suppai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ramen noodles'?",
      "options": [
        "kaimono (o) shimasu",
        "〜 ya (san)",
        "raamen",
        "hanashimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "raamen"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to explain'?",
      "options": [
        "Suriranka",
        "yakyuu",
        "setsumee (o) shimasu",
        "sofu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "setsumee (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Tai'?",
      "options": [
        "もの",
        "れんしゅう（を）します",
        "おけしょう（を）します",
        "タイ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "タイ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ぶどう'?",
      "options": [
        "easy",
        "suitcase",
        "bookshelf",
        "grapes"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "grapes"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tomato'?",
      "options": [
        "バースデー",
        "トマト",
        "みます",
        "コンピューター"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "トマト"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'housewife / homemaker'?",
      "options": [
        "otoko-no-hito",
        "orenji-juusu",
        "shufu",
        "watashi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shufu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Japan'?",
      "options": [
        "おとうさん",
        "にほん／にっぽん",
        "ロック",
        "うさぎ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "にほん／にっぽん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'Fujisan'?",
      "options": [
        "Mt. Fuji",
        "(my) elder brother",
        "to play the guitar / piano",
        "garden"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Mt. Fuji"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'hanabi'?",
      "options": [
        "to chat with 〜",
        "fireworks",
        "South Korea",
        "to do exercise"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "fireworks"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'おんなのこ'?",
      "options": [
        "to take a shower",
        "tatami mat",
        "girl",
        "Judo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "girl"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to listen'?",
      "options": [
        "osushi / sushi",
        "kikimasu",
        "sanpo (o) shimasu",
        "kyooshi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kikimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'tomodachi'?",
      "options": [
        "friend",
        "bed",
        "tableware",
        "origami"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "friend"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'golf'?",
      "options": [
        "otoshiyori",
        "gorufu",
        "Yooroppa",
        "kontesuto"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "gorufu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Europe'?",
      "options": [
        "バースデー",
        "ギター",
        "ヨーロッパ",
        "〜を　のみます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ヨーロッパ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'keetai-denwa'?",
      "options": [
        "うさぎ",
        "がいこくご",
        "キャベツ",
        "けいたいでんわ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "けいたいでんわ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'shoosetsu'?",
      "options": [
        "しゅふ",
        "ごしゅじん",
        "しょうせつ",
        "コンピューター"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "しょうせつ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'いま'?",
      "options": [
        "hot / spicy / salty",
        "floor cushion",
        "fruit",
        "living room"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "living room"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'otoshiyori'?",
      "options": [
        "おとしより",
        "よこ",
        "マンガ",
        "さむい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おとしより"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'かおを　あらいます'?",
      "options": [
        "fuku o kimasu",
        "〜 to oshaberi (o) shimasu",
        "yukkuri shimasu",
        "kao o araimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kao o araimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'konpyuutaa'?",
      "options": [
        "コンピューター",
        "カード",
        "とこのま",
        "こうむいん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "コンピューター"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'れい'?",
      "options": [
        "example",
        "kitchen",
        "miso soup",
        "fish"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "example"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'まえ'?",
      "options": [
        "Europe",
        "whisky",
        "front",
        "sugar"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "front"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'cereal'?",
      "options": [
        "kurasu",
        "Yooroppa",
        "tsukue",
        "shiriaru"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shiriaru"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'かいもの（を）します'?",
      "options": [
        "kazoku",
        "terebi",
        "jibun",
        "kaimono (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kaimono (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for '(someone else's) grandmother'?",
      "options": [
        "アメリカ",
        "おばあさん",
        "ゲーム（を）します",
        "ちゃわん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おばあさん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Spain'?",
      "options": [
        "スペイン",
        "せんたく（を）します",
        "じゃがいも",
        "にほん／にっぽん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "スペイン"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'クラシック'?",
      "options": [
        "pork",
        "tableware",
        "classical music",
        "coffee"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "classical music"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'shrimp / prawn'?",
      "options": [
        "えび",
        "ねむい",
        "とり",
        "やさい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "えび"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'hospital'?",
      "options": [
        "soba",
        "byooin",
        "shukudai",
        "resutoran"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "byooin"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kyuuri'?",
      "options": [
        "homework",
        "cucumber",
        "teacher / instructor",
        "washing machine"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "cucumber"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'かに'?",
      "options": [
        "bataa",
        "Indo",
        "gooruden-uiiku",
        "kani"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kani"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'okeshoo (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "おじいさん",
        "おけしょう（を）します",
        "ふくしゅう",
        "ちょっと"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おけしょう（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kaaten'?",
      "options": [
        "curtain",
        "telephone",
        "bright",
        "hotel / Japanese inn"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "curtain"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'benkyoo (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "コピー（を）します",
        "こども",
        "べんきょう（を）します",
        "はを　みがきます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "べんきょう（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'alcoholic drinks / Japanese sake'?",
      "options": [
        "matsuri",
        "osake",
        "tesuto",
        "Chuugoku"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "osake"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'office room'?",
      "options": [
        "sakana",
        "jimushitsu",
        "fusuma",
        "taihen"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "jimushitsu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'yuki-matsuri'?",
      "options": [
        "ゆきま つり",
        "インターネット（を）します",
        "じむしつ",
        "ヨガ（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ゆきま つり"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'アイスクリーム'?",
      "options": [
        "pen",
        "Afurika",
        "gaikokujin",
        "aisu-kuriimu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "aisu-kuriimu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'iimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "tomato",
        "to say / to tell",
        "origami",
        "(my) grandfather"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to say / to tell"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to take care of / look after'?",
      "options": [
        "〜の　せわをします",
        "はくぶつかん",
        "よこ",
        "がいこくじん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜の　せわをします"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kagu'?",
      "options": [
        "movie / film",
        "furniture",
        "question / problem",
        "scary / frightening"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "furniture"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'raamen'?",
      "options": [
        "chopsticks",
        "quantity",
        "ramen noodles",
        "rabbit"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ramen noodles"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'jagaimo'?",
      "options": [
        "じゃがいも",
        "ねむい",
        "やきそば",
        "ぶどうがり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "じゃがいも"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'often'?",
      "options": [
        "sadoo",
        "otoko",
        "yoku",
        "menyuu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "yoku"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'hiru-gohan'?",
      "options": [
        "foreigner",
        "to play",
        "microwave oven",
        "lunch"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "lunch"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'りょかん'?",
      "options": [
        "Doitsugo",
        "misoshiru",
        "imooto",
        "ryokan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ryokan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'cake'?",
      "options": [
        "とうきょう",
        "アジア",
        "りょこう",
        "ケーキ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ケーキ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'あまり'?",
      "options": [
        "atsui",
        "akachan",
        "ningyoo",
        "amari"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "amari"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'mono'?",
      "options": [
        "spoon",
        "out / outside",
        "eraser",
        "things (found at home)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "things (found at home)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'やすい'?",
      "options": [
        "uchi ni kaerimasu",
        "yasui",
        "kanojo",
        "tenisu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "yasui"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'yogurt'?",
      "options": [
        "mondai",
        "suppai",
        "enpitsu",
        "yooguruto"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "yooguruto"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'けいたいでんわ'?",
      "options": [
        "water",
        "mobile phone / cellular phone",
        "shrine",
        "soccer / football"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "mobile phone / cellular phone"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'whisky'?",
      "options": [
        "usagi",
        "mago",
        "oinori (o) shimasu",
        "uisukii"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "uisukii"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for '〜に　いきます'?",
      "options": [
        "to go to 〜",
        "to smoke",
        "swimming in the sea",
        "friend"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to go to 〜"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'mazui'?",
      "options": [
        "ミステリー",
        "まずい",
        "つり（を　します）",
        "ばんごはん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "まずい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'フォーク'?",
      "options": [
        "fooku",
        "kaisuiyoku",
        "origami",
        "washitsu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "fooku"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'オレンジジュース'?",
      "options": [
        "momijigari",
        "orenji-juusu",
        "watashi",
        "nooto"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "orenji-juusu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'minna'?",
      "options": [
        "to have a conversation",
        "everyone",
        "festival / celebration",
        "sofa"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "everyone"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tori'?",
      "options": [
        "ホテル",
        "〜を　もらいます",
        "とり",
        "ジョギング"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "とり"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'strawberry'?",
      "options": [
        "ichigo",
        "sumoo",
        "ree",
        "howaito-boodo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ichigo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'suika'?",
      "options": [
        "winter holidays",
        "watermelon",
        "France",
        "nearby"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "watermelon"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to look like 〜'?",
      "options": [
        "〜 ni nite imasu ne",
        "Nihongo",
        "ryoori (o) shimasu",
        "Burajiru"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜 ni nite imasu ne"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'たたみ'?",
      "options": [
        "action",
        "kitchen",
        "beautiful / pretty",
        "tatami mat"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tatami mat"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'くうこう'?",
      "options": [
        "ofuro",
        "kuukoo",
        "karendaa",
        "denki-seehin"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kuukoo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'tana'?",
      "options": [
        "in / inside",
        "suitcase",
        "shelf",
        "lettuce"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shelf"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'peeji'?",
      "options": [
        "page",
        "woman",
        "tennis",
        "spaghetti / pasta"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "page"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kikimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "sweet",
        "to check",
        "textbook",
        "to listen"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to listen"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Eego'?",
      "options": [
        "えいご",
        "ちち",
        "まる",
        "やさしい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "えいご"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'untidy / dirty'?",
      "options": [
        "ドイツ",
        "となり",
        "きたない",
        "アニメ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "きたない"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'スプーン'?",
      "options": [
        "tabemono",
        "yamanobori (o shimasu)",
        "beddo-ruumu",
        "supuun"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "supuun"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'chikaku'?",
      "options": [
        "とこのま",
        "ドイツ",
        "いま",
        "ちかく"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ちかく"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'suutsukeesu'?",
      "options": [
        "ラジオ",
        "ねます",
        "つめたい",
        "スーツケース"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "スーツケース"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'electrical appliance'?",
      "options": [
        "ベッド",
        "にほんしゅ",
        "でんきせいひん",
        "あいさつ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "でんきせいひん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'ii'?",
      "options": [
        "いい",
        "だんぼう",
        "ホテル",
        "ざんぎょう（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "いい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'おんなのひと'?",
      "options": [
        "(my) elder sister",
        "woman",
        "swimming",
        "nurse"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "woman"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'ibento'?",
      "options": [
        "イベント",
        "チラシ",
        "ゲーム",
        "やきゅう"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "イベント"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'cola'?",
      "options": [
        "kabe",
        "koora",
        "niwa",
        "jukoosha"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "koora"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'gaikoku'?",
      "options": [
        "がいこく",
        "にほんしゅ",
        "キャベツ",
        "〜や（さん）"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "がいこく"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ringo'?",
      "options": [
        "apple",
        "to take care of / look after",
        "dance",
        "nice / good"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "apple"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'batsu'?",
      "options": [
        "エンジニア",
        "ばつ",
        "ひと",
        "ゴルフ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ばつ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'はを　みがきます'?",
      "options": [
        "to listen to music",
        "to brush / clean one's teeth",
        "(my) son",
        "to have a meal"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to brush / clean one's teeth"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ジョギング'?",
      "options": [
        "〜 no sewa o shimasu",
        "byooin",
        "karaoke",
        "jogingu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "jogingu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'the Philippines'?",
      "options": [
        "Firipin",
        "baabekyuu",
        "takusan",
        "okimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Firipin"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'amari'?",
      "options": [
        "elderly person",
        "company / firm",
        "cereal",
        "(not) often"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(not) often"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'atatakai'?",
      "options": [
        "warm",
        "iron",
        "autumn festival",
        "skating"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "warm"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'かいごし'?",
      "options": [
        "beddo-ruumu",
        "konpyuutaa",
        "kaigoshi",
        "ryokoo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kaigoshi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to eat 〜'?",
      "options": [
        "すもう",
        "とうきょう",
        "かに",
        "〜を　たべます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜を　たべます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kudamono'?",
      "options": [
        "fishing / to go fishing",
        "under / below",
        "to go home",
        "fruit"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "fruit"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kao o araimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "show",
        "to wash one's face",
        "coffee",
        "to help"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to wash one's face"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'さかな'?",
      "options": [
        "oneesan",
        "kissaten",
        "sakana",
        "Roshia"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sakana"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'microwave oven'?",
      "options": [
        "resutoran",
        "denshi-renji",
        "watashitachi",
        "nemui"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "denshi-renji"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'preparation (for the lesson)'?",
      "options": [
        "okeshoo (o) shimasu",
        "yoshuu",
        "yuki-matsuri",
        "otootosan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "yoshuu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'まご'?",
      "options": [
        "sofa",
        "naifu",
        "mago",
        "watashitachi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "mago"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'fast-food restaurant'?",
      "options": [
        "ribingu",
        "omoshiroi",
        "isogashii",
        "faasuto-fuudo-ten"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "faasuto-fuudo-ten"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'amazing / wonderful'?",
      "options": [
        "そうだん（を）します",
        "すばらしい",
        "ちち",
        "つめたい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "すばらしい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ばんごう'?",
      "options": [
        "number",
        "pencil",
        "taiko drumming",
        "museum"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "number"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'oneesan'?",
      "options": [
        "(someone else's) elder sister",
        "iced (coffee / tea)",
        "everyone",
        "to take care of / look after"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(someone else's) elder sister"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'えび'?",
      "options": [
        "shrimp / prawn",
        "curtain",
        "you",
        "answer"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shrimp / prawn"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'fireworks display'?",
      "options": [
        "やすみます",
        "おとしより",
        "かに",
        "はなびた いかい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "はなびた いかい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'おさけ／さけ'?",
      "options": [
        "プレゼント",
        "エアコン",
        "おさけ",
        "かんこ うち"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おさけ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'whiteboard'?",
      "options": [
        "washitsu",
        "hanabi-taikai",
        "howaito-boodo",
        "supuun"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "howaito-boodo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ヨーロッパ'?",
      "options": [
        "Japanese food",
        "(not) at all",
        "Europe",
        "chair"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Europe"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'かんこうち'?",
      "options": [
        "tourist spot / sightseeing area",
        "breakfast",
        "Spanish language",
        "myself / me"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tourist spot / sightseeing area"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'fireworks display'?",
      "options": [
        "kissaten",
        "shashin (o torimasu)",
        "keetai-denwa",
        "hanabi-taikai"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hanabi-taikai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ラジオ'?",
      "options": [
        "ame",
        "hon",
        "ryuugakusee",
        "rajio"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "rajio"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'バースデー'?",
      "options": [
        "baasudee",
        "shoppai",
        "e (o kakimasu)",
        "〜ga dekimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "baasudee"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'sandoicchi'?",
      "options": [
        "bookshelf",
        "beautiful / pretty",
        "doll",
        "sandwich"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sandwich"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ステーキ'?",
      "options": [
        "suteeki",
        "〜go",
        "goshujin",
        "akachan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "suteeki"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'answer'?",
      "options": [
        "kotae",
        "zenzen",
        "sandoicchi",
        "Kanada"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kotae"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'コンサート'?",
      "options": [
        "cereal",
        "concert",
        "to tidy up",
        "to cook"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "concert"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ひと'?",
      "options": [
        "minasan",
        "shita",
        "hito",
        "shukudai"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hito"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'オレンジジュース'?",
      "options": [
        "orange juice",
        "homework",
        "to take off clothes",
        "quantity"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "orange juice"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'suppai'?",
      "options": [
        "すっぱい",
        "つかれます",
        "さむい",
        "がいこくご"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "すっぱい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'soto'?",
      "options": [
        "フィリピン",
        "インターネット（を）します",
        "〜の　せわをします",
        "そと"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "そと"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'reservation / booking (to make a reservation)'?",
      "options": [
        "tamanegi",
        "senpuuki",
        "yoyaku (o shimasu)",
        "sanpo (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "yoyaku (o shimasu)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'しょくじ（を）します'?",
      "options": [
        "shokuji (o) shimasu",
        "yasumimasu",
        "pasupooto",
        "hikimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shokuji (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ちゅうごく'?",
      "options": [
        "Furansugo",
        "kuukoo",
        "Chuugoku",
        "dansu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Chuugoku"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'toilet'?",
      "options": [
        "かおを　あらいます",
        "えいが",
        "トイレ",
        "たっきゅう／ピンポン"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "トイレ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'なまえ'?",
      "options": [
        "kaimono (o) shimasu",
        "okashi",
        "namae",
        "keetai-denwa"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "namae"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'mado'?",
      "options": [
        "どくしょ",
        "そうじ（を）します",
        "コーヒー",
        "まど"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "まど"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'myself / me'?",
      "options": [
        "keshigomu",
        "sanpo (o) shimasu",
        "musuko",
        "watashi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "watashi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'Malaysia'?",
      "options": [
        "kirai",
        "Mareeshia",
        "haiku",
        "tamago"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Mareeshia"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'bread'?",
      "options": [
        "パン",
        "カップ",
        "でんわ",
        "かいすいよく"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "パン"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'sakkaa'?",
      "options": [
        "〜を　あげます",
        "みかん",
        "サッカー",
        "すいえい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "サッカー"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ピザ'?",
      "options": [
        "piza",
        "kingyo",
        "toriniku / chikin",
        "udon"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "piza"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'Korean language'?",
      "options": [
        "Kankokugo",
        "taiko",
        "nori",
        "karendaa"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Kankokugo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for '(my) daughter'?",
      "options": [
        "コメディ",
        "むすめ",
        "こたえ",
        "ほん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "むすめ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'きょうかしょ'?",
      "options": [
        "table",
        "mountain-climbing (to climb a mountain)",
        "textbook",
        "to get tired"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "textbook"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'foreigner'?",
      "options": [
        "でんき",
        "さんぽ（を）します",
        "がいこくじん",
        "さとう"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "がいこくじん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'haha'?",
      "options": [
        "かぐ",
        "せつめい（を）します",
        "なつやすみ",
        "はは"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "はは"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'クラス'?",
      "options": [
        "friend",
        "salty",
        "class / lesson",
        "oneself"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "class / lesson"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'suika'?",
      "options": [
        "おしいれ",
        "だんぼう",
        "すいか",
        "ファンタジー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "すいか"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'man'?",
      "options": [
        "おとこのひと",
        "ともだち",
        "テレビを　みます",
        "でんきせいひん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おとこのひと"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'spaghetti / pasta'?",
      "options": [
        "jugyoo",
        "ryokoo",
        "supagethi (pasuta)",
        "panfuretto"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "supagethi (pasuta)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ドイツご'?",
      "options": [
        "paatotaimu (paato)",
        "Doitsugo",
        "furaido-poteto",
        "tomato"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Doitsugo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'パンフレット'?",
      "options": [
        "ofuro",
        "panfuretto",
        "kyuuri",
        "yoyaku (o shimasu)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "panfuretto"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'SF'?",
      "options": [
        "to copy",
        "science fiction",
        "cabbage",
        "child"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "science fiction"
    },
    
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'happy / glad / delighted'?",
      "options": [
        "いそがしい",
        "すいえい",
        "うれしい",
        "ホテル"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "うれしい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'atarashii'?",
      "options": [
        "baby",
        "on / above",
        "Japanese food",
        "new"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "new"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'student studying abroad / international student'?",
      "options": [
        "asobimasu",
        "Tookyoo",
        "ryuugakusee",
        "reezooko"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ryuugakusee"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'itsumo'?",
      "options": [
        "そうじき",
        "ペン",
        "いつも",
        "ステーキ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "いつも"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ノート'?",
      "options": [
        "rabbit",
        "notebook",
        "travel / trip",
        "baggage / luggage"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "notebook"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'cake'?",
      "options": [
        "kaimono (o) shimasu",
        "hima",
        "keeki",
        "kurai"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "keeki"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'cheese'?",
      "options": [
        "kotae",
        "kippu",
        "chiizu",
        "sukeeto"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "chiizu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'sweets / confectionery'?",
      "options": [
        "カナダ",
        "ナイフ",
        "おかし",
        "え"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おかし"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ぶたにく／ポーク'?",
      "options": [
        "always",
        "to draw",
        "unappetizing",
        "pork"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "pork"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'shrimp / prawn'?",
      "options": [
        "ebi",
        "chotto",
        "kagu",
        "dansu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ebi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'hanami'?",
      "options": [
        "つまらない",
        "でんわ（を）します／かけます",
        "さんぽ（を）します",
        "はなみ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "はなみ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'akachan'?",
      "options": [
        "number",
        "mountain-climbing (to climb a mountain)",
        "baby",
        "piano"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "baby"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'カレンダー'?",
      "options": [
        "(my) grandmother",
        "calendar",
        "door",
        "Western-style room"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "calendar"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'remon'?",
      "options": [
        "じむしつ",
        "レモン",
        "いもうと",
        "さどう"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "レモン"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to cook'?",
      "options": [
        "ryoori (o) shimasu",
        "suteeki",
        "〜jin",
        "paathii"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ryoori (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'しょっき'?",
      "options": [
        "bentoo",
        "jibun",
        "shokki",
        "jukoosha"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shokki"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kopii (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "to copy",
        "to go home",
        "never",
        "soccer / football"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to copy"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'New Year's visit to a shrine or temple'?",
      "options": [
        "hatsu-moode",
        "aisu",
        "arubaito / baito (o) shimasu",
        "jibun"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hatsu-moode"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'Germany'?",
      "options": [
        "Doitsu",
        "yoshuu",
        "pasupooto",
        "hottodoggu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Doitsu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'New Zealand'?",
      "options": [
        "ニュージーランド",
        "おんなのこ",
        "そうじき",
        "にもつ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ニュージーランド"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'あなた'?",
      "options": [
        "budoogari",
        "nori",
        "kaigoshi",
        "anata"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "anata"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to do a part-time job'?",
      "options": [
        "jimushitsu",
        "zangyoo (o) shimasu",
        "arubaito / baito (o) shimasu",
        "kissaten"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "arubaito / baito (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'レモン'?",
      "options": [
        "shoosetsu",
        "remon",
        "yamanobori (o shimasu)",
        "kontesuto"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "remon"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ぼんおどり'?",
      "options": [
        "strawberry",
        "Bon Festival dance",
        "answer",
        "radio"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Bon Festival dance"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'watashi'?",
      "options": [
        "わたし",
        "かいしゃ",
        "チケット",
        "たかい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "わたし"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'おもしろい'?",
      "options": [
        "interesting",
        "telephone",
        "summer holidays",
        "wine"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "interesting"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'Suriranka'?",
      "options": [
        "rice",
        "whiteboard",
        "Sri Lanka",
        "rice bowl"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Sri Lanka"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to play the guitar / piano'?",
      "options": [
        "hikimasu",
        "Hangarii",
        "ren'ai",
        "ureshii"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hikimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'うどん'?",
      "options": [
        "udon noodles",
        "to read",
        "steak",
        "cooked rice"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "udon noodles"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'karendaa'?",
      "options": [
        "カレンダー",
        "きもの",
        "でんしレンジ",
        "バーベキュー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "カレンダー"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for '〜を　たべます'?",
      "options": [
        "hito",
        "mizu",
        "〜 o tabemasu",
        "sobo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜 o tabemasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kiree'?",
      "options": [
        "air conditioner",
        "on / above",
        "slow",
        "beautiful / pretty"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "beautiful / pretty"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tabemono'?",
      "options": [
        "みそしる",
        "たべもの",
        "ジャム",
        "みんな"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "たべもの"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'mago'?",
      "options": [
        "wine",
        "grandchild",
        "nice / good",
        "balcony"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "grandchild"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'そふ'?",
      "options": [
        "oishii",
        "sofu",
        "koocha",
        "tomodachi ni aimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sofu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'とけい'?",
      "options": [
        "cabbage",
        "festival / celebration",
        "summer holidays",
        "clock"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "clock"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ちかく'?",
      "options": [
        "fast-food restaurant",
        "name",
        "nearby",
        "out / outside"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "nearby"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'Amerika'?",
      "options": [
        "U.S.A. / America",
        "quantity",
        "egg",
        "nurse"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "U.S.A. / America"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'trip / to go on a trip'?",
      "options": [
        "りょこう",
        "げんかん",
        "ヨーロッパ",
        "まつり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "りょこう"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'した'?",
      "options": [
        "geemu",
        "shita",
        "haiku",
        "Supeingo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shita"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'yomimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "しゅくだい",
        "べんきょう（を）します",
        "きょうし",
        "よみます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "よみます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'hima'?",
      "options": [
        "かぞく",
        "きっぷ",
        "ベランダ",
        "ひま（な）"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ひま（な）"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'renshuu (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "れんしゅう（を）します",
        "れい",
        "おんがくを　ききます",
        "アラビアご"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "れんしゅう（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'supuun'?",
      "options": [
        "すばらしい",
        "スプーン",
        "ちいさい",
        "おちゃ／ちゃ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "スプーン"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'breakfast'?",
      "options": [
        "ホットドッグ",
        "あさごはん",
        "〜ご",
        "うさぎ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "あさごはん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'にわ'?",
      "options": [
        "chiketto",
        "niwa",
        "karai",
        "hotto"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "niwa"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'びょういん'?",
      "options": [
        "mazui",
        "byooin",
        "onigiri (omusubi)",
        "sandoicchi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "byooin"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'しんぶんを　よみます'?",
      "options": [
        "kappu",
        "shinbun o yomimasu",
        "〜 o agemasu",
        "mae"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shinbun o yomimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'gitaa'?",
      "options": [
        "くらい",
        "あかちゃん",
        "ギター",
        "すこし"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ギター"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'てんぷら'?",
      "options": [
        "onna-no-hito",
        "wain",
        "tenpura",
        "musuko"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tenpura"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'warm'?",
      "options": [
        "あたたかい",
        "ふゆやすみ",
        "まる",
        "たべもの"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "あたたかい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'strawberry'?",
      "options": [
        "おっと",
        "いちご",
        "あかちゃん",
        "きゅうり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "いちご"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'soodan (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "poster",
        "to do exercise",
        "I",
        "to consult / to discuss"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to consult / to discuss"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'basuketto-booru'?",
      "options": [
        "ロック",
        "バスケットボール",
        "ばんごう",
        "ジャム"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "バスケットボール"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'Nihon / Nippon'?",
      "options": [
        "to go out",
        "Japan",
        "breakfast",
        "(my) wife"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Japan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'yoga (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "スペインご",
        "しゅくだい",
        "ヨガ（を）します",
        "にんぎょう"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ヨガ（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'whiteboard'?",
      "options": [
        "フランス",
        "しょっぱい",
        "ホワイトボード",
        "きょうしつ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ホワイトボード"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'shelf'?",
      "options": [
        "たな",
        "しょくじ",
        "たんじょうび",
        "コメディ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "たな"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ともだちが　きます'?",
      "options": [
        "washing machine",
        "a friend comes to visit",
        "jam",
        "cheese"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "a friend comes to visit"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'woman / female'?",
      "options": [
        "ninjin",
        "onna",
        "koomuin",
        "chokoreeto"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "onna"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to help'?",
      "options": [
        "Kankoku",
        "retasu",
        "ofuro",
        "tetsudaimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tetsudaimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'shio'?",
      "options": [
        "salt",
        "student studying abroad / international student",
        "bedroom",
        "dog"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "salt"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'natsu-yasumi'?",
      "options": [
        "いしゃ",
        "すき",
        "パスポ ート",
        "なつや すみ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "なつや すみ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ゴルフ'?",
      "options": [
        "cross (false)",
        "crab",
        "golf",
        "test"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "golf"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to play a game'?",
      "options": [
        "にっきを　かきます",
        "たかい",
        "ゲーム（を）します",
        "ふくしゅう"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ゲーム（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'rabbit'?",
      "options": [
        "usagi",
        "akushon",
        "bataa",
        "arubaito (baito)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "usagi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'cookie'?",
      "options": [
        "uisukii",
        "〜 ni tomarimasu",
        "kukkii",
        "osushi / sushi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kukkii"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'けいようし'?",
      "options": [
        "keeyooshi",
        "Nyuujiirando",
        "furui",
        "suiee"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "keeyooshi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'はは'?",
      "options": [
        "shashin",
        "haha",
        "jieegyoo",
        "konpyuutaa"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "haha"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'shiriaru'?",
      "options": [
        "(someone else's) elder brother",
        "camera",
        "cereal",
        "knife"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "cereal"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'くうこう'?",
      "options": [
        "airport",
        "song",
        "to play a game",
        "concert"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "airport"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'hotto'?",
      "options": [
        "だいどころ",
        "けいようし",
        "ホット",
        "おしょうがつ／しょうがつ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ホット"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'purezento'?",
      "options": [
        "ちゅうごく",
        "きょうし",
        "あきまつり",
        "プレゼント"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "プレゼント"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'utaimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "to sing",
        "preparation (for the lesson)",
        "bread",
        "butter"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to sing"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'しゅくだい'?",
      "options": [
        "rice ball",
        "homework",
        "chair",
        "event"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "homework"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'soup'?",
      "options": [
        "じむしつ",
        "おばあさん",
        "スープ",
        "オレンジジュース"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "スープ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'party'?",
      "options": [
        "せんたくき",
        "しんぶんを　よみます",
        "さら",
        "パーティー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "パーティー"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ざぶとん'?",
      "options": [
        "cheese burger",
        "floor cushion",
        "Japanese language",
        "literature"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "floor cushion"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'renshuu (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "oneself",
        "tourist spot / sightseeing area",
        "civil servant",
        "to practice"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to practice"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kyabetsu'?",
      "options": [
        "いつも",
        "つかれます",
        "ふじさん",
        "キャベツ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "キャベツ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'baggage / luggage'?",
      "options": [
        "ningyoo",
        "oneesan",
        "fooku",
        "nimotsu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "nimotsu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'karai'?",
      "options": [
        "homework",
        "present",
        "hot / spicy / salty",
        "medical doctor"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hot / spicy / salty"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for '〜 to oshaberi (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "あかるい",
        "コーラ",
        "まずい",
        "〜と　おしゃべり（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜と　おしゃべり（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Brazil'?",
      "options": [
        "ブラジル",
        "ジャム",
        "わかもの",
        "ちょっと"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ブラジル"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'shelf'?",
      "options": [
        "tana",
        "soodan (o) shimasu",
        "pen",
        "reezooko"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tana"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'にっきを　かきます'?",
      "options": [
        "tatami",
        "toriniku / chikin",
        "yooshitsu",
        "nikki o kakimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "nikki o kakimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'pasupooto'?",
      "options": [
        "あかるい",
        "まえ",
        "パスポート",
        "おりがみ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "パスポート"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'mizu'?",
      "options": [
        "goldfish",
        "microwave oven",
        "nearby",
        "water"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "water"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'やきそば'?",
      "options": [
        "sumoo",
        "ebi",
        "oniisan",
        "yakisoba"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "yakisoba"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'sumoo'?",
      "options": [
        "すもう",
        "せんせい",
        "すばらしい",
        "まる"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "すもう"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'maru'?",
      "options": [
        "to use / surf the Internet",
        "vacuum cleaner",
        "circle (true)",
        "tempura"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "circle (true)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'akushon'?",
      "options": [
        "suitcase",
        "to have a meal",
        "to cook",
        "action"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "action"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'restaurant'?",
      "options": [
        "toire",
        "ofuro",
        "juusu",
        "resutoran"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "resutoran"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ビザ'?",
      "options": [
        "Betonamu",
        "〜 o nomimasu",
        "yukkuri shimasu",
        "biza"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "biza"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'Japanese person'?",
      "options": [
        "jazu",
        "Nihonjin",
        "mae",
        "hatsu-moode"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Nihonjin"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to take a shower'?",
      "options": [
        "shinbun o yomimasu",
        "suteeki",
        "shawaa o abimasu",
        "kaisha"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shawaa o abimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'べんとう'?",
      "options": [
        "tanoshii",
        "bentoo",
        "niku",
        "remon"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "bentoo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'eraser'?",
      "options": [
        "けしごむ",
        "いま",
        "メニュー",
        "はは"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "けしごむ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'sobo'?",
      "options": [
        "ジャム",
        "りょこう",
        "そぼ",
        "なつまつり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "そぼ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'sugar'?",
      "options": [
        "suteeki",
        "kyanpu (o shimasu)",
        "yakisoba",
        "satoo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "satoo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'みそしる'?",
      "options": [
        "civil servant",
        "to pray",
        "miso soup",
        "to wash clothes"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "miso soup"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Chuugoku'?",
      "options": [
        "おんがくを　ききます",
        "ちゅうごく",
        "にほんしゅ",
        "かに"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ちゅうごく"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for '(my) younger brother'?",
      "options": [
        "otooto",
        "sandoicchi",
        "uchi ni kaerimasu",
        "basuketto-booru"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "otooto"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'じえいぎょう'?",
      "options": [
        "self-employed",
        "Tokyo",
        "steak",
        "example"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "self-employed"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'Australia'?",
      "options": [
        "howaito-boodo",
        "shio",
        "Oosutoraria",
        "doa"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Oosutoraria"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'mobile phone / cellular phone'?",
      "options": [
        "kome",
        "shokuji (o) shimasu",
        "toofu",
        "keetai-denwa"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "keetai-denwa"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'natsu-matsuri'?",
      "options": [
        "Egypt",
        "summer festival",
        "fork",
        "to take a shower"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "summer festival"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'biza'?",
      "options": [
        "〜 language",
        "visa",
        "cooking / dish",
        "question / problem"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "visa"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'おすし／すし'?",
      "options": [
        "Hangarii",
        "osushi / sushi",
        "bungaku",
        "kotae"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "osushi / sushi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'under / below'?",
      "options": [
        "パスポート",
        "ドイツ",
        "した",
        "しゃしん（を　とります）"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "した"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ごはん／ライス'?",
      "options": [
        "temple",
        "cooked rice",
        "things (found at home)",
        "manga / comic strips / comic books"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "cooked rice"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'onigiri (omusubi)'?",
      "options": [
        "おにぎり（おむすび）",
        "しょっき",
        "コンサート",
        "スリランカ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おにぎり（おむすび）"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to write / send an e-mail'?",
      "options": [
        "kisetsu no ibento",
        "〜go",
        "E-meeru (o) shimasu",
        "obaasan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "E-meeru (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'inexpensive / cheap'?",
      "options": [
        "しゃしん（を　とります）",
        "ページ",
        "やすい",
        "きょうし"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "やすい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'romance / love story'?",
      "options": [
        "ren'ai",
        "ree",
        "Firipin",
        "kaisha"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ren'ai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'restaurant'?",
      "options": [
        "tsuma",
        "itsumo",
        "resutoran",
        "koora"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "resutoran"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'がいこくご／〜ご'?",
      "options": [
        "to do housework",
        "desk / table",
        "(someone else's) wife",
        "foreign language"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "foreign language"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'uta'?",
      "options": [
        "うた",
        "おんなのこ",
        "はなします",
        "かいごし"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "うた"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for '(someone else's) younger sister'?",
      "options": [
        "たまご",
        "とうふ",
        "いもうとさん",
        "えいご"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "いもうとさん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kyookasho'?",
      "options": [
        "おかし",
        "スペインご",
        "そうだん（を）します",
        "きょうかしょ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "きょうかしょ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'soup'?",
      "options": [
        "onigiri (omusubi)",
        "sooji (o) shimasu",
        "omiyage",
        "suupu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "suupu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ふゆやすみ'?",
      "options": [
        "fuyu-yasumi",
        "zangyoo (o) shimasu",
        "osoi",
        "hiru-gohan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "fuyu-yasumi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'furniture'?",
      "options": [
        "かぐ",
        "おとこ",
        "おんがくを　ききます",
        "けいたいでんわ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かぐ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'たのしい'?",
      "options": [
        "camera",
        "child",
        "rice ball",
        "fun / enjoyable"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "fun / enjoyable"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'わかもの'?",
      "options": [
        "to use / surf the Internet",
        "seasonal events",
        "Japanese food",
        "youth"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "youth"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'okusan'?",
      "options": [
        "iced (coffee / tea)",
        "example",
        "radio",
        "(someone else's) wife"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(someone else's) wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'かのじょ'?",
      "options": [
        "ani",
        "setsumee (o) shimasu",
        "kanojo",
        "〜ga dekimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kanojo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'isha'?",
      "options": [
        "いしゃ",
        "かぞく",
        "しゅふ",
        "おいのり（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "いしゃ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'マンガ'?",
      "options": [
        "manga / comic strips / comic books",
        "preparation (for the lesson)",
        "(my) wife",
        "breakfast"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "manga / comic strips / comic books"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'meal'?",
      "options": [
        "gaikoku",
        "hanashimasu",
        "shokuji",
        "odori"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shokuji"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kyooshitsu'?",
      "options": [
        "event",
        "classroom",
        "to go home",
        "we"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "classroom"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'おんがくを　ききます'?",
      "options": [
        "ima",
        "beddo",
        "ongaku o kikimasu",
        "kopii (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ongaku o kikimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kippu'?",
      "options": [
        "part-time job",
        "ticket",
        "reservation / booking (to make a reservation)",
        "barbecue"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ticket"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kabuki'?",
      "options": [
        "Kabuki",
        "〜 shop / restaurant",
        "Africa",
        "event"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Kabuki"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to have breakfast / lunch / dinner'?",
      "options": [
        "gohan",
        "naka",
        "asa / hiru / ban-gohan o tabemasu",
        "akushon"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "asa / hiru / ban-gohan o tabemasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'cool'?",
      "options": [
        "すずし い",
        "〜に　とまりま す",
        "おとしより",
        "〜りょうり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "すずし い"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'science fiction'?",
      "options": [
        "エスエフ",
        "おねえさん",
        "スポーツ",
        "ソファ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "エスエフ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'class / school lessons'?",
      "options": [
        "よしゅう",
        "じゅぎょう",
        "やきそば",
        "ギター"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "じゅぎょう"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'しけん'?",
      "options": [
        "soba noodles",
        "dictionary",
        "examination",
        "fireworks display"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "examination"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'pencil'?",
      "options": [
        "enpitsu",
        "raamen",
        "dokusho",
        "omiyage"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "enpitsu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'yoshuu'?",
      "options": [
        "busy",
        "near / close",
        "preparation (for the lesson)",
        "to practice"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "preparation (for the lesson)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'きょうかしょ'?",
      "options": [
        "misuterii",
        "ii",
        "kyookasho",
        "mono"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kyookasho"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'にほんご'?",
      "options": [
        "hotel",
        "Japanese language",
        "to play",
        "to write"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Japanese language"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'じゃがいも'?",
      "options": [
        "jagaimo",
        "odorimasu",
        "Doitsugo",
        "ojiisan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "jagaimo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'arubaito (baito)'?",
      "options": [
        "アルバイト（バイト）",
        "れい",
        "アイロン",
        "ダンス"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "アルバイト（バイト）"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'tomodachi'?",
      "options": [
        "kimono",
        "friend",
        "civil servant",
        "hot / spicy / salty"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "friend"
    },
    
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'show'?",
      "options": [
        "ばつ",
        "ざぶとん",
        "イタリア",
        "ショー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ショー"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'faasuto-fuudo-ten'?",
      "options": [
        "そうじ（を）します",
        "ホラー",
        "ファーストフードてん",
        "とけい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ファーストフードてん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tourist spot / sightseeing area'?",
      "options": [
        "おどります",
        "ピザ",
        "かんこ うち",
        "インドネシア"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かんこ うち"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'okosan'?",
      "options": [
        "boy",
        "〜 shop / restaurant",
        "(someone else's) child",
        "Japanese pop music"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(someone else's) child"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ニュージーランド'?",
      "options": [
        "hon-dana",
        "sonohoka",
        "Nyuujiirando",
        "taihen"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Nyuujiirando"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ろうか'?",
      "options": [
        "rooka",
        "peeji",
        "okosan",
        "tanjoobi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "rooka"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Doitsugo'?",
      "options": [
        "ドイツご",
        "おいのり（を）します",
        "ソファ",
        "アイス"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ドイツご"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'よこ'?",
      "options": [
        "yoko",
        "asa-gohan",
        "purezento",
        "minna"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "yoko"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'gaikoku'?",
      "options": [
        "foreign country",
        "Africa",
        "foreign language",
        "breakfast"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "foreign country"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Russia'?",
      "options": [
        "きょうだい",
        "かのじょ",
        "〜を　たべます",
        "ロシア"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ロシア"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'map'?",
      "options": [
        "chizu",
        "katudoo / ibento",
        "beddo",
        "nihonshu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "chizu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'cool'?",
      "options": [
        "Betonamu",
        "sandoicchi",
        "suzushii",
        "yoku"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "suzushii"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ushiro'?",
      "options": [
        "meat",
        "myself / me",
        "back / behind",
        "big / spacious / large"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "back / behind"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'gaikokugo'?",
      "options": [
        "grandchild",
        "number",
        "hot water",
        "foreign language"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "foreign language"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'shokki'?",
      "options": [
        "とうきょう",
        "おとこのこ",
        "ねます",
        "しょっき"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "しょっき"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'しょくじ（を）します'?",
      "options": [
        "food",
        "to have a meal",
        "he",
        "festival / celebration"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to have a meal"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'long'?",
      "options": [
        "kaidan",
        "katazukemasu",
        "nagai",
        "juudoo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "nagai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'example'?",
      "options": [
        "jukoosha",
        "kyooshi",
        "tomodachi ga kimasu",
        "ree"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ree"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Mt. Fuji'?",
      "options": [
        "ふじさん",
        "え（を　かきます）",
        "つまらない",
        "コーヒー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ふじさん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'yooshitsu'?",
      "options": [
        "もみじがり",
        "アイスクリーム",
        "ようしつ",
        "にく"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ようしつ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'museum'?",
      "options": [
        "ねます",
        "はくぶつかん",
        "せんせい",
        "かんこくご"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "はくぶつかん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'autumn festival'?",
      "options": [
        "いま",
        "れい",
        "あきまつり",
        "カレンダー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "あきまつり"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'bright'?",
      "options": [
        "かなしい",
        "あかるい",
        "テレビを　みます",
        "となり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "あかるい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'いしゃ'?",
      "options": [
        "beef",
        "name",
        "medical doctor",
        "fishing / to go fishing"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "medical doctor"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'chotto'?",
      "options": [
        "airport",
        "name",
        "to watch TV",
        "a little / a few"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "a little / a few"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'concert'?",
      "options": [
        "ミステリー",
        "コンサート",
        "かに",
        "いい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "コンサート"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'slow'?",
      "options": [
        "おそい",
        "いけばな",
        "たまねぎ",
        "しょうせつ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おそい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'そのほか'?",
      "options": [
        "Burajiru",
        "sonohoka",
        "wakamono",
        "kodomo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sonohoka"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'とけい'?",
      "options": [
        "takai",
        "tokee",
        "bataa",
        "shooji"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tokee"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to take care of / look after'?",
      "options": [
        "〜 no sewa o shimasu",
        "yooshitsu",
        "jukoosha",
        "mado"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜 no sewa o shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'さんぽ（を）します'?",
      "options": [
        "to play a game",
        "tableware",
        "to pray",
        "to take a walk"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to take a walk"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'chair'?",
      "options": [
        "たべもの",
        "いす",
        "はやい",
        "びじゅつかん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "いす"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'kitchen'?",
      "options": [
        "ryoori (o) shimasu",
        "ni ikimasu",
        "taiko",
        "daidokoro"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "daidokoro"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'the person next to you'?",
      "options": [
        "Amerika",
        "taiko",
        "tonari no hito",
        "kare"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tonari no hito"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'tetsudaimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "answer",
        "nearby",
        "to help",
        "to get up / to wake up"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to help"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ウイスキー'?",
      "options": [
        "whisky",
        "cereal",
        "greetings",
        "man"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "whisky"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'べんきょう（を）します'?",
      "options": [
        "benkyoo (o) shimasu",
        "Itaria",
        "kukkii",
        "yasumimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "benkyoo (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'table tennis / ping-pong'?",
      "options": [
        "じゅこうしゃ",
        "キャベツ",
        "あめ",
        "たっきゅう／ピンポン"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "たっきゅう／ピンポン"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'taiko'?",
      "options": [
        "せんせい",
        "たいこ",
        "ひるごはん",
        "うしろ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "たいこ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'gurasu'?",
      "options": [
        "he",
        "review",
        "glass",
        "sport"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "glass"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'yasumimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "Mt. Fuji",
        "to rest / take a rest",
        "bed",
        "jam"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to rest / take a rest"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'atatakai'?",
      "options": [
        "あたたか い",
        "わたし",
        "かぞく",
        "〜りょうり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "あたたか い"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'きたない'?",
      "options": [
        "kitanai",
        "fuyu-yasumi",
        "karaoke",
        "obaasan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kitanai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'かつどう・イベント'?",
      "options": [
        "Doitsu",
        "kippu",
        "katudoo / ibento",
        "shufu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "katudoo / ibento"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'hanami'?",
      "options": [
        "company employee",
        "boring / dull",
        "cherry-blossom viewing",
        "dictionary"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "cherry-blossom viewing"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'fantasy fiction'?",
      "options": [
        "kurashikku",
        "natsu-matsuri",
        "byooin",
        "fantajii"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "fantajii"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for '(someone else's) child'?",
      "options": [
        "okosan",
        "〜 ni tomarimasu",
        "otto",
        "intaanetto (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "okosan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'aisatsu'?",
      "options": [
        "adjectives",
        "greetings",
        "to use / surf the Internet",
        "party"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "greetings"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'おとしより'?",
      "options": [
        "yomimasu",
        "ikebana",
        "otoshiyori",
        "chizu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "otoshiyori"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for '〜 ni nite imasu ne'?",
      "options": [
        "いけばな",
        "〜に にて いますね",
        "よく",
        "けいたいでんわ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜に にて いますね"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'niwa'?",
      "options": [
        "greetings",
        "park",
        "South Korea",
        "garden"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "garden"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'hikimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "fun / enjoyable",
        "to play the guitar / piano",
        "department store",
        "song"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to play the guitar / piano"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ともだち'?",
      "options": [
        "tomodachi",
        "mikan",
        "konsaato",
        "otooto"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tomodachi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'onna-no-hito'?",
      "options": [
        "えび",
        "え（を　かきます）",
        "あめ",
        "おんなのひと"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おんなのひと"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'karee'?",
      "options": [
        "すばらしい",
        "じぶん",
        "カレー",
        "コーヒー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "カレー"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'akushon'?",
      "options": [
        "〜に　とまります",
        "こめ",
        "ステーキ",
        "アクション"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "アクション"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'apple'?",
      "options": [
        "ヨーロッパ",
        "ねこ",
        "がいこくじん",
        "りんご"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "りんご"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'we'?",
      "options": [
        "わたしたち",
        "しょくじ（を）します",
        "となりのひと",
        "ドイツご"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "わたしたち"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to go out'?",
      "options": [
        "にほんりょうり",
        "がくせい",
        "イタリア",
        "でかけま す"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "でかけま す"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to play'?",
      "options": [
        "そうじき",
        "ちいさい",
        "かいすいよく",
        "あそびます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "あそびます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'oinori (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "アイロン",
        "おりがみ",
        "おいのり（を）します",
        "べんきょう（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おいのり（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for '(my) son'?",
      "options": [
        "むすこ",
        "けいようし",
        "リビング",
        "かぞく"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "むすこ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'gaikokujin'?",
      "options": [
        "to go out",
        "Africa",
        "to say / to tell",
        "foreigner"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "foreigner"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ゲーム（を）します'?",
      "options": [
        "packed lunch / lunch box",
        "expensive",
        "to play a game",
        "chopsticks"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to play a game"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'window'?",
      "options": [
        "hanabi-taikai",
        "mado",
        "kabe",
        "Mekishiko"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "mado"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'cheese'?",
      "options": [
        "あまり",
        "アクション",
        "やすい",
        "チーズ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "チーズ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'あそびます'?",
      "options": [
        "to play",
        "New Year's visit to a shrine or temple",
        "I can speak (language)",
        "terrible"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to play"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for '(my) grandfather'?",
      "options": [
        "J ポップ",
        "まど",
        "そふ",
        "にわ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "そふ"
    },
    
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to say / to tell'?",
      "options": [
        "okaasan",
        "kippu",
        "shooyu",
        "iimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "iimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'pen'?",
      "options": [
        "Judo",
        "participant",
        "bathroom / bath",
        "pen"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "pen"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for '(someone else's) husband'?",
      "options": [
        "あめ",
        "ピザ",
        "ごしゅじん",
        "べんきょう（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ごしゅじん"
    },
    
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'black tea'?",
      "options": [
        "〜go",
        "Kanada",
        "teeburu",
        "koocha"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "koocha"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to have breakfast / lunch / dinner'?",
      "options": [
        "たべもの",
        "あさ／ひる／ばんごはんを　たべます",
        "〜ご",
        "ぎゅうにく／ビーフ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "あさ／ひる／ばんごはんを　たべます"
    },
    
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kimono'?",
      "options": [
        "おさけ／さけ",
        "けいようし",
        "きもの",
        "かぐ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "きもの"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'danboo'?",
      "options": [
        "しょうせつ",
        "おどり",
        "にほんご",
        "だんぼう"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "だんぼう"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'hotto'?",
      "options": [
        "nearby",
        "hot (coffee / tea)",
        "to ask a question",
        "we"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hot (coffee / tea)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'butaniku / pooku'?",
      "options": [
        "おいしい",
        "ぶたにく／ポーク",
        "あそびます",
        "じゅこうしゃ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ぶたにく／ポーク"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'かなしい'?",
      "options": [
        "ofuro",
        "senpuuki",
        "kisetsu no ibento",
        "kanashii"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kanashii"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'hakubutsukan'?",
      "options": [
        "carrot",
        "sofa",
        "museum",
        "autumn festival"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "museum"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'コンサート'?",
      "options": [
        "konsaato",
        "ryokoo (shimasu)",
        "aisu-kuriimu",
        "jiko-shookai (shimasu)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "konsaato"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for '〜を　のみます'?",
      "options": [
        "to drink 〜",
        "alcove",
        "sliding door",
        "movie / film"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to drink 〜"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ケーキ'?",
      "options": [
        "Thailand",
        "cake",
        "to shave",
        "horror"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "cake"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'small / cramped'?",
      "options": [
        "まど",
        "コーヒー",
        "バスケットボール",
        "せまい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "せまい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for '〜りょうり'?",
      "options": [
        "Nihonjin",
        "kabuki",
        "enpitsu",
        "〜 ryoori"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜 ryoori"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'table tennis / ping-pong'?",
      "options": [
        "chirashi",
        "takai",
        "takkyuu / pinpon",
        "osoi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "takkyuu / pinpon"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for '(my) elder sister'?",
      "options": [
        "あね",
        "そふ",
        "ケーキ",
        "おどり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "あね"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tenpura'?",
      "options": [
        "スープ",
        "てんぷら",
        "おかあさん",
        "りょうり（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "てんぷら"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'rice bowl'?",
      "options": [
        "アジア",
        "スポーツ",
        "ちゃわん",
        "ラーメン"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ちゃわん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'うちに　かえります'?",
      "options": [
        "uchi ni kaerimasu",
        "sakkaa",
        "jukoosha",
        "amai"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "uchi ni kaerimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ゴールデンウィーク'?",
      "options": [
        "kikimasu",
        "kankoochi",
        "gooruden-uiiku",
        "〜ga dekimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "gooruden-uiiku"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'おとうさん'?",
      "options": [
        "expensive",
        "(someone else's) father",
        "a lot",
        "on / above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(someone else's) father"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'Mareeshia'?",
      "options": [
        "Malaysia",
        "page",
        "Canada",
        "(someone else's) elder sister"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Malaysia"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'nagai'?",
      "options": [
        "たたみ",
        "〜の　せわをします",
        "なが い",
        "しょっき"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "なが い"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'furaido-poteto'?",
      "options": [
        "おもしろい",
        "わたしたち",
        "まご",
        "フライドポテト"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "フライドポテト"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'のり'?",
      "options": [
        "reezooko",
        "chiisai",
        "Arabiago",
        "nori"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "nori"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'chikaku'?",
      "options": [
        "おてら",
        "ちか く／ち かく",
        "ふすま",
        "あさごはん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ちか く／ち かく"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'tsumetai'?",
      "options": [
        "a lot",
        "cold",
        "song",
        "bookshelf"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "cold"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'おとこ'?",
      "options": [
        "otoko",
        "ureshii",
        "remon",
        "supagethi (pasuta)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "otoko"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'airport'?",
      "options": [
        "くうこう",
        "うどん",
        "アジア",
        "となり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "くうこう"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'チーズバーガー'?",
      "options": [
        "e (o kakimasu)",
        "kyoodai",
        "jisho",
        "chiizu-baagaa"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "chiizu-baagaa"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'きもの'?",
      "options": [
        "kazoku",
        "oinori (o) shimasu",
        "kimono",
        "supootsu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kimono"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'dictionary'?",
      "options": [
        "supagethi (pasuta)",
        "kankoochi",
        "hako",
        "jisho"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "jisho"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'chicken'?",
      "options": [
        "hottodoggu",
        "Mekishiko",
        "toriniku / chikin",
        "gaikokugo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "toriniku / chikin"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'seaweed'?",
      "options": [
        "のり",
        "おかし",
        "した",
        "ポップス"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "のり"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tomodachi ni aimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "ともだちに　あいます",
        "グラス",
        "コーヒー",
        "インドネシア"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ともだちに　あいます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'teacher / instructor'?",
      "options": [
        "kao o araimasu",
        "sensee",
        "hottodoggu",
        "chichi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sensee"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'bed'?",
      "options": [
        "おとうとさん",
        "どくしょ",
        "ベッド",
        "こめ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ベッド"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'かいしゃ'?",
      "options": [
        "kaisha",
        "nimotsu",
        "depaato",
        "watashi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kaisha"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'タイ'?",
      "options": [
        "Thailand",
        "cereal",
        "U.S.A. / America",
        "sweet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Thailand"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'わしつ'?",
      "options": [
        "Japanese-style room",
        "friend",
        "hot / spicy / salty",
        "Please call me \"〜\""
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Japanese-style room"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ワイン'?",
      "options": [
        "〜 o moraimasu",
        "wain",
        "onna-no-ko",
        "yamanobori (o shimasu)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "wain"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'sliding screen'?",
      "options": [
        "shooji",
        "haha",
        "shooyu",
        "sandoicchi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shooji"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'otooto'?",
      "options": [
        "to do exercise",
        "woman / female",
        "menu",
        "(my) younger brother"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(my) younger brother"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ナイフ'?",
      "options": [
        "knife",
        "to give",
        "book",
        "dictionary"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "knife"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'literature'?",
      "options": [
        "きらい（な）",
        "ハンガリー",
        "ぶんがく",
        "ふじさん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ぶんがく"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'fantasy fiction'?",
      "options": [
        "ファンタジー",
        "〜と よんでください",
        "しょうじ",
        "ホワイトボード"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ファンタジー"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'レストラン'?",
      "options": [
        "garden",
        "sometimes",
        "alcoholic drinks / Japanese sake",
        "restaurant"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "restaurant"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'intaanetto (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "インターネット（を）します",
        "ざっし",
        "しゅみ",
        "チェック（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "インターネット（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to do housework'?",
      "options": [
        "かじ（を）します",
        "くだもの",
        "キャベツ",
        "ながい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かじ（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'class / lesson'?",
      "options": [
        "asobimasu",
        "kurasu",
        "supuun",
        "ibento"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kurasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'snow festival'?",
      "options": [
        "Fujisan",
        "hima",
        "yuki-matsuri",
        "kotae"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "yuki-matsuri"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'foreign language'?",
      "options": [
        "がいこくご",
        "えび",
        "じこしょうかい（します）",
        "たたみ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "がいこくご"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'picture'?",
      "options": [
        "え",
        "スーツケース",
        "ちいさい",
        "どくしょ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "え"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'にほん／にっぽん'?",
      "options": [
        "a lot",
        "Japan",
        "company employee",
        "poster"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Japan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'ima'?",
      "options": [
        "シャワーを　あびます",
        "ひと",
        "かんごし",
        "いま"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "いま"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'anime / animated cartoons'?",
      "options": [
        "アニメ",
        "きょうしつ",
        "まずい",
        "メニュー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "アニメ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'asa / hiru / ban-gohan o tabemasu'?",
      "options": [
        "sugar",
        "(my) wife",
        "to have breakfast / lunch / dinner",
        "Western-style room"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to have breakfast / lunch / dinner"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'staircase'?",
      "options": [
        "kaidan",
        "Nihonjin",
        "konsaato",
        "jogingu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kaidan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ヨガ（を）します'?",
      "options": [
        "people from … (nationality)",
        "to do yoga",
        "window",
        "easy"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to do yoga"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'gurasu'?",
      "options": [
        "おくさん",
        "むずかしい",
        "グラス",
        "あね"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "グラス"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'natsu-yasumi'?",
      "options": [
        "summer holidays",
        "to wash clothes",
        "(someone else's) elder sister",
        "elderly person"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "summer holidays"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'setsumee (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "to work / do one's job",
        "to explain",
        "wasabi (Japanese horseradish)",
        "fork"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to explain"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'shufu'?",
      "options": [
        "ギター",
        "なっとう",
        "そうだん（を）します",
        "しゅふ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "しゅふ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tsumetai'?",
      "options": [
        "まずい",
        "おすし／すし",
        "りょうしん",
        "つめたい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "つめたい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'bread'?",
      "options": [
        "nemasu",
        "Amerika",
        "pan",
        "tabemono"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "pan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'soy sauce'?",
      "options": [
        "shooyu",
        "ningyoo",
        "shokuji (o) shimasu",
        "wasabi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shooyu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'アイロン'?",
      "options": [
        "engineer",
        "miso soup",
        "light",
        "iron"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "iron"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ロシア'?",
      "options": [
        "big / large",
        "Tokyo",
        "Russia",
        "(not) many / (not) much"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Russia"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'びじゅつかん'?",
      "options": [
        "picture (to draw a picture)",
        "watermelon",
        "grandchild",
        "art museum"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "art museum"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'リビング'?",
      "options": [
        "bed",
        "living room",
        "bathroom / bath",
        "fried noodles"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "living room"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'にんぎょう'?",
      "options": [
        "rice ball",
        "(my) husband",
        "Hungary",
        "doll"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "doll"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'がっこう'?",
      "options": [
        "gakkoo",
        "Furansu",
        "Nihon / Nippon",
        "jibun"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "gakkoo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'denwa'?",
      "options": [
        "Chinese language",
        "telephone",
        "to check",
        "guitar"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "telephone"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'sanpo (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "〜に　とまります",
        "たたみ",
        "さんぽ（を）します",
        "ジャズ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "さんぽ（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'こわい'?",
      "options": [
        "shawaa o abimasu",
        "kippu",
        "kisetsu no ibento",
        "kowai"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kowai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'television'?",
      "options": [
        "ichigo",
        "kabe",
        "terebi",
        "Chuugoku"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "terebi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'fireworks'?",
      "options": [
        "わたしたち",
        "はなび",
        "かべ",
        "やさい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "はなび"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'チョコレート'?",
      "options": [
        "paathii",
        "kimono",
        "shooyu",
        "chokoreeto"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "chokoreeto"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'imootosan'?",
      "options": [
        "mystery",
        "(someone else's) younger sister",
        "to pray",
        "hobby / interest"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(someone else's) younger sister"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'jagaimo'?",
      "options": [
        "potato",
        "water",
        "telephone",
        "Egypt"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "potato"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'airon'?",
      "options": [
        "おとうさん",
        "〜と よんでください",
        "しょっき",
        "アイロン"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "アイロン"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'menyuu'?",
      "options": [
        "baggage / luggage",
        "winter holidays",
        "action",
        "menu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "menu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'hospital'?",
      "options": [
        "バナナ",
        "とうきょう",
        "アルバイト／バイト（を）します",
        "びょういん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "びょういん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to do exercise'?",
      "options": [
        "しょうせつ",
        "げんかん",
        "うんどう（を）します",
        "えいご"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "うんどう（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'あまい'?",
      "options": [
        "tana",
        "amai",
        "yoyaku (o shimasu)",
        "karendaa"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "amai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ちかく'?",
      "options": [
        "wine",
        "myself / me",
        "shelf",
        "near / close"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "near / close"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'Supein'?",
      "options": [
        "Spain",
        "evening meal",
        "cooking / dish",
        "food"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Spain"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'せんたく（を）します'?",
      "options": [
        "yooshitsu",
        "sentaku (o) shimasu",
        "Arabiago",
        "teeburu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sentaku (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'かのじょ'?",
      "options": [
        "housewife / homemaker",
        "expensive",
        "baseball",
        "she"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "she"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'フライドポテト'?",
      "options": [
        "fried potatoes / french fries / chips",
        "comedy",
        "desk",
        "staircase"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "fried potatoes / french fries / chips"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to have a meal'?",
      "options": [
        "おしょうがつ／しょうがつ",
        "しょくじ（を）します",
        "まる",
        "ともだちが　きます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "しょくじ（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'bedroom'?",
      "options": [
        "ねます",
        "あたたかい",
        "アイス",
        "ベッドルーム"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ベッドルーム"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'yooshitsu'?",
      "options": [
        "pizza",
        "cake",
        "number",
        "Western-style room"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Western-style room"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tamago'?",
      "options": [
        "メニュー",
        "ききます",
        "たまご",
        "トイレ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "たまご"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'I'?",
      "options": [
        "isu",
        "sara",
        "watashi",
        "geemu (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "watashi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'senpuuki'?",
      "options": [
        "ワイン",
        "せんぷうき",
        "かじ（を）します",
        "みず"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "せんぷうき"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'notebook'?",
      "options": [
        "さむい",
        "さかな",
        "おけしょう（を）します",
        "ノート"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ノート"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'e'?",
      "options": [
        "toilet",
        "picture",
        "(someone else's) child",
        "to go out"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "picture"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'やきゅう'?",
      "options": [
        "nearby",
        "baseball",
        "〜 shop / restaurant",
        "jogging"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "baseball"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'もみじがり'?",
      "options": [
        "autumn-leaf viewing",
        "sofa",
        "(my) mother",
        "baby"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "autumn-leaf viewing"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'イベント'?",
      "options": [
        "chirashi",
        "jisho",
        "ibento",
        "tatami"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ibento"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for '〜 language'?",
      "options": [
        "うちに　かえります",
        "どくしょ",
        "〜を　のみます",
        "〜ご"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜ご"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'pen'?",
      "options": [
        "あつい",
        "うえ",
        "ペン",
        "おふろに　はいります"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ペン"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'intaanetto (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "park",
        "Europe",
        "to use / surf the Internet",
        "(my) younger sister"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to use / surf the Internet"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'eega'?",
      "options": [
        "glass",
        "movie / film",
        "to play",
        "to dance"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "movie / film"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to watch TV'?",
      "options": [
        "taiko",
        "〜go",
        "Chuugokugo",
        "terebi o mimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "terebi o mimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'いす'?",
      "options": [
        "isu",
        "〜 o moraimasu",
        "bungaku",
        "remon"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "isu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'りょこう'?",
      "options": [
        "nice / good",
        "textbook",
        "to write",
        "travel / trip"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "travel / trip"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'tsukue'?",
      "options": [
        "desk / table",
        "company / firm",
        "lettuce",
        "yogurt"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "desk / table"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'family'?",
      "options": [
        "かぞく",
        "コンテスト",
        "みます",
        "パンフレット"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かぞく"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'すこし'?",
      "options": [
        "すこ し",
        "じむしつ",
        "さんぽ（を）します",
        "おかし"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "すこ し"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for '(someone else's) grandfather'?",
      "options": [
        "しゃしん",
        "おじいさん",
        "あきまつり",
        "チケット"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おじいさん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'とうふ'?",
      "options": [
        "to give",
        "child",
        "bean curd / tofu",
        "page"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "bean curd / tofu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'クッキー'?",
      "options": [
        "cookie",
        "park",
        "sandwich",
        "U.K."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "cookie"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tsukue'?",
      "options": [
        "けいたいでんわ",
        "ぶどうがり",
        "おみやげ",
        "つくえ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "つくえ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'baseball'?",
      "options": [
        "カラオケ",
        "やきゅう",
        "イベント",
        "カップ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "やきゅう"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tidy / clean'?",
      "options": [
        "やすみます",
        "きれい（な）",
        "かぐ",
        "こうむいん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "きれい（な）"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'rajio'?",
      "options": [
        "ふゆやすみ",
        "ラジオ",
        "おすし／すし",
        "〜りょうり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ラジオ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'chokoreeto'?",
      "options": [
        "Bonsai",
        "fried noodles",
        "swimming in the sea",
        "chocolate"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "chocolate"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'おすし／すし'?",
      "options": [
        "doll",
        "sushi",
        "to dance",
        "busy"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sushi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'スペインご'?",
      "options": [
        "tsukaremasu",
        "retasu",
        "Supeingo",
        "〜 to oshaberi (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Supeingo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'company employee'?",
      "options": [
        "kaishain",
        "kao o araimasu",
        "Nihongo",
        "kingyo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kaishain"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'skating'?",
      "options": [
        "スケート",
        "あたらしい",
        "たかい",
        "バースデー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "スケート"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'shukudai'?",
      "options": [
        "がっこう",
        "すいか",
        "こうちゃ",
        "しゅくだい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "しゅくだい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'front'?",
      "options": [
        "びじゅつかん",
        "れい",
        "おばあさん",
        "ま え"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ま え"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'gakkoo'?",
      "options": [
        "cucumber",
        "school",
        "bedroom",
        "office room"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "school"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'こども'?",
      "options": [
        "ofuro",
        "ryokoo (shimasu)",
        "oniisan",
        "kodomo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kodomo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Firipin'?",
      "options": [
        "フィリピン",
        "おとこのこ",
        "しょうゆ",
        "すばらしい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "フィリピン"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'toofu'?",
      "options": [
        "〜の　せわをします",
        "とうふ",
        "おいのり（を）します",
        "あなた"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "とうふ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'everyone'?",
      "options": [
        "かんごし",
        "みなさん",
        "すき（な）",
        "にんじん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "みなさん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'paatotaimu (paato)'?",
      "options": [
        "がいこく",
        "そば",
        "パートタイム（パート）",
        "ページ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "パートタイム（パート）"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'かいすいよく'?",
      "options": [
        "ni ikimasu",
        "namae",
        "asa / hiru / ban-gohan o tabemasu",
        "kaisuiyoku"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kaisuiyoku"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'byooin'?",
      "options": [
        "Asia",
        "to give",
        "garden",
        "hospital"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hospital"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'おすし／すし'?",
      "options": [
        "sushi",
        "Spanish language",
        "bookshelf",
        "to do yoga"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sushi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'horaa'?",
      "options": [
        "horror",
        "dish / plate",
        "hotel / Japanese inn",
        "piano"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "horror"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'satoo'?",
      "options": [
        "old",
        "lettuce",
        "kimono",
        "sugar"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sugar"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tonari'?",
      "options": [
        "ふくを　きます",
        "ドア",
        "しゅみ",
        "となり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "となり"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kaji (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "to do housework",
        "difficult",
        "(my) elder sister",
        "potato"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to do housework"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'supuun'?",
      "options": [
        "dark",
        "park",
        "concert",
        "spoon"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "spoon"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ハンバーガー'?",
      "options": [
        "hoteru",
        "jamu",
        "hanbaagaa",
        "otto"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hanbaagaa"
    },
    
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Germany'?",
      "options": [
        "J ポップ",
        "オーストラリア",
        "しゃしん（を　とります）",
        "ドイツ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ドイツ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'Kankoku'?",
      "options": [
        "South Korea",
        "a little / a few",
        "art museum",
        "rice"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "South Korea"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Igirisu'?",
      "options": [
        "カップ",
        "（ひとが）おおい",
        "イギリス",
        "チーズバーガー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "イギリス"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'jam'?",
      "options": [
        "やさい",
        "スケート",
        "エアコン",
        "ジャム"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ジャム"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'てんぷら'?",
      "options": [
        "faasuto-fuudo-ten",
        "tenpura",
        "sensee",
        "suiee"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tenpura"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'gitaa'?",
      "options": [
        "nearby",
        "guitar",
        "office room",
        "cheese burger"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "guitar"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'カップ'?",
      "options": [
        "(someone else's) father",
        "cup",
        "foreign country",
        "student studying abroad / international student"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "cup"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'たまご'?",
      "options": [
        "shufu",
        "tamago",
        "hiroi",
        "kuukoo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tamago"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'アニメ'?",
      "options": [
        "hon-dana",
        "shiriaru",
        "anime",
        "aisu-kuriimu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "anime"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'futon'?",
      "options": [
        "to consult / to discuss",
        "to make a phone call",
        "bed",
        "bedding"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "bedding"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'gakusee'?",
      "options": [
        "suitcase",
        "soup",
        "student",
        "(someone else's) wife"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "student"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'baby'?",
      "options": [
        "omoshiroi",
        "akachan",
        "musume",
        "yoga (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "akachan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'medical doctor'?",
      "options": [
        "Eego",
        "isha",
        "yamanobori (o shimasu)",
        "mondai"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "isha"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'menu'?",
      "options": [
        "きんぎょ",
        "メニュー",
        "つま",
        "あめ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "メニュー"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'たんじょうび'?",
      "options": [
        "yoshuu",
        "mono",
        "tanjoobi",
        "butaniku / pooku"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tanjoobi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'びじゅつかん'?",
      "options": [
        "bijutsukan",
        "karee",
        "ocha",
        "nooka"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "bijutsukan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kaishain'?",
      "options": [
        "かいしゃいん",
        "あきまつり",
        "テーブル",
        "もみじがり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かいしゃいん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'unappetizing'?",
      "options": [
        "mazui",
        "hottodoggu",
        "airon",
        "kakimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "mazui"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to look'?",
      "options": [
        "かべ",
        "わしつ",
        "ウイスキー",
        "みます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "みます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'interesting'?",
      "options": [
        "せまい",
        "すずしい",
        "さしみ",
        "おもしろい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おもしろい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to make a phone call'?",
      "options": [
        "ざんぎょう（を）します",
        "かんこくご",
        "でんわ（を）します／かけます",
        "コップ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "でんわ（を）します／かけます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for '〜に にて いますね'?",
      "options": [
        "student",
        "Kabuki",
        "photograph (to take a photo)",
        "to look like 〜"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to look like 〜"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'やまのぼり（を　します）'?",
      "options": [
        "yamanobori (o shimasu)",
        "raamen",
        "ha o migakimasu",
        "okaasan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "yamanobori (o shimasu)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'カード'?",
      "options": [
        "table tennis / ping-pong",
        "basketball",
        "card",
        "curtain"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "card"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'tamanegi'?",
      "options": [
        "crab",
        "radio",
        "onion",
        "to read a newspaper"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "onion"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ともだち'?",
      "options": [
        "jugyoo",
        "yasai",
        "tomodachi",
        "tsukue"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tomodachi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Hangarii'?",
      "options": [
        "うれしい",
        "こども",
        "ハンガリー",
        "ペン"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ハンガリー"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ふくを　きます'?",
      "options": [
        "kome",
        "fuku o kimasu",
        "futon",
        "goshujin"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "fuku o kimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to get tired'?",
      "options": [
        "つかれます",
        "ゲーム（を）します",
        "スプーン",
        "ふとん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "つかれます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'difficult'?",
      "options": [
        "しょうゆ",
        "さかな",
        "おこさん",
        "むずかしい／むずかし い"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "むずかしい／むずかし い"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kaaten'?",
      "options": [
        "はなみ",
        "けいようし",
        "にほんりょうり",
        "カーテン"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "カーテン"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'seasonal events'?",
      "options": [
        "otoko",
        "onigiri (omusubi)",
        "Burajiru",
        "kisetsu no ibento"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kisetsu no ibento"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'card'?",
      "options": [
        "shio",
        "juudoo",
        "kaado",
        "ribingu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kaado"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'むずかしい'?",
      "options": [
        "ren'ai",
        "ree",
        "muzukashii",
        "wasabi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "muzukashii"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'みそしる'?",
      "options": [
        "usagi",
        "kyooshitsu",
        "misoshiru",
        "ebi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "misoshiru"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to watch TV'?",
      "options": [
        "テレビを　みます",
        "チーズバーガー",
        "にほんご",
        "かんこくご"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "テレビを　みます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'すばらしい'?",
      "options": [
        "すばらし い",
        "うれしい",
        "れいぞうこ",
        "イベント"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "すばらし い"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'mago'?",
      "options": [
        "おちゃ／ちゃ",
        "せんたくき",
        "ねます",
        "まご"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "まご"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'じむしつ'?",
      "options": [
        "Russia",
        "office room",
        "rabbit",
        "easy"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "office room"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'さら'?",
      "options": [
        "dish / plate",
        "Japanese food",
        "wine",
        "(someone else's) father"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "dish / plate"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ねます'?",
      "options": [
        "nemasu",
        "menyuu",
        "tabako o suimasu",
        "mondai"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "nemasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'front'?",
      "options": [
        "kanojo",
        "subarashii",
        "mae",
        "kagu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "mae"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'orange juice'?",
      "options": [
        "オレンジジュース",
        "なつまつり",
        "とうきょう",
        "やすみます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "オレンジジュース"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'boy'?",
      "options": [
        "バター",
        "となり",
        "〜を　たべます",
        "おとこのこ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おとこのこ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'はなびたいかい'?",
      "options": [
        "table tennis / ping-pong",
        "Vietnam",
        "to put on makeup",
        "fireworks display"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "fireworks display"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'summer festival'?",
      "options": [
        "つかれま す",
        "ごはん／ライス",
        "なつま つり",
        "おすし／すし"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "なつま つり"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'shoo'?",
      "options": [
        "things (found at home)",
        "show",
        "New Year's holiday",
        "beer"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "show"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'せんぷうき'?",
      "options": [
        "suiee",
        "denshi-renji",
        "senpuuki",
        "akushon"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "senpuuki"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'sofa'?",
      "options": [
        "かんごし",
        "ソファ",
        "みそしる",
        "ひげを　そります"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ソファ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ryokoo (shimasu)'?",
      "options": [
        "trip / to go on a trip",
        "nurse",
        "company employee",
        "to take care of / look after"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "trip / to go on a trip"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'baasudee'?",
      "options": [
        "birthday",
        "review",
        "calendar",
        "next to"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "birthday"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'うどん'?",
      "options": [
        "posutaa",
        "juusu",
        "sooji (o) shimasu",
        "udon"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "udon"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'chair'?",
      "options": [
        "とけい",
        "つかれます",
        "いす",
        "あそびます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "いす"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'しつもん（を）します'?",
      "options": [
        "goshujin",
        "paathii",
        "e (o kakimasu)",
        "shitsumon (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shitsumon (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'chiisai'?",
      "options": [
        "バスケットボール",
        "ちいさい",
        "エアコン",
        "そのほか"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ちいさい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'おかし'?",
      "options": [
        "amari",
        "rooka",
        "sakana",
        "okashi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "okashi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ベッドルーム'?",
      "options": [
        "yoku",
        "beddo-ruumu",
        "budoogari",
        "beranda"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "beddo-ruumu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'うれしい'?",
      "options": [
        "happy / glad / delighted",
        "Australia",
        "orange juice",
        "to watch TV"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "happy / glad / delighted"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kao o araimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "かおを　あらいます",
        "クッキー",
        "こわい",
        "はなみ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かおを　あらいます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'Canada'?",
      "options": [
        "Kanada",
        "goshujin",
        "Supeingo",
        "Afurika"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Kanada"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'E-meeru (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "pizza",
        "〜 language",
        "to write / send an e-mail",
        "(my) grandmother"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to write / send an e-mail"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'watashi'?",
      "options": [
        "electrical appliance",
        "myself / me",
        "raw fish dish",
        "bedroom"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "myself / me"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'restaurant'?",
      "options": [
        "ほん",
        "クラス",
        "レストラン",
        "イタリア"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "レストラン"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'happy / glad / delighted'?",
      "options": [
        "hakubutsukan",
        "zenzen",
        "ureshii",
        "jiko-shookai (shimasu)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ureshii"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'はいく'?",
      "options": [
        "haiku",
        "nikki o kakimasu",
        "nattoo",
        "sumoo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "haiku"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'sakkaa'?",
      "options": [
        "cold",
        "camera",
        "soccer / football",
        "Europe"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "soccer / football"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'New Year's visit to a shrine or temple'?",
      "options": [
        "ノート",
        "はつもうで",
        "ねます",
        "フランス"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "はつもうで"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'hon'?",
      "options": [
        "book",
        "slippers",
        "company employee",
        "housewife / homemaker"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "book"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'いそがしい'?",
      "options": [
        "uchi ni kaerimasu",
        "ryokoo",
        "isogashii",
        "posutaa"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "isogashii"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'hashi'?",
      "options": [
        "free / not occupied",
        "chopsticks",
        "review",
        "expensive"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "chopsticks"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'えいご'?",
      "options": [
        "English language",
        "Mt. Fuji",
        "office room",
        "man / male"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "English language"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'みんな'?",
      "options": [
        "momijigari",
        "asa / hiru / ban-gohan o tabemasu",
        "minna",
        "watashitachi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "minna"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'tennis'?",
      "options": [
        "amai",
        "howaito-boodo",
        "tenisu",
        "menyuu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tenisu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ふくしゅう'?",
      "options": [
        "(my) mother",
        "sleepy",
        "cheese",
        "review"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "review"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'enpitsu'?",
      "options": [
        "えんぴつ",
        "はなみ",
        "つまらない",
        "となり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "えんぴつ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ビール'?",
      "options": [
        "hoteru",
        "namae",
        "biiru",
        "danboo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "biiru"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'watermelon'?",
      "options": [
        "toire",
        "suika",
        "amari",
        "hanashimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "suika"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ドイツご'?",
      "options": [
        "packed lunch / lunch box",
        "menu",
        "question / problem",
        "German language"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "German language"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'steak'?",
      "options": [
        "かのじょ",
        "ろうか",
        "マンガ",
        "ステーキ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ステーキ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'かに'?",
      "options": [
        "crab",
        "student",
        "coffee",
        "heater"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "crab"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'たべもの'?",
      "options": [
        "video game / computer game",
        "cake",
        "food",
        "rabbit"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "food"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'itsumo'?",
      "options": [
        "to go out",
        "hamburger",
        "cherry-blossom viewing",
        "always"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "always"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'きれい（な）'?",
      "options": [
        "easy",
        "dog",
        "tidy / clean",
        "vegetable"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tidy / clean"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'おしょうがつ／しょうがつ'?",
      "options": [
        "oshoogatsu",
        "kurasu",
        "nemasu",
        "tabemono"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "oshoogatsu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'foreign language'?",
      "options": [
        "バーベキュー",
        "よこ",
        "〜に　いきます",
        "がいこくご ／〜ご"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "がいこくご ／〜ご"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'hamburger'?",
      "options": [
        "りょこう",
        "ポップス",
        "ハンバーガー",
        "ほん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ハンバーガー"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'かれ'?",
      "options": [
        "eega",
        "kare",
        "chiizu",
        "osoi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kare"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'review'?",
      "options": [
        "みなさん",
        "ふくしゅう",
        "にく",
        "まご"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ふくしゅう"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'e (o kakimasu)'?",
      "options": [
        "picture (to draw a picture)",
        "Western-style room",
        "classroom",
        "swimming"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "picture (to draw a picture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'book'?",
      "options": [
        "imooto",
        "horaa",
        "hon",
        "akushon"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hon"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'cheese burger'?",
      "options": [
        "ジャム",
        "きょうし",
        "チーズバーガー",
        "マンガ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "チーズバーガー"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'semai'?",
      "options": [
        "to wash clothes",
        "Germany",
        "small / cramped",
        "breakfast"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "small / cramped"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'soto'?",
      "options": [
        "そ と",
        "がっこう",
        "せんたく（を）します",
        "しょくじ（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "そ と"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Italy'?",
      "options": [
        "イタリア",
        "えいが",
        "アルバイト（バイト）",
        "コーヒー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "イタリア"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for '〜ga dekimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "English language",
        "big / spacious / large",
        "I can speak (language)",
        "wall"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "I can speak (language)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ichigo'?",
      "options": [
        "piano",
        "strawberry",
        "page",
        "seasonal events"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "strawberry"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'suki'?",
      "options": [
        "たのしい",
        "さしみ",
        "すき（な）",
        "ともだちが　きます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "すき（な）"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'えんぴつ'?",
      "options": [
        "rock music",
        "table tennis / ping-pong",
        "pencil",
        "to play"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "pencil"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'がっこう'?",
      "options": [
        "ryokan",
        "gurasu",
        "gakkoo",
        "yooshitsu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "gakkoo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'tesuto'?",
      "options": [
        "jogging",
        "(not) often",
        "test",
        "autumn festival"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "test"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'odorimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "to explain",
        "dark",
        "soy sauce",
        "to dance"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to dance"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to say / to tell'?",
      "options": [
        "がいこくご",
        "いいます",
        "メニュー",
        "ふくを　ぬぎます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "いいます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'jazu'?",
      "options": [
        "あなた",
        "インターネット（を）します",
        "ジャズ",
        "テスト"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ジャズ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'otona'?",
      "options": [
        "おとな",
        "カード",
        "こめ",
        "もんだい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おとな"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kirai'?",
      "options": [
        "ぶたにく／ポーク",
        "やまのぼり（を　します）",
        "きらい（な）",
        "しゃしん（を　とります）"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "きらい（な）"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kaisuiyoku'?",
      "options": [
        "lunch",
        "sport",
        "rabbit",
        "swimming in the sea"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "swimming in the sea"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'okashi'?",
      "options": [
        "sweets / confectionery",
        "to help",
        "Asia",
        "contest"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sweets / confectionery"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'photograph (to take a photo)'?",
      "options": [
        "ざんぎょう（を）します",
        "おゆ／ゆ",
        "しゃしん（を　とります）",
        "きっぷ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "しゃしん（を　とります）"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'toilet'?",
      "options": [
        "yoko",
        "toire",
        "ichigo",
        "hige o sorimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "toire"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'participant'?",
      "options": [
        "おねえさん",
        "そのほか",
        "じゅこうしゃ",
        "ホワイトボード"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "じゅこうしゃ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'つまらない'?",
      "options": [
        "basketball",
        "whiteboard",
        "fun / enjoyable",
        "boring / dull"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "boring / dull"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'J-poppu'?",
      "options": [
        "J ポップ",
        "にわ",
        "うたいます",
        "べんとう"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "J ポップ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'とこのま'?",
      "options": [
        "grapes",
        "the person next to you",
        "alcove",
        "foreign language"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "alcove"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'りょうしん'?",
      "options": [
        "〜jin",
        "tsumaranai",
        "misuterii",
        "ryooshin"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ryooshin"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'quick'?",
      "options": [
        "hayai",
        "tanjoobi",
        "chotto",
        "matsuri"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hayai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'free / not occupied'?",
      "options": [
        "カレ ンダー",
        "そうだん（を）します",
        "ひま",
        "はやい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ひま"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'rabbit'?",
      "options": [
        "〜や（さん）",
        "ほんだな",
        "うさぎ",
        "そのほか"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "うさぎ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'sumoo'?",
      "options": [
        "garden",
        "India",
        "sad",
        "Sumo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Sumo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for '〜 ni tomarimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "ハンバーガー",
        "〜に　とまります",
        "コメディ",
        "ロシア"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜に　とまります"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tea / Japanese tea'?",
      "options": [
        "あまい",
        "とこのま",
        "おちゃ／ちゃ",
        "かんごし"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おちゃ／ちゃ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'vegetable'?",
      "options": [
        "フランス",
        "きんぎょ",
        "〜や（さん）",
        "やさい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "やさい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'wine'?",
      "options": [
        "おっと",
        "コメディ",
        "ビザ",
        "ワイン"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ワイン"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'banana'?",
      "options": [
        "つま",
        "かおを　あらいます",
        "バナナ",
        "ピザ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "バナナ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'a friend comes to visit'?",
      "options": [
        "うどん",
        "しお",
        "よやく （を します）",
        "ともだちが　きます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ともだちが　きます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'sleepy'?",
      "options": [
        "ねむい",
        "ケーキ",
        "〜と よんでください",
        "のうか"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ねむい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'はなします'?",
      "options": [
        "yooshitsu",
        "hanashimasu",
        "ryoo",
        "soojiki"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hanashimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'おきます'?",
      "options": [
        "pop music",
        "boring / dull",
        "calendar",
        "to get up / to wake up"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to get up / to wake up"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for '〜を　もらいます'?",
      "options": [
        "to receive",
        "apple",
        "basketball",
        "scary / frightening"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to receive"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'New Year's holiday'?",
      "options": [
        "おしょうがつ／しょうがつ",
        "おいしい",
        "トマト",
        "りょうしん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おしょうがつ／しょうがつ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'しけん'?",
      "options": [
        "shooyu",
        "zasshi",
        "shiken",
        "ningyoo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shiken"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'hako'?",
      "options": [
        "alcoholic drinks / Japanese sake",
        "meal",
        "(someone else's) wife",
        "box"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "box"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'カレンダー'?",
      "options": [
        "Malaysia",
        "seaweed",
        "calendar",
        "like"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "calendar"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'chotto'?",
      "options": [
        "インド",
        "おじいさん",
        "ちょっと",
        "よこ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ちょっと"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'となり'?",
      "options": [
        "tonari",
        "kagu",
        "misoshiru",
        "chichi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tonari"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'furui'?",
      "options": [
        "ふるい",
        "テスト",
        "おんがくを　ききます",
        "トイレ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ふるい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'レタス'?",
      "options": [
        "jugyoo",
        "paatotaimu (paato)",
        "〜 o nomimasu",
        "retasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "retasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'department store'?",
      "options": [
        "tori",
        "depaato",
        "odori",
        "shigoto (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "depaato"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'living room'?",
      "options": [
        "tonari no hito",
        "ribingu",
        "tsukue",
        "gohan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ribingu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'つめたい'?",
      "options": [
        "watashi",
        "Indo",
        "bangoo",
        "tsumetai"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tsumetai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'youth'?",
      "options": [
        "おとしより",
        "わかもの",
        "むすこ",
        "にんぎょう"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "わかもの"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'new'?",
      "options": [
        "atarashii",
        "tenpura",
        "yukkuri shimasu",
        "yooshitsu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "atarashii"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for '(someone else's) elder brother'?",
      "options": [
        "pasupooto",
        "oniisan",
        "omoshiroi",
        "kurai"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "oniisan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'パートタイム（パート）'?",
      "options": [
        "pasupooto",
        "〜 no sewa o shimasu",
        "paatotaimu (paato)",
        "gakusee"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "paatotaimu (paato)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for '〜ga dekimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "しごと（を）します",
        "〜が　できます",
        "エアコン",
        "つま"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜が　できます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'ue'?",
      "options": [
        "かなしい",
        "しごと（を）します",
        "いしゃ",
        "うえ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "うえ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kippu'?",
      "options": [
        "かいすいよく",
        "びじゅつかん",
        "やさい",
        "きっぷ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "きっぷ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'new'?",
      "options": [
        "よこ",
        "あたらしい",
        "れい",
        "にんぎょう"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "あたらしい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'civil servant'?",
      "options": [
        "Arabiago",
        "e",
        "shumi",
        "koomuin"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "koomuin"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Bonsai'?",
      "options": [
        "ぼんさい",
        "おおきい",
        "ホテル",
        "コーヒー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ぼんさい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'Betonamu'?",
      "options": [
        "beer",
        "hot water",
        "Vietnam",
        "refrigerator"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Vietnam"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'test'?",
      "options": [
        "tana",
        "tesuto",
        "shokuji (o) shimasu",
        "taihen"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tesuto"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'gooruden-uiiku'?",
      "options": [
        "Golden Week holidays",
        "to read a newspaper",
        "boy",
        "cat"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Golden Week holidays"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'osoi'?",
      "options": [
        "Judo",
        "summer festival",
        "romance / love story",
        "slow"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "slow"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kotae'?",
      "options": [
        "きょうしつ",
        "いしゃ",
        "ゴールデンウィーク",
        "こたえ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "こたえ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'never'?",
      "options": [
        "かんごし",
        "かいだん",
        "ぜんぜん",
        "みんな"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ぜんぜん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'osake'?",
      "options": [
        "まご",
        "ジャズ",
        "きっぷ",
        "おさけ／さけ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おさけ／さけ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'Hangarii'?",
      "options": [
        "meal",
        "office / company / firm",
        "Hungary",
        "soba noodles"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Hungary"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'でんしレンジ'?",
      "options": [
        "you",
        "winter holidays",
        "sandwich",
        "microwave oven"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "microwave oven"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'man / male'?",
      "options": [
        "おとこ",
        "なつやすみ",
        "インターネット（を）します",
        "ぎゅうにゅう／ミルク"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おとこ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kyooshi'?",
      "options": [
        "quantity",
        "teacher",
        "television",
        "book"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "teacher"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'おりがみ'?",
      "options": [
        "dog",
        "origami",
        "department store",
        "meat"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "origami"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'Ejiputo'?",
      "options": [
        "lots of (people) / crowded (with people)",
        "Egypt",
        "cereal",
        "Indonesia"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Egypt"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'posutaa'?",
      "options": [
        "never",
        "to take a walk",
        "soup",
        "poster"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "poster"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'sentakuki / sentakki'?",
      "options": [
        "せんたくき",
        "じえいぎょう",
        "やきそば",
        "スリランカ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "せんたくき"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'shio'?",
      "options": [
        "フランスご",
        "とりにく／チキン",
        "しお",
        "〜を　のみます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "しお"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ふくしゅう'?",
      "options": [
        "sofa",
        "fukushuu",
        "Chuugoku",
        "tokonoma"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "fukushuu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to relax'?",
      "options": [
        "howaito-boodo",
        "komedhi",
        "yukkuri shimasu",
        "shashin (o torimasu)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "yukkuri shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'hima'?",
      "options": [
        "to practice",
        "youth",
        "free / not occupied",
        "Please call me \"〜\""
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "free / not occupied"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'おおきい'?",
      "options": [
        "konsaato",
        "ookii",
        "baasudee",
        "yoko"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ookii"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'soba'?",
      "options": [
        "(someone else's) wife",
        "soba noodles",
        "boring / dull",
        "spaghetti / pasta"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "soba noodles"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'hayai'?",
      "options": [
        "Japanese person",
        "quick",
        "cherry-blossom viewing",
        "to say / to tell"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "quick"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ofuro ni hairimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "sad",
        "Kabuki",
        "evening meal",
        "to take a bath"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to take a bath"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'とり'?",
      "options": [
        "bird",
        "Japanese-style room",
        "(my) son",
        "festival / celebration"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "bird"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'おけしょう（を）します'?",
      "options": [
        "to check",
        "to put on makeup",
        "teacher",
        "adjectives"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to put on makeup"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ninjin'?",
      "options": [
        "origami",
        "tatami mat",
        "friend",
        "carrot"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "carrot"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'gakusee'?",
      "options": [
        "かんごし",
        "エジプト",
        "つかれます",
        "がくせい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "がくせい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tsumaranai'?",
      "options": [
        "え（を　かきます）",
        "とけい",
        "つまら ない",
        "おにいさん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "つまら ない"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'retasu'?",
      "options": [
        "soba noodles",
        "parents",
        "lettuce",
        "cooking / dish"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "lettuce"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'farmer'?",
      "options": [
        "にもつ",
        "バースデー",
        "のうか",
        "はくぶつかん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "のうか"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'ryokoo'?",
      "options": [
        "りょこう",
        "チョコレート",
        "たたみ",
        "ふくしゅう"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "りょこう"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'imooto'?",
      "options": [
        "おどり",
        "ぶどうがり",
        "いもうと",
        "ラーメン"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "いもうと"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'こうむいん'?",
      "options": [
        "snow festival",
        "things (found at home)",
        "civil servant",
        "medical doctor"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "civil servant"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'jinja'?",
      "options": [
        "じんじゃ",
        "とこのま",
        "まご",
        "さどう"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "じんじゃ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ホラー'?",
      "options": [
        "hanami",
        "sofu",
        "horaa",
        "retasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "horaa"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'となりのひと'?",
      "options": [
        "swimming",
        "strawberry",
        "the person next to you",
        "cheese"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "the person next to you"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kangoshi'?",
      "options": [
        "きせつのイベント",
        "アメリカ",
        "チケット",
        "かんごし"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かんごし"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'chiketto'?",
      "options": [
        "evening meal",
        "yogurt",
        "fishing / to go fishing",
        "ticket"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ticket"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for '(someone else's) wife'?",
      "options": [
        "ヨーロッパ",
        "たまねぎ",
        "おくさん",
        "そぼ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おくさん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'がいこくご／〜ご'?",
      "options": [
        "Mareeshia",
        "sandoicchi",
        "gaikokugo",
        "kiree"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "gaikokugo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ミステリー'?",
      "options": [
        "oshi'ire",
        "misuterii",
        "Furansu",
        "mizu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "misuterii"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'tenpura'?",
      "options": [
        "tempura",
        "bright",
        "engineer",
        "shrine"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tempura"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ちいさい'?",
      "options": [
        "shoosetsu",
        "otera",
        "raamen",
        "chiisai"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "chiisai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'oshi'ire'?",
      "options": [
        "おしいれ",
        "インドネシア",
        "はし",
        "カード"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おしいれ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for '〜を　あげます'?",
      "options": [
        "kodomo",
        "Roshia",
        "tenpura",
        "〜 o agemasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜 o agemasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'つくえ'?",
      "options": [
        "mazui",
        "suika",
        "keetai-denwa",
        "tsukue"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tsukue"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'かんごし'?",
      "options": [
        "kyoodai",
        "geemu",
        "kangoshi",
        "shitsumon (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kangoshi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'つくえ'?",
      "options": [
        "tsukue",
        "jazu",
        "panfuretto",
        "ringo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tsukue"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to look'?",
      "options": [
        "dansu",
        "mimasu",
        "yakisoba",
        "basuketto-booru"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "mimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'yogurt'?",
      "options": [
        "とりにく／チキン",
        "ろうか",
        "やまのぼり（を　します）",
        "ヨーグルト"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ヨーグルト"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'suteeki'?",
      "options": [
        "show",
        "slow",
        "steak",
        "meal"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "steak"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'part-time job'?",
      "options": [
        "かぞく",
        "パートタイム",
        "キャベツ",
        "おんなのひと"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "パートタイム"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'おっと'?",
      "options": [
        "fried noodles",
        "summer holidays",
        "alcoholic drinks / Japanese sake",
        "(my) husband"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(my) husband"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'どくしょ'?",
      "options": [
        "〜 ya (san)",
        "dokusho",
        "komedhi",
        "jisho"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "dokusho"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'mado'?",
      "options": [
        "orange",
        "window",
        "vacuum cleaner",
        "the person next to you"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "window"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to get up / to wake up'?",
      "options": [
        "nikki o kakimasu",
        "sanpo (o) shimasu",
        "okimasu",
        "asobimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "okimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'air conditioner'?",
      "options": [
        "コピー（を）します",
        "エアコン",
        "ぼんさい",
        "にほんじん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "エアコン"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'matsuri'?",
      "options": [
        "ぎゅうにく／ビーフ",
        "エンジニア",
        "まつり",
        "りょかん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "まつり"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'バター'?",
      "options": [
        "matsuri",
        "baabekyuu",
        "sadoo",
        "bataa"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "bataa"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tanjoobi'?",
      "options": [
        "たばこを　すいます",
        "しょくじ（を）します",
        "つま",
        "たんじょうび"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "たんじょうび"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'きゅうり'?",
      "options": [
        "Chuugoku",
        "kyuuri",
        "Mekishiko",
        "gyuuniku / biifu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kyuuri"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'soba noodles'?",
      "options": [
        "そば",
        "イギリス",
        "でんきせいひん",
        "ニュージーランド"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "そば"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'shrine'?",
      "options": [
        "yoshuu",
        "osushi / sushi",
        "suteeki",
        "jinja"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "jinja"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'スープ'?",
      "options": [
        "soup",
        "to take a walk",
        "event",
        "we"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "soup"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'にほんしゅ'?",
      "options": [
        "family",
        "old",
        "Japanese sake / rice wine",
        "youth"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Japanese sake / rice wine"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'odori'?",
      "options": [
        "おどり",
        "にほんりょうり",
        "すもう",
        "はなみ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おどり"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'nearby'?",
      "options": [
        "ドイツ",
        "ニュージーランド",
        "ちかく",
        "はやい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ちかく"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for '〜ご'?",
      "options": [
        "karaoke",
        "〜go",
        "itsumo",
        "otootosan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜go"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ryooshin'?",
      "options": [
        "food",
        "cereal",
        "butter",
        "parents"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "parents"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'soodan (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "みず",
        "いす",
        "そうだん（を）します",
        "チョコレート"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "そうだん（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'さかな'?",
      "options": [
        "bathroom / bath",
        "(my) younger brother",
        "fish",
        "she"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "fish"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'brothers and sisters'?",
      "options": [
        "きょうだい",
        "ふくを　ぬぎます",
        "え",
        "コンテスト"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "きょうだい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for '(someone else's) grandmother'?",
      "options": [
        "yakisoba",
        "suppai",
        "obaasan",
        "toire"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "obaasan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'retasu'?",
      "options": [
        "さかな",
        "やまのぼり（を　します）",
        "イベント",
        "レタス"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "レタス"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'bean curd / tofu'?",
      "options": [
        "fuku o nugimasu",
        "sumoo",
        "toofu",
        "yooguruto"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "toofu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for '(hito ga) ooi'?",
      "options": [
        "（ひとが）おおい",
        "ロシア",
        "あめ",
        "あたたかい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "（ひとが）おおい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'scary / frightening'?",
      "options": [
        "くらい",
        "こわい",
        "そぼ",
        "たかい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "こわい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'うしろ'?",
      "options": [
        "yamanobori (o shimasu)",
        "nemasu",
        "tsuma",
        "ushiro"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ushiro"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'りょこう（します）'?",
      "options": [
        "kangoshi",
        "asa / hiru / ban-gohan o tabemasu",
        "otoshiyori",
        "ryokoo (shimasu)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ryokoo (shimasu)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'manga / comic strips / comic books'?",
      "options": [
        "マンガ",
        "ひるごはん",
        "アイロン",
        "ひと"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "マンガ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'おしいれ'?",
      "options": [
        "table tennis / ping-pong",
        "beef",
        "sliding-door closet",
        "cherry-blossom viewing"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sliding-door closet"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'toriniku / chikin'?",
      "options": [
        "とりにく／チキン",
        "ホラー",
        "りょこう（します）",
        "サッカー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "とりにく／チキン"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'やすい'?",
      "options": [
        "France",
        "civil servant",
        "inexpensive / cheap",
        "happy / glad / delighted"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "inexpensive / cheap"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for '〜と よんでください'?",
      "options": [
        "terebi o mimasu",
        "batsu",
        "hayai",
        "〜 to yonde kudasai"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜 to yonde kudasai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'curtain'?",
      "options": [
        "kaiwa (o) shimasu",
        "Tai",
        "kaaten",
        "dokusho"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kaaten"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tokidoki'?",
      "options": [
        "エジプト",
        "ゲーム（を）します",
        "〜を　もらいます",
        "ときどき"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ときどき"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'oishii'?",
      "options": [
        "えび",
        "おいしい",
        "テーブル",
        "レストラン"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おいしい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'とり'?",
      "options": [
        "tori",
        "nikki o kakimasu",
        "komedhi",
        "manga"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tori"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'South Korea'?",
      "options": [
        "かんこく",
        "ホテル",
        "となりのひと",
        "たっきゅう／ピンポン"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かんこく"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kodomo'?",
      "options": [
        "たいこ",
        "ページ",
        "ほん",
        "こども"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "こども"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kyanpu (o shimasu)'?",
      "options": [
        "ひろい",
        "おねえさん",
        "キャンプ（を　します）",
        "みます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "キャンプ（を　します）"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ちゃわん'?",
      "options": [
        "rice bowl",
        "sliding-door closet",
        "tennis",
        "classroom"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "rice bowl"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'meat'?",
      "options": [
        "ベッドルーム",
        "にく",
        "おしょうがつ／しょうがつ",
        "ぜんぜん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "にく"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'shokuji'?",
      "options": [
        "Asia",
        "boring / dull",
        "meal",
        "quantity"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "meal"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'コップ'?",
      "options": [
        "zenzen",
        "koppu",
        "minasan",
        "tori"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "koppu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kaisha'?",
      "options": [
        "かいしゃ",
        "おとうと",
        "ちず",
        "ばんごう"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かいしゃ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'fried noodles'?",
      "options": [
        "やまのぼり（を　します）",
        "りょうり（を）します",
        "かいしゃ",
        "やきそば"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "やきそば"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ぼんおどり'?",
      "options": [
        "〜 ni nite imasu ne",
        "〜 no sewa o shimasu",
        "bon-odori",
        "maru"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "bon-odori"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'manga / comic strips / comic books'?",
      "options": [
        "poppusu",
        "Mekishiko",
        "amai",
        "manga"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "manga"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kaisha'?",
      "options": [
        "suitcase",
        "scary / frightening",
        "nearby",
        "office / company / firm"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "office / company / firm"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'map'?",
      "options": [
        "さどう",
        "ちず",
        "ステーキ",
        "ページ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ちず"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'おちゃ／ちゃ'?",
      "options": [
        "coffee",
        "I can speak (language)",
        "U.S.A. / America",
        "tea / Japanese tea"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tea / Japanese tea"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'いけばな'?",
      "options": [
        "ikebana",
        "tsukue",
        "fukushuu",
        "ryuugakusee"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ikebana"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for '(my) father'?",
      "options": [
        "chichi",
        "soojiki",
        "hoteru",
        "samui"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "chichi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'amazing / wonderful'?",
      "options": [
        "subarashii",
        "origami",
        "tomodachi ni aimasu",
        "sadoo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "subarashii"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ようしつ'?",
      "options": [
        "e (o kakimasu)",
        "tomodachi",
        "Betonamu",
        "yooshitsu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "yooshitsu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'fooku'?",
      "options": [
        "フォーク",
        "とけい",
        "おしょうがつ／しょうがつ",
        "むすめ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "フォーク"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'delicious / tasty'?",
      "options": [
        "kyooshi",
        "odorimasu",
        "koora",
        "oishii"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "oishii"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'in / inside'?",
      "options": [
        "jisho",
        "naka",
        "denshi-renji",
        "gakusee"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "naka"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'なっとう'?",
      "options": [
        "curry",
        "Sri Lanka",
        "natto (fermented soybeans)",
        "baby"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "natto (fermented soybeans)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'bangoo'?",
      "options": [
        "ベトナム",
        "ばんごう",
        "ケーキ",
        "ポップス"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ばんごう"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'でんきせいひん'?",
      "options": [
        "jibun",
        "hon-dana",
        "denki-seehin",
        "gaikokujin"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "denki-seehin"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'classical music'?",
      "options": [
        "danboo",
        "kurashikku",
        "hatsu-moode",
        "koocha"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kurashikku"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'がいこくじん'?",
      "options": [
        "gaikokujin",
        "Amerika",
        "shukudai",
        "atsui"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "gaikokujin"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ドア'?",
      "options": [
        "to make a phone call",
        "door",
        "to practice",
        "restaurant"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "door"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'show'?",
      "options": [
        "しょっぱい",
        "ショ ー",
        "たたみ",
        "じゅうどう"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ショ ー"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'office room'?",
      "options": [
        "じむしつ",
        "〜や（さん）",
        "てんぷら",
        "きょうかしょ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "じむしつ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'musume'?",
      "options": [
        "black tea",
        "(my) daughter",
        "foreign country",
        "photograph"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(my) daughter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'menu'?",
      "options": [
        "haha",
        "hiroi",
        "ureshii",
        "menyuu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "menyuu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'novel'?",
      "options": [
        "shoosetsu",
        "toriniku / chikin",
        "koora",
        "hiru-gohan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shoosetsu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'beautiful / pretty'?",
      "options": [
        "おとうさん",
        "ふくを　ぬぎます",
        "すずしい",
        "きれい（な）"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "きれい（な）"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ふじさん'?",
      "options": [
        "Fujisan",
        "ane",
        "sanpo (o) shimasu",
        "〜 o agemasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Fujisan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'りょう'?",
      "options": [
        "hanami",
        "iimasu",
        "ryoo",
        "atatakai"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ryoo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to play a game'?",
      "options": [
        "tsuri (o shimasu)",
        "geemu (o) shimasu",
        "atatakai",
        "oniisan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "geemu (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'test'?",
      "options": [
        "テレビ",
        "テスト",
        "ビザ",
        "こうむいん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "テスト"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'たまねぎ'?",
      "options": [
        "tamanegi",
        "shashin (o torimasu)",
        "Nyuujiirando",
        "Indoneshia"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tamanegi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'あつい'?",
      "options": [
        "to dance",
        "Italy",
        "reservation / booking (to make a reservation)",
        "hot"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hot"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'office / company / firm'?",
      "options": [
        "kaisha",
        "natsu-matsuri",
        "rooka",
        "aisatsu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kaisha"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'かいだん'?",
      "options": [
        "flower arrangement",
        "show",
        "(someone else's) child",
        "staircase"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "staircase"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'スリッパ'?",
      "options": [
        "butaniku / pooku",
        "surippa",
        "chichi",
        "supuun"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "surippa"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'いもうと'?",
      "options": [
        "book",
        "to watch TV",
        "(my) younger sister",
        "to help"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(my) younger sister"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'カレンダー'?",
      "options": [
        "kooen",
        "tonari no hito",
        "karendaa",
        "asa-gohan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "karendaa"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for '(hito ga) ooi'?",
      "options": [
        "lots of (people) / crowded (with people)",
        "pizza",
        "flower arrangement",
        "photograph (to take a photo)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "lots of (people) / crowded (with people)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'rice ball'?",
      "options": [
        "yooshitsu",
        "onigiri (omusubi)",
        "sonohoka",
        "dokusho"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "onigiri (omusubi)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'taihen'?",
      "options": [
        "たいへん",
        "みます",
        "ナイフ",
        "おとな"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "たいへん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ざっし'?",
      "options": [
        "ofuro",
        "tsumetai",
        "tsukaremasu",
        "zasshi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "zasshi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'そぼ'?",
      "options": [
        "(my) grandmother",
        "a friend comes to visit",
        "grapes",
        "staircase"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(my) grandmother"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'しょうじ'?",
      "options": [
        "birthday",
        "sliding screen",
        "greetings",
        "parents"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sliding screen"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'activities and events'?",
      "options": [
        "ぎゅうにく／ビーフ",
        "あさ／ひる／ばんごはんを　たべます",
        "いつも",
        "かつどう・イベント"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かつどう・イベント"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'やきゅう'?",
      "options": [
        "kagu",
        "okosan",
        "yakyuu",
        "kyabetsu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "yakyuu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'dekakemasu'?",
      "options": [
        "cold",
        "magazine",
        "to go out",
        "(not) many / (not) much"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to go out"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'フランスご'?",
      "options": [
        "to give",
        "big / large",
        "French language",
        "refrigerator"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "French language"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kirai'?",
      "options": [
        "dislike / hate",
        "visa",
        "(someone else's) elder sister",
        "Japanese sake / rice wine"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "dislike / hate"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to do a part-time job'?",
      "options": [
        "きゅうり",
        "ラーメン",
        "イギリス",
        "アルバイト／バイト（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "アルバイト／バイト（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'easy'?",
      "options": [
        "J ポップ",
        "コピー（を）します",
        "よやく （を します）",
        "やさしい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "やさしい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'notebook'?",
      "options": [
        "katudoo / ibento",
        "hiru-gohan",
        "nooto",
        "ryooshin"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "nooto"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'コメディ'?",
      "options": [
        "okosan",
        "sakkaa",
        "komedhi",
        "yomimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "komedhi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'karaoke'?",
      "options": [
        "gakkoo",
        "komedhi",
        "karaoke",
        "dokusho"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "karaoke"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'むすめ'?",
      "options": [
        "wain",
        "usagi",
        "fuku o nugimasu",
        "musume"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "musume"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'howaito-boodo'?",
      "options": [
        "fantasy fiction",
        "expensive",
        "man",
        "whiteboard"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "whiteboard"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'comedy'?",
      "options": [
        "コメディ",
        "しょうせつ",
        "ステーキ",
        "ベッド"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "コメディ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'きもの'?",
      "options": [
        "suitcase",
        "origami",
        "meat",
        "kimono"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kimono"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'すっぱい'?",
      "options": [
        "self-employed",
        "cola",
        "foreign country",
        "sour"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sour"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tsumaranai'?",
      "options": [
        "こわい",
        "つまらない",
        "スプーン",
        "ようしつ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "つまらない"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ドイツ'?",
      "options": [
        "boy",
        "mobile phone / cellular phone",
        "Germany",
        "ice cream"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Germany"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'おんなのこ'?",
      "options": [
        "aisu-kuriimu",
        "onna-no-ko",
        "reezooko",
        "remon"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "onna-no-ko"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'trip / to go on a trip'?",
      "options": [
        "〜ご",
        "おこさん",
        "さむい",
        "りょこう（します）"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "りょこう（します）"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'suzushii'?",
      "options": [
        "おふろ",
        "すずしい",
        "そうじき",
        "はは"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "すずしい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'warm'?",
      "options": [
        "スリランカ",
        "フィリピン",
        "あたたかい",
        "おとこのひと"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "あたたかい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'salty'?",
      "options": [
        "shoppai",
        "ima",
        "minna",
        "momijigari"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shoppai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Judo'?",
      "options": [
        "おいのり（を）します",
        "じゅうどう",
        "J ポップ",
        "べんきょう（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "じゅうどう"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'amari'?",
      "options": [
        "はは",
        "あまり",
        "たっきゅう／ピンポン",
        "ソファ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "あまり"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kabe'?",
      "options": [
        "hotel",
        "rock music",
        "clock",
        "wall"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "wall"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'bright'?",
      "options": [
        "akarui",
        "keeyooshi",
        "suika",
        "ane"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "akarui"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'zenzen'?",
      "options": [
        "パン",
        "おふろ",
        "あめ",
        "ぜんぜん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ぜんぜん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'hobby / interest'?",
      "options": [
        "takai",
        "shumi",
        "baasudee",
        "paathii"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shumi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'にく'?",
      "options": [
        "niku",
        "tonari",
        "〜 ryoori",
        "uchi ni kaerimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "niku"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'jiko-shookai (shimasu)'?",
      "options": [
        "ベッド",
        "メニュー",
        "じこしょうかい（します）",
        "さんぽ（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "じこしょうかい（します）"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'とりにく／チキン'?",
      "options": [
        "chicken",
        "to tidy up",
        "to use / surf the Internet",
        "(not) often"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "chicken"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Golden Week holidays'?",
      "options": [
        "ベッド",
        "ゴールデンウィーク",
        "いぬ",
        "にわ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ゴールデンウィーク"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'インド'?",
      "options": [
        "pen",
        "suzushii",
        "menyuu",
        "Indo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Indo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'France'?",
      "options": [
        "ハンバーガー",
        "ひと",
        "〜じん",
        "フランス"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "フランス"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'origami'?",
      "options": [
        "origami",
        "furaido-poteto",
        "(hito ga) ooi",
        "shufu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "origami"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'shrine'?",
      "options": [
        "とこのま",
        "アメリカ",
        "じ んじゃ",
        "きれい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "じ んじゃ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'takai'?",
      "options": [
        "(my) son",
        "Brazil",
        "expensive",
        "classical music"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "expensive"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'picture (to draw a picture)'?",
      "options": [
        "ryokoo (shimasu)",
        "kuukoo",
        "bataa",
        "e (o kakimasu)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "e (o kakimasu)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kabe'?",
      "options": [
        "やさい",
        "かべ",
        "どくしょ",
        "カレー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かべ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'かぞく'?",
      "options": [
        "family",
        "heater",
        "Europe",
        "Chinese language"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "family"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'アルバイト（バイト）'?",
      "options": [
        "tempura",
        "part-time job",
        "action",
        "to practice"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "part-time job"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to shave'?",
      "options": [
        "せんせい",
        "〜と　おしゃべり（を）します",
        "でんわ",
        "ひげを　そります"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ひげを　そります"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'まずい'?",
      "options": [
        "to say / to tell",
        "juice",
        "taiko drumming",
        "unappetizing"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "unappetizing"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'piano'?",
      "options": [
        "ニュージーランド",
        "たくさん",
        "ピアノ",
        "ショー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ピアノ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'warm'?",
      "options": [
        "faasuto-fuudo-ten",
        "atatakai",
        "kikimasu",
        "reezooko"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "atatakai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'nimotsu'?",
      "options": [
        "そのほか",
        "にもつ",
        "コーヒー",
        "りょかん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "にもつ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'bentoo'?",
      "options": [
        "チーズバーガー",
        "なまえ",
        "べんとう",
        "ひと"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "べんとう"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ばんごはん'?",
      "options": [
        "to say / to tell",
        "soba noodles",
        "watermelon",
        "evening meal"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "evening meal"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'always'?",
      "options": [
        "itsumo",
        "zangyoo (o) shimasu",
        "omoshiroi",
        "sooji (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "itsumo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'beranda'?",
      "options": [
        "adjectives",
        "balcony",
        "map",
        "to keep a diary"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "balcony"
    },
    
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'すき（な）'?",
      "options": [
        "suki",
        "chiisai",
        "otooto",
        "purezento"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "suki"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'ushiro'?",
      "options": [
        "ふくしゅう",
        "ベッド",
        "からい",
        "うしろ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "うしろ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'ban-gohan'?",
      "options": [
        "ゲーム（を）します",
        "しお",
        "よく",
        "ばんごはん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ばんごはん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kingyo'?",
      "options": [
        "comedy",
        "goldfish",
        "Thailand",
        "to drink 〜"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "goldfish"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'muzukashii'?",
      "options": [
        "せんたく（を）します",
        "テーブル",
        "しゃしん（を　とります）",
        "むずかしい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "むずかしい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'namae'?",
      "options": [
        "trip / to go on a trip",
        "Egypt",
        "name",
        "(my) wife"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "name"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'さしみ'?",
      "options": [
        "sashimi",
        "ima",
        "aisu",
        "misoshiru"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sashimi"
    },
    
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to have a conversation'?",
      "options": [
        "つまらない",
        "スーツケース",
        "わかもの",
        "かいわ（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かいわ（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ゆきまつり'?",
      "options": [
        "Brazil",
        "baby",
        "snow festival",
        "autumn festival"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "snow festival"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'paatotaimu (paato)'?",
      "options": [
        "living room",
        "part-time job",
        "electric fan",
        "man"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "part-time job"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ホットドッグ'?",
      "options": [
        "karendaa",
        "hottodoggu",
        "amari",
        "shokuji"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hottodoggu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'かたづけます'?",
      "options": [
        "oneesan",
        "katazukemasu",
        "shooyu",
        "menyuu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "katazukemasu"
    },
    
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'brochure / pamphlet'?",
      "options": [
        "ヨガ（を）します",
        "ようしつ",
        "パ ンフレット",
        "した"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "パ ンフレット"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'カナダ'?",
      "options": [
        "fishing / to go fishing",
        "Canada",
        "foreign language",
        "cooking / dish"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Canada"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to use / surf the Internet'?",
      "options": [
        "karendaa",
        "suiee",
        "jazu",
        "intaanetto (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "intaanetto (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Tokyo'?",
      "options": [
        "とうきょう",
        "きょうしつ",
        "おさけ／さけ",
        "けしごむ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "とうきょう"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'chiizu'?",
      "options": [
        "fast-food restaurant",
        "souvenir",
        "cheese",
        "to brush / clean one's teeth"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "cheese"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'fireworks'?",
      "options": [
        "ocha",
        "hanabi",
        "sonohoka",
        "manga"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hanabi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ピザ'?",
      "options": [
        "Italy",
        "sushi",
        "goldfish",
        "pizza"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "pizza"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'yukkuri shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "to relax",
        "to work / do one's job",
        "cabbage",
        "to draw"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to relax"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for '〜じん'?",
      "options": [
        "〜jin",
        "konsaato",
        "ha o migakimasu",
        "chiizu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜jin"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'バナナ'?",
      "options": [
        "suiee",
        "banana",
        "tabako o suimasu",
        "gohan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "banana"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tourist spot / sightseeing area'?",
      "options": [
        "ゆっくりします",
        "おすし／すし",
        "〜に　とまります",
        "かんこうち"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かんこうち"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'grapes'?",
      "options": [
        "bijutsukan",
        "jieegyoo",
        "budoo",
        "fusuma"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "budoo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'telephone'?",
      "options": [
        "tori",
        "denwa",
        "mimasu",
        "chiketto"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "denwa"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'oshoogatsu'?",
      "options": [
        "New Year's holiday",
        "onion",
        "family",
        "to take a shower"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "New Year's holiday"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'usagi'?",
      "options": [
        "leaflet / flyer",
        "to read a newspaper",
        "rabbit",
        "breakfast"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "rabbit"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'mikan'?",
      "options": [
        "ゴルフ",
        "みかん",
        "ゆきまつり",
        "れんしゅう（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "みかん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'coffee shop'?",
      "options": [
        "Ejiputo",
        "Oosutoraria",
        "odorimasu",
        "kissaten"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kissaten"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'Ajia'?",
      "options": [
        "quantity",
        "fried potatoes / french fries / chips",
        "Asia",
        "soccer / football"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Asia"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for '(someone else's) elder brother'?",
      "options": [
        "すき（な）",
        "ピアノ",
        "おにいさん",
        "おちゃ／ちゃ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おにいさん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Oosutoraria'?",
      "options": [
        "ホワイトボード",
        "オーストラリア",
        "やきゅう",
        "かんごし"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "オーストラリア"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'farmer'?",
      "options": [
        "zenzen",
        "nooka",
        "hanami",
        "kabuki"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "nooka"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'school'?",
      "options": [
        "がっこう",
        "あたたかい",
        "がくせい",
        "しゅみ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "がっこう"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'leaflet / flyer'?",
      "options": [
        "chirashi",
        "sentaku (o) shimasu",
        "okeshoo (o) shimasu",
        "eakon"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "chirashi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'かんこく'?",
      "options": [
        "Kankoku",
        "zasshi",
        "oishii",
        "peeji"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Kankoku"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'okaasan'?",
      "options": [
        "くうこう",
        "おかあさん",
        "ことば",
        "しゅみ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おかあさん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'nimotsu'?",
      "options": [
        "やすみます",
        "かつどう・イベント",
        "に もつ",
        "スーツケ ース"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "に もつ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'おとうとさん'?",
      "options": [
        "(someone else's) younger brother",
        "Japanese pop music",
        "to look",
        "free / not occupied"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(someone else's) younger brother"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ふくを　ぬぎます'?",
      "options": [
        "J-poppu",
        "rajio",
        "fuku o nugimasu",
        "uta"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "fuku o nugimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'daidokoro'?",
      "options": [
        "だいどころ",
        "チョコレート",
        "こうむいん",
        "りょこう"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "だいどころ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'genkan'?",
      "options": [
        "あまい",
        "ジュース",
        "あたたかい",
        "げんかん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "げんかん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for '〜と　おしゃべり（を）します'?",
      "options": [
        "to go to bed / to sleep",
        "to chat with 〜",
        "whiteboard",
        "party"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to chat with 〜"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'しゅくだい'?",
      "options": [
        "Oosutoraria",
        "denki-seehin",
        "shukudai",
        "Roshia"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shukudai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'おどり'?",
      "options": [
        "tsumetai",
        "odori",
        "subarashii",
        "watashitachi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "odori"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'すき（な）'?",
      "options": [
        "suki",
        "Yooroppa",
        "tsukaremasu",
        "nori"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "suki"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'chichi'?",
      "options": [
        "ろうか",
        "ヨーグルト",
        "ちち",
        "れんしゅう（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ちち"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ひげを　そります'?",
      "options": [
        "nagai",
        "ringo",
        "takai",
        "hige o sorimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hige o sorimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'かぞく'?",
      "options": [
        "ima",
        "kazoku",
        "baabekyuu",
        "gaikokugo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kazoku"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kodomo'?",
      "options": [
        "child",
        "foreigner",
        "Australia",
        "video game / computer game"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "child"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'song'?",
      "options": [
        "uta",
        "kaimono (o) shimasu",
        "Ajia",
        "shitsumon (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "uta"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'keeki'?",
      "options": [
        "chopsticks",
        "cake",
        "leaflet / flyer",
        "Italy"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "cake"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'Tookyoo'?",
      "options": [
        "lunch",
        "Tokyo",
        "soy sauce",
        "onion"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Tokyo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'cooked rice'?",
      "options": [
        "niku",
        "tatami",
        "shio",
        "gohan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "gohan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'photograph'?",
      "options": [
        "isu",
        "shooji",
        "shiriaru",
        "shashin"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shashin"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to take a bath'?",
      "options": [
        "naka",
        "ofuro ni hairimasu",
        "denki",
        "imootosan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ofuro ni hairimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'わしつ'?",
      "options": [
        "washitsu",
        "yooguruto",
        "shawaa o abimasu",
        "taiko"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "washitsu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for '(hard) candy'?",
      "options": [
        "あめ",
        "ぼんおどり",
        "ニュージーランド",
        "〜が　できます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "あめ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'はいく'?",
      "options": [
        "〜 shop / restaurant",
        "Haiku",
        "foreign language",
        "girl"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Haiku"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'はこ'?",
      "options": [
        "aki-matsuri",
        "keetai-denwa",
        "semai",
        "hako"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hako"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'jam'?",
      "options": [
        "fusuma",
        "Mekishiko",
        "aisatsu",
        "jamu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "jamu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'もの'?",
      "options": [
        "mono",
        "Tookyoo",
        "kowai",
        "baabekyuu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "mono"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'yomimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "to read",
        "like",
        "dish / plate",
        "sweet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to read"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'Spain'?",
      "options": [
        "natsu-yasumi",
        "sukoshi",
        "Supein",
        "e"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Supein"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to check'?",
      "options": [
        "koohii",
        "gakusee",
        "chekku (o) shimasu",
        "gitaa"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "chekku (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'oneesan'?",
      "options": [
        "たのしい",
        "おねえさん",
        "おとこのこ",
        "スケート"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おねえさん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'あまり'?",
      "options": [
        "amari",
        "gaikokugo",
        "shukudai",
        "resutoran"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "amari"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'suki'?",
      "options": [
        "サラダ",
        "アイロン",
        "うたいます",
        "すき"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "すき"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'shoppai'?",
      "options": [
        "to have a meal",
        "salty",
        "pop music",
        "(my) younger brother"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "salty"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'question / problem'?",
      "options": [
        "ばんごはん",
        "みそしる",
        "きゅうり",
        "もんだい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "もんだい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'fruit'?",
      "options": [
        "くだもの",
        "ほん",
        "おとうとさん",
        "こわい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "くだもの"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'hayai'?",
      "options": [
        "たかい",
        "はやい",
        "いもうと",
        "あまい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "はやい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'こうちゃ'?",
      "options": [
        "card",
        "(my) mother",
        "black tea",
        "fireworks display"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "black tea"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'teacher / instructor'?",
      "options": [
        "せんせい",
        "ざぶとん",
        "くうこう",
        "ゆっくりします"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "せんせい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'pizza'?",
      "options": [
        "バーベキュー",
        "べんきょう（を）します",
        "ピザ",
        "レモン"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ピザ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'yooguruto'?",
      "options": [
        "dog",
        "fork",
        "to read a newspaper",
        "yogurt"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "yogurt"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'sooji (o) shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "きれい（な）",
        "そうじ（を）します",
        "ばんごう",
        "かぶき"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "そうじ（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'みかん'?",
      "options": [
        "Indonesia",
        "orange",
        "fruit",
        "foreigner"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "orange"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'hottodoggu'?",
      "options": [
        "engineer",
        "hot dog",
        "a lot",
        "jogging"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hot dog"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kakimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "shelf",
        "origami",
        "brothers and sisters",
        "to write"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to write"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'きたない'?",
      "options": [
        "child",
        "hamburger",
        "untidy / dirty",
        "reading"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "untidy / dirty"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'keeki'?",
      "options": [
        "せまい",
        "なつやすみ",
        "いちご",
        "ケーキ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ケーキ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'cereal'?",
      "options": [
        "ピザ",
        "おしょうがつ／しょうがつ",
        "じぶん",
        "シリアル"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "シリアル"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'terebi o mimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "to watch TV",
        "literature",
        "(someone else's) grandmother",
        "(my) mother"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to watch TV"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'interesting'?",
      "options": [
        "omoshiroi",
        "kabe",
        "odorimasu",
        "〜 ryoori"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "omoshiroi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'television'?",
      "options": [
        "あなた",
        "ラジオ",
        "テレビ",
        "フランス"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "テレビ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kooen'?",
      "options": [
        "(my) son",
        "self-introduction (to introduce oneself)",
        "bread",
        "park"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "park"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'はし'?",
      "options": [
        "eega",
        "suika",
        "oyu",
        "hashi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hashi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'teeburu'?",
      "options": [
        "カラオケ",
        "テーブル",
        "おとしより",
        "つめたい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "テーブル"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'tomodachi ni aimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "cooked rice",
        "cheese burger",
        "to meet a friend",
        "jogging"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to meet a friend"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'あいさつ'?",
      "options": [
        "aisatsu",
        "Supein",
        "naifu",
        "okashi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "aisatsu"
    },
    
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'samui'?",
      "options": [
        "はやい",
        "さむ い",
        "でんきせいひん",
        "すいえい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "さむ い"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'naifu'?",
      "options": [
        "くだもの",
        "サンドイッチ",
        "ナイフ",
        "ヨーグルト"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ナイフ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'youth'?",
      "options": [
        "resutoran",
        "chikaku",
        "wakamono",
        "gurasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "wakamono"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'でんき'?",
      "options": [
        "ryokan",
        "denki",
        "ichigo",
        "kome"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "denki"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'science fiction'?",
      "options": [
        "SF",
        "せつめい（を）します",
        "うどん",
        "そぼ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "SF"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Korean language'?",
      "options": [
        "〜が　できます",
        "かんこくご",
        "うえ",
        "たくさん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かんこくご"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ろうか'?",
      "options": [
        "quick",
        "corridor",
        "travel / trip",
        "book"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "corridor"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'のり'?",
      "options": [
        "seaweed",
        "fireworks",
        "electrical appliance",
        "a friend comes to visit"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "seaweed"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Bon Festival dance'?",
      "options": [
        "ヨーロッパ",
        "たいこ",
        "ゲーム",
        "ぼんおどり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ぼんおどり"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Arabic language'?",
      "options": [
        "アラビアご",
        "カップ",
        "ざぶとん",
        "からい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "アラビアご"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'classroom'?",
      "options": [
        "つくえ",
        "きょうかしょ",
        "スリランカ",
        "きょうしつ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "きょうしつ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ゲーム'?",
      "options": [
        "momijigari",
        "geemu",
        "fuku o kimasu",
        "shinbun o yomimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "geemu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kanojo'?",
      "options": [
        "しょくじ（を）します",
        "かのじょ",
        "とり",
        "よやく （を します）"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かのじょ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tenisu'?",
      "options": [
        "テニス",
        "〜じん",
        "あさ／ひる／ばんごはんを　たべます",
        "しんぶんを　よみます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "テニス"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'natsu-matsuri'?",
      "options": [
        "フランスご",
        "ちいさい",
        "さむい",
        "なつまつり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "なつまつり"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'げんかん'?",
      "options": [
        "jamu",
        "〜 o agemasu",
        "takai",
        "genkan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "genkan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'ookii'?",
      "options": [
        "きんぎょ",
        "ステーキ",
        "キャベツ",
        "おおきい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おおきい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Japanese-style room'?",
      "options": [
        "がくせい",
        "アルバイト／バイト（を）します",
        "〜じん",
        "わしつ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "わしつ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'otootosan'?",
      "options": [
        "すもう",
        "エンジニア",
        "おとうとさん",
        "とりにく／チキン"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おとうとさん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Kabuki'?",
      "options": [
        "かぶき",
        "にほん／にっぽん",
        "じゅぎょう",
        "わたし"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "かぶき"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'often'?",
      "options": [
        "バスケットボール",
        "やきゅう",
        "レタス",
        "よく"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "よく"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'rock music'?",
      "options": [
        "yamanobori (o shimasu)",
        "akushon",
        "sarada",
        "rokku"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "rokku"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'やさしい'?",
      "options": [
        "mountain-climbing (to climb a mountain)",
        "Japanese sake / rice wine",
        "easy",
        "visa"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'sonohoka'?",
      "options": [
        "school",
        "entrance",
        "ice cream",
        "others"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "others"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'でんわ（を）します／かけます'?",
      "options": [
        "mystery",
        "bright",
        "to make a phone call",
        "tidy / clean"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to make a phone call"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'movie / film'?",
      "options": [
        "ヨーグルト",
        "えいが",
        "カレー",
        "おんなのこ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "えいが"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ofuro'?",
      "options": [
        "clock",
        "Malaysia",
        "French language",
        "bathroom / bath"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "bathroom / bath"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'akachan'?",
      "options": [
        "はなします",
        "あかちゃん",
        "たたみ",
        "つり（を　します）"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "あかちゃん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'コメディ'?",
      "options": [
        "to receive",
        "lettuce",
        "comedy",
        "sugar"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "comedy"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'yukkuri shimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "ひきます",
        "チラシ",
        "ゆっくりします",
        "はくぶつかん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ゆっくりします"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'foreign language'?",
      "options": [
        "gaikokugo",
        "hima",
        "subarashii",
        "kisetsu no ibento"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "gaikokugo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'つかれます'?",
      "options": [
        "you",
        "to get tired",
        "tempura",
        "tea ceremony"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to get tired"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for '〜を　もらいます'?",
      "options": [
        "geemu (o) shimasu",
        "〜 o moraimasu",
        "kaiwa (o) shimasu",
        "tonari no hito"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜 o moraimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'cucumber'?",
      "options": [
        "きゅうり",
        "みかん",
        "ひきます",
        "にっきを　かきます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "きゅうり"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tomodachi'?",
      "options": [
        "きたない",
        "べんとう",
        "ともだち",
        "フライドポテト"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ともだち"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'dictionary'?",
      "options": [
        "じしょ",
        "いけばな",
        "おとこのこ",
        "たばこを　すいます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "じしょ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for '〜 ryoori'?",
      "options": [
        "Indonesia",
        "rice ball",
        "〜 food / 〜 cuisine",
        "to meet a friend"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜 food / 〜 cuisine"
    },
    
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'あさごはん'?",
      "options": [
        "breakfast",
        "yogurt",
        "air conditioner",
        "Japanese-style room"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "breakfast"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'wasabi (Japanese horseradish)'?",
      "options": [
        "チーズ",
        "げんかん",
        "つま",
        "わさび"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "わさび"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'okosan'?",
      "options": [
        "さら",
        "おねえさん",
        "こわい",
        "おこさん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おこさん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'cooking / dish'?",
      "options": [
        "kitanai",
        "watashitachi",
        "ryoori",
        "karai"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ryoori"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'shashin'?",
      "options": [
        "たのしい",
        "ポップス",
        "しゅふ",
        "しゃしん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "しゃしん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'alcove'?",
      "options": [
        "エンジニア",
        "とこのま",
        "かんこうち",
        "ショー"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "とこのま"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'sushi'?",
      "options": [
        "きたない",
        "わさび",
        "おすし／すし",
        "せつめい（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おすし／すし"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'fuyu-yasumi'?",
      "options": [
        "(someone else's) younger sister",
        "Italy",
        "to relax",
        "winter holidays"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "winter holidays"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to do yoga'?",
      "options": [
        "yoga (o) shimasu",
        "fuku o kimasu",
        "kamera",
        "kowai"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "yoga (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'Kankokugo'?",
      "options": [
        "Korean language",
        "lemon",
        "yogurt",
        "snow festival"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Korean language"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'せんせい'?",
      "options": [
        "milk",
        "teacher / instructor",
        "piano",
        "to do yoga"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "teacher / instructor"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'soojiki'?",
      "options": [
        "vacuum cleaner",
        "dance",
        "the person next to you",
        "cat"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "vacuum cleaner"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'shashin'?",
      "options": [
        "fireworks display",
        "classroom",
        "orange",
        "photograph"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "photograph"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to write'?",
      "options": [
        "〜 ni tomarimasu",
        "hanbaagaa",
        "kakimasu",
        "juusu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kakimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ねます'?",
      "options": [
        "adult",
        "school",
        "Egypt",
        "to go to bed / to sleep"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to go to bed / to sleep"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'satoo'?",
      "options": [
        "メニュー",
        "はは",
        "さとう",
        "わたし"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "さとう"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to get up / to wake up'?",
      "options": [
        "おきます",
        "チェック（を）します",
        "ロック",
        "いぬ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おきます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'uchi ni kaerimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "そのほか",
        "うちに　かえります",
        "ポップス",
        "もの"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "うちに　かえります"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'omiyage'?",
      "options": [
        "おみやげ",
        "じしょ",
        "もみじがり",
        "うれしい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おみやげ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'to stop over / to stay at (a hotel)'?",
      "options": [
        "hotto",
        "koohii",
        "oneesan",
        "〜 ni tomarimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜 ni tomarimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'チケット'?",
      "options": [
        "Itaria",
        "hanabi-taikai",
        "chiketto",
        "musuko"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "chiketto"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'language'?",
      "options": [
        "ha o migakimasu",
        "sadoo",
        "kotoba",
        "gaikokujin"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kotoba"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'かいわ（を）します'?",
      "options": [
        "ureshii",
        "terebi o mimasu",
        "kanojo",
        "kaiwa (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kaiwa (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'フライドポテト'?",
      "options": [
        "asa-gohan",
        "furaido-poteto",
        "sarada",
        "isha"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "furaido-poteto"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ばんごはん'?",
      "options": [
        "kabuki",
        "ocha",
        "ban-gohan",
        "watashi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ban-gohan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'nattoo'?",
      "options": [
        "なっとう",
        "コーラ",
        "まど",
        "なか"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "なっとう"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'oyu'?",
      "options": [
        "かいしゃ",
        "ぶたにく／ポーク",
        "スープ",
        "おゆ／ゆ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おゆ／ゆ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ショー'?",
      "options": [
        "yasumimasu",
        "hiru-gohan",
        "zabuton",
        "shoo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shoo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'たばこを　すいます'?",
      "options": [
        "kiree",
        "faasuto-fuudo-ten",
        "posutaa",
        "tabako o suimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tabako o suimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'butter'?",
      "options": [
        "バター",
        "なまえ",
        "カメラ",
        "ひま（な）"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "バター"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'takusan'?",
      "options": [
        "カナダ",
        "コーラ",
        "たくさん",
        "カメラ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "たくさん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'koppu'?",
      "options": [
        "コップ",
        "〜に　いきます",
        "かぶき",
        "こめ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "コップ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'like'?",
      "options": [
        "すき（な）",
        "たいこ",
        "かいもの（を）します",
        "プレゼント"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "すき（な）"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'hon-dana'?",
      "options": [
        "ホット",
        "かのじょ",
        "ほんだな",
        "おんな"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ほんだな"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'わたしたち'?",
      "options": [
        "yooshitsu",
        "musuko",
        "sakana",
        "watashitachi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "watashitachi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'pork'?",
      "options": [
        "ongaku o kikimasu",
        "beddo",
        "butaniku / pooku",
        "supootsu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "butaniku / pooku"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'park'?",
      "options": [
        "こうえん",
        "スポーツ",
        "むすこ",
        "みず"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "こうえん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'sandwich'?",
      "options": [
        "コーヒー",
        "サンドイッチ",
        "クラシック",
        "きっさてん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "サンドイッチ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ryoo'?",
      "options": [
        "Sri Lanka",
        "quantity",
        "table",
        "elderly person"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "quantity"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'tsuri (o shimasu)'?",
      "options": [
        "grandchild",
        "Egypt",
        "curtain",
        "fishing / to go fishing"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "fishing / to go fishing"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'にほんしゅ'?",
      "options": [
        "kooen",
        "okashi",
        "nihonshu",
        "basuketto-booru"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "nihonshu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'イギリス'?",
      "options": [
        "Indonesia",
        "U.K.",
        "German language",
        "pork"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "U.K."
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'Japanese language'?",
      "options": [
        "Nihongo",
        "imootosan",
        "Amerika",
        "denwa"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Nihongo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'fun / enjoyable'?",
      "options": [
        "もの",
        "すずしい",
        "たのしい",
        "たまご"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "たのしい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'otooto'?",
      "options": [
        "ぼんおどり",
        "おとうと",
        "キャンプ（を　します）",
        "からい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おとうと"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'しょうせつ'?",
      "options": [
        "microwave oven",
        "to check",
        "to pray",
        "novel"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "novel"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'しょっき'?",
      "options": [
        "to watch TV",
        "tableware",
        "kitchen",
        "cucumber"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tableware"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Japan'?",
      "options": [
        "にほん／にっぽん",
        "わかもの",
        "りょこう",
        "ちず"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "にほん／にっぽん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'にほんじん'?",
      "options": [
        "book",
        "ticket",
        "Japanese person",
        "fried potatoes / french fries / chips"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Japanese person"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'おけしょう（を）します'?",
      "options": [
        "muzukashii",
        "okeshoo (o) shimasu",
        "Yooroppa",
        "arubaito (baito)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "okeshoo (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for '〜 shop / restaurant'?",
      "options": [
        "odori",
        "〜 ya (san)",
        "okashi",
        "itsumo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜 ya (san)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for '〜go'?",
      "options": [
        "〜 language",
        "bedroom",
        "adjectives",
        "to work overtime / extra hours"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜 language"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ふるい'?",
      "options": [
        "ane",
        "pan",
        "shawaa o abimasu",
        "furui"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "furui"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'おじいさん'?",
      "options": [
        "tonari",
        "onna-no-ko",
        "ojiisan",
        "kurasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ojiisan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'watashi'?",
      "options": [
        "かんごし",
        "おとうさん",
        "わたし",
        "てんぷら"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "わたし"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'juice'?",
      "options": [
        "ebi",
        "gohan",
        "juusu",
        "futon"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "juusu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for '(someone else's) father'?",
      "options": [
        "oniisan",
        "sara",
        "chichi",
        "otoosan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "otoosan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'expensive'?",
      "options": [
        "aki-matsuri",
        "senpuuki",
        "tenisu",
        "takai"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "takai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'sarada'?",
      "options": [
        "fried noodles",
        "salad",
        "leaflet / flyer",
        "civil servant"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "salad"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tempura'?",
      "options": [
        "となりのひと",
        "おとこのひと",
        "てんぷら",
        "バター"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "てんぷら"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'furniture'?",
      "options": [
        "namae",
        "imooto",
        "Indoneshia",
        "kagu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kagu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to cook'?",
      "options": [
        "たっきゅう／ピンポン",
        "からい",
        "ぼんおどり",
        "りょうり（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "りょうり（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'toire'?",
      "options": [
        "window",
        "wasabi (Japanese horseradish)",
        "Indonesia",
        "toilet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "toilet"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'おどります'?",
      "options": [
        "kyooshitsu",
        "hima",
        "odorimasu",
        "sashimi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "odorimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for '〜に　いきます'?",
      "options": [
        "ni ikimasu",
        "otona",
        "Betonamu",
        "jieegyoo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ni ikimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'oishii'?",
      "options": [
        "(someone else's) husband",
        "seaweed",
        "France",
        "delicious / tasty"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "delicious / tasty"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'じぶん'?",
      "options": [
        "kyooshi",
        "Supein",
        "jibun",
        "beddo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "jibun"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'picture'?",
      "options": [
        "senpuuki",
        "asa-gohan",
        "osushi / sushi",
        "e"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "e"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'oshoogatsu'?",
      "options": [
        "わたしたち",
        "おしょうがつ ／おしょうがつ",
        "イギリス",
        "がっこう"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おしょうがつ ／おしょうがつ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'tanjoobi'?",
      "options": [
        "pencil",
        "table",
        "to relax",
        "birthday"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "birthday"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'きせつのイベント'?",
      "options": [
        "grapes",
        "to take a shower",
        "salt",
        "seasonal events"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "seasonal events"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kurashikku'?",
      "options": [
        "はくぶつかん",
        "クラシック",
        "アイロン",
        "りんご"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "クラシック"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'べんきょう（を）します'?",
      "options": [
        "out / outside",
        "balcony",
        "to study",
        "to have a meal"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to study"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'chiisai'?",
      "options": [
        "sweets / confectionery",
        "rock music",
        "small",
        "microwave oven"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "small"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'minasan'?",
      "options": [
        "sleepy",
        "farmer",
        "Tokyo",
        "everyone"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "everyone"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'water'?",
      "options": [
        "みず",
        "スーツケース",
        "ベランダ",
        "しごと（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "みず"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'karee'?",
      "options": [
        "(hard) candy",
        "boy",
        "China",
        "curry"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "curry"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'gohan'?",
      "options": [
        "ごはん／ライス",
        "ぶどう",
        "きせつのイベント",
        "さら"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ごはん／ライス"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'エジプト'?",
      "options": [
        "Nihon / Nippon",
        "otoko-no-hito",
        "Ejiputo",
        "kotoba"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Ejiputo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'ani'?",
      "options": [
        "サッカー",
        "たたみ",
        "〜を　あげます",
        "あに"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "あに"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'じゅぎょう'?",
      "options": [
        "cherry-blossom viewing",
        "class / school lessons",
        "iced (coffee / tea)",
        "entrance"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "class / school lessons"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'Bonsai'?",
      "options": [
        "Ejiputo",
        "jimushitsu",
        "bonsai",
        "〜 to oshaberi (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "bonsai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'がくせい'?",
      "options": [
        "shooji",
        "gakusee",
        "aisu",
        "geemu (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "gakusee"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'zasshi'?",
      "options": [
        "ざっし",
        "ごはん／ライス",
        "しゃしん",
        "たべもの"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ざっし"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'people from … (nationality)'?",
      "options": [
        "みそしる",
        "〜じん",
        "たべもの",
        "けいたいでんわ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜じん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'かいわ（を）します'?",
      "options": [
        "cooking / dish",
        "rice",
        "Italy",
        "to have a conversation"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to have a conversation"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'tenpura'?",
      "options": [
        "potato",
        "tempura",
        "calendar",
        "cooking / dish"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tempura"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'sakana'?",
      "options": [
        "さかな",
        "しょっき",
        "きっさてん",
        "きもの"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "さかな"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'はなみ'?",
      "options": [
        "hotto",
        "jinja",
        "karai",
        "hanami"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hanami"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ぶんがく'?",
      "options": [
        "toofu",
        "bungaku",
        "tsukue",
        "oinori (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "bungaku"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'げんかん'?",
      "options": [
        "Japanese food",
        "ice cream",
        "entrance",
        "(hard) candy"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "entrance"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'niku'?",
      "options": [
        "meat",
        "cooked rice",
        "wine",
        "Mexico"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "meat"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ticket'?",
      "options": [
        "ryoori (o) shimasu",
        "kippu",
        "Burajiru",
        "chekku (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kippu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'nice / good'?",
      "options": [
        "ii",
        "obaasan",
        "chotto",
        "inu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ii"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kome'?",
      "options": [
        "かいもの（を）します",
        "こめ",
        "フォーク",
        "みず"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "こめ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'eraser'?",
      "options": [
        "Ajia",
        "dekakemasu",
        "keshigomu",
        "ofuro"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "keshigomu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'hot / spicy / salty'?",
      "options": [
        "karai",
        "〜 o nomimasu",
        "Indo",
        "suupu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "karai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'ha o migakimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "サラダ",
        "はを　みがきます",
        "おこさん",
        "おとうさん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "はを　みがきます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'haha'?",
      "options": [
        "(my) mother",
        "tea ceremony",
        "U.S.A. / America",
        "adjectives"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(my) mother"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'concert'?",
      "options": [
        "シャワーを　あびます",
        "すき（な）",
        "やきそば",
        "コンサート"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "コンサート"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'ちず'?",
      "options": [
        "うた",
        "ぶんがく",
        "ち ず",
        "よしゅう"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ち ず"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'suki'?",
      "options": [
        "winter holidays",
        "pen",
        "airport",
        "like"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "like"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'sonohoka'?",
      "options": [
        "しゅみ",
        "ようしつ",
        "そのほか",
        "うたいます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "そのほか"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'yoku'?",
      "options": [
        "class / lesson",
        "often",
        "hotel",
        "menu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "often"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'kontesuto'?",
      "options": [
        "れい",
        "あめ",
        "コ ンテスト",
        "ホットドッグ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "コ ンテスト"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'isu'?",
      "options": [
        "engineer",
        "chair",
        "to put on clothes",
        "tatami mat"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "chair"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'しつもん（を）します'?",
      "options": [
        "to ask a question",
        "interesting",
        "Tokyo",
        "(someone else's) elder brother"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "to ask a question"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ピアノ'?",
      "options": [
        "piano",
        "musume",
        "batsu",
        "washitsu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "piano"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Mekishiko'?",
      "options": [
        "メキシコ",
        "りんご",
        "みんな",
        "せつめい（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "メキシコ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'examination'?",
      "options": [
        "ホット",
        "たいこ",
        "しけん",
        "おっと"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "しけん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'card'?",
      "options": [
        "ジャム",
        "がっこう",
        "カード",
        "しょっき"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "カード"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to copy'?",
      "options": [
        "ばんごう",
        "ゆっくりします",
        "コピー（を）します",
        "〜に　いきます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "コピー（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'Mekishiko'?",
      "options": [
        "Mexico",
        "passport",
        "bedroom",
        "school"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Mexico"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'student'?",
      "options": [
        "ピアノ",
        "メキシコ",
        "がくせい",
        "ダンス"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "がくせい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'paathii'?",
      "options": [
        "パ ーティー",
        "おくさん",
        "おしょうがつ ／おしょうがつ",
        "ヨーグルト"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "パ ーティー"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'byooin'?",
      "options": [
        "hospital",
        "to go out",
        "calendar",
        "foreign language"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hospital"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'onna-no-ko'?",
      "options": [
        "しけん",
        "ゴールデンウィーク",
        "テレビ",
        "おんなのこ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おんなのこ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to go to 〜'?",
      "options": [
        "てんぷら",
        "ファーストフードてん",
        "〜に　いきます",
        "まど"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜に　いきます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ばつ'?",
      "options": [
        "shitsumon (o) shimasu",
        "batsu",
        "Nihonjin",
        "utaimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "batsu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Indo'?",
      "options": [
        "おとうと",
        "だんぼう",
        "あなた",
        "インド"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "インド"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'lots of (people) / crowded (with people)'?",
      "options": [
        "(hito ga) ooi",
        "suupu",
        "musume",
        "e (o kakimasu)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "(hito ga) ooi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'sushi'?",
      "options": [
        "osushi / sushi",
        "ninjin",
        "sukoshi",
        "okashi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "osushi / sushi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to work overtime / extra hours'?",
      "options": [
        "ざんぎょう（を）します",
        "いもうとさん",
        "かに",
        "シャワーを　あびます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ざんぎょう（を）します"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'dance'?",
      "options": [
        "pan",
        "okashi",
        "kissaten",
        "dansu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "dansu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'さむい'?",
      "options": [
        "fuku o nugimasu",
        "koohii",
        "tsuri (o shimasu)",
        "samui"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "samui"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'おそい'?",
      "options": [
        "subarashii",
        "tonari",
        "osoi",
        "furaido-poteto"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "osoi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'anata'?",
      "options": [
        "とうふ",
        "ドイツ",
        "おみやげ",
        "あなた"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "あなた"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kaishain'?",
      "options": [
        "to read",
        "to go out",
        "company employee",
        "(not) many / (not) much"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "company employee"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tea ceremony'?",
      "options": [
        "さどう",
        "あまい",
        "チラシ",
        "えいご"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "さどう"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'Nihongo'?",
      "options": [
        "にほんご",
        "ジョギング",
        "やまのぼり（を　します）",
        "かおを　あらいます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "にほんご"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'camera'?",
      "options": [
        "あたたかい",
        "そふ",
        "カメラ",
        "ビール"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "カメラ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'hiroi'?",
      "options": [
        "tempura",
        "big / spacious / large",
        "grapes",
        "to play the guitar / piano"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "big / spacious / large"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'name'?",
      "options": [
        "きょうかしょ",
        "ごしゅじん",
        "なまえ",
        "さむい"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "なまえ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'paathii'?",
      "options": [
        "sometimes",
        "lunch",
        "guitar",
        "party"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "party"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'I can speak (language)'?",
      "options": [
        "〜が　できま す",
        "しょうせつ",
        "はを　みがきます",
        "スパゲティ（パスタ）"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜が　できま す"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kotoba'?",
      "options": [
        "to read",
        "(someone else's) elder sister",
        "(not) at all",
        "language"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "language"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ibento'?",
      "options": [
        "(someone else's) wife",
        "to talk / to speak",
        "event",
        "Chinese language"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "event"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'hotel'?",
      "options": [
        "oishii",
        "soto",
        "chiisai",
        "hoteru"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hoteru"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'バター'?",
      "options": [
        "tea ceremony",
        "butter",
        "onion",
        "bookshelf"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "butter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'kyoodai'?",
      "options": [
        "bookshelf",
        "cereal",
        "school",
        "brothers and sisters"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "brothers and sisters"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for '〜 o moraimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "しゅふ",
        "そぼ",
        "〜を　もらいます",
        "かいわ（を）します"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "〜を　もらいます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'りょうり'?",
      "options": [
        "lots of (people) / crowded (with people)",
        "New Zealand",
        "amazing / wonderful",
        "cooking / dish"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "cooking / dish"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ばんごう'?",
      "options": [
        "tokee",
        "kaisha",
        "kyookasho",
        "bangoo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "bangoo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'だんぼう'?",
      "options": [
        "tsuma",
        "asobimasu",
        "danboo",
        "toofu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "danboo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'あたたかい'?",
      "options": [
        "warm",
        "sliding door",
        "office room",
        "name"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "warm"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'civil servant'?",
      "options": [
        "きょうしつ",
        "いそがしい",
        "おどります",
        "こうむいん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "こうむいん"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'コーラ'?",
      "options": [
        "telephone",
        "to play a game",
        "chopsticks",
        "cola"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "cola"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'いもうとさん'?",
      "options": [
        "suutsukeesu",
        "karee",
        "kissaten",
        "imootosan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "imootosan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'sushi'?",
      "options": [
        "びじゅつかん",
        "ポップス",
        "おすし／すし",
        "きゅうり"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おすし／すし"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'to read a newspaper'?",
      "options": [
        "しんぶんを　よみます",
        "ふゆやすみ",
        "でんわ（を）します／かけます",
        "ホテル"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "しんぶんを　よみます"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'こども'?",
      "options": [
        "floor cushion",
        "alcoholic drinks / Japanese sake",
        "Vietnam",
        "child"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "child"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'しょくじ（を）します'?",
      "options": [
        "osoi",
        "katudoo / ibento",
        "jagaimo",
        "shokuji (o) shimasu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shokuji (o) shimasu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'yoko'?",
      "options": [
        "あつい",
        "よこ",
        "えいが",
        "ふくを　ぬぎます"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "よこ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'French language'?",
      "options": [
        "Furansugo",
        "Supeingo",
        "kodomo",
        "keeyooshi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Furansugo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'ソファ'?",
      "options": [
        "lots of (people) / crowded (with people)",
        "to put on clothes",
        "department store",
        "sofa"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sofa"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Romaji for 'ベランダ'?",
      "options": [
        "〜 ya (san)",
        "yoga (o) shimasu",
        "ofuro",
        "beranda"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "beranda"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'goldfish'?",
      "options": [
        "え",
        "アフリカ",
        "きんぎょ",
        "がいこくじん"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "きんぎょ"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'tokee'?",
      "options": [
        "〜じん",
        "とけい",
        "むすめ",
        "インド"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "とけい"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'supagethi (pasuta)'?",
      "options": [
        "poster",
        "friend",
        "spaghetti / pasta",
        "meat"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "spaghetti / pasta"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hiragana/Katakana for 'ofuro ni hairimasu'?",
      "options": [
        "せんたくき",
        "ごしゅじん",
        "おふろに　はいります",
        "ばんごう"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "おふろに　はいります"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English for 'おみやげ'?",
      "options": [
        "ticket",
        "souvenir",
        "to relax",
        "warm"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "souvenir"
    }
  ]